(STATIC)
A tense new year
has dawned in Baghdad
after U.S. air strikes against
an Iranian-backed militia
led today
to one of the worst attacks
on a U.S. embassy in years.
(REPORTER 1): The protest was in
response to Sunday’s U.S. air strikes
against that same militia.
The U.S. blames the militia
for a rocket attack
that killed an American
defense worker.
And President Trump blamed Iran.
(STATIC)
(REPORTER 2): An elite
Iranian General is dead
and the United States and Iran
are closer to conflict.
Soleimani was personally
responsible
for some of the absolutely
worst atrocities.
(REPORTER 3): The President gave
the go-ahead to kill Soleimani
if Iran’s aggression led
to the death of any American.
America martyred our commander.
(REPORTER 4): You killed
our number-two guy.
We’re ready to surrender.
They’re not going to do that.
Death to America!
(IN FARSI):
(REPORTER 3):
52 Iranian sites
will be hit very fast
and very hard,
if Iran retaliates.
(TRUMP): Missiles fired
last night at us.
(REPORTER 5): The strikes
were in retaliation for
the U.S. drone strike
which killed Iranian General
Qasem Soleimani.
Recorded images of the 2-hour
missile barrage on Al-Asad base.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(IN FARSI):
After threats from the President
and military
of the criminal state of America
to attack many targets in Iranian territory
in case we retaliate,
our armed forces
are ready to respond.
(TRUMP):
Our missiles are big, powerful,
accurate, lethal and fast.
Urgent preparations are being
made for the President
to potentially address the
nation on these attacks tonight.
(WOMAN): Avoid all
non-essential travel.
We should update our viewers
and say that the President
does not appear to be
looking to make a statement
to the nation tonight
here at the White House.
(STATIC)
At 3 o’clock in the afternoon
on January 8th, 2020,
I was on my way
to the Pearson International
Airport in Toronto.
That was our plan.
The flight was supposed
to land at 3:00 PM
and I was going to pick them up.
I was supposed to park my car,
linger in the arrivals’ hall
with flowers in my hand.
(HAMED): Right around 3:00 PM,
I should be seeing Reera
tunning towards me
through the crowd
with a big smile on her face,
throwing herself in my arms.
I would kiss her
and hold her tight,
smell her hair,
and see Parisa walking
watchfully behind her,
timing her approach.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Parisa would be pushing
the luggage cart
with happy tears in her eyes.
I would hug and kiss her
and our family of three
would be whole again.
(INDISTINCT PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
(AIRPLANE CHIME)
(INDISTINCT PILOT
PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
(AIRPLANE CHIME)
The region is at heading 320.
Is it an active region?
(STATIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN FARSI)
(IN FARSI):
There are lights.
At heading 320?
(STATIC)
I can't tell, but it seems west.
What kind of a light is it?
It is a missile.
(STATIC)
How many miles? Where?
(EXPLOSION)
(WOMAN GASPING)
Oh my lord, what was that?
What is that, Mahdi?
(GASPS)
They attacked somewhere.
(STATIC)
(MAN): Ukraine
International 752 radar.
(STATIC)
Ukraine International 752 radar.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
(IN FARSI):
What were you doing that day?
It is difficult to talk
about it, but I will try.
Some parts I will, some I may not.
The day before, I cleaned up the house.
It was a work day,
but I cleaned the house.
I was cleaning the bathroom.
It is impossible for me
to talk about that day.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(BABAK):
On the morning of January 8th,
a friend approached me
and told me that
Hamed Esmaeilion
was on his way to Tehran
to bury his family.
He warned that there
might be trouble
and asked if I could help.
Hamed was a dentist
by profession,
but also an accomplished
rising star
in the contemporary Iranian
literary scene
with a few published novels,
some of them banned
by the Iranian Government.
(AIRPLANE CHIME)
(IN FARSI):
I got on the airplane.
Many passengers recognized me.
We embraced. Even the passengers.
I saw Javad and Alireza for the first time.
Saloome...
and Amir.
The four of us combined...
No, there were five of us.
We had lost ten people.
(BABAK): Within
hours, Canada’s Prime Minister
confirmed he had received
intelligence
suggesting that Iran
was responsible
for the lethal plane crash.
American officials reported
an Iranian anti-aircraft missile
shot the plane out of the sky.
Meanwhile, Iranian officials
swiftly rejected those reports,
claiming that the crash
was due to technical failures.
They are attributing
that this, uh...
so claimed mistake,
has been done by our military.
We are very clear
and confident about
our military and the missile,
if it has been in fact launched.
We are confident from our side
that there has been
no missile launched
in that area at that time.
Certainly no missile has hit it.
But we must investigate the reason.
(IN FARSI):
It is now
more important than ever
that we know exactly
how such a tragedy
could have happened.
(IN FARSI):
When we arrived
at the Iranian border,
there were media reports that
the plane was shot down.
(REPORTER):
Justin Trudeau speaking about
the Boeing plane
that crashed in Iran
killing 176, including
many Canadian citizens.
(TRUDEAU): We have intelligence
from multiple sources,
including our allies
and our own intelligence,
the evidence indicates
that the plane was shot down
by an Iranian
surface-to-air missile.
(REPORTER): Other officials
in Canada
are demanding that they
have access
not only to the crash site,
but also to any investigation
that takes place.
It remains to be seen...
I went to the rear of the airplane,
(IN FARSI):
to get some water.
Three men stood up on my way back.
They said,
"When you arrive in Iran...
there will be TV cameras.
The situation will be tense."
I told them I don't care
and won't talk to them.
We took the Firooz Kooh Road.
Parisa loved that road.
I couldn't see the mountains
and forests anymore.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(HONKING)
I only remember the screams.
Everyone was screaming,
"I miss them."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CRYING)
I raised my child so she would love Iran.
To feel she belongs to that country.
She was proud of being born
in Tehran.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
She said she is an Iranian-Canadian.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
It is difficult to spell.
The wolf bites?
Or the Fox is black. Is that hard?
Yes, it is very hard.
You hanger-on!
Bye-bye.
(SOFT MUSIC)
My friends suggested
to bury the girls in Iran.
My friend asked if I would bring them back.
So he can say goodbye.
I said no.
The thought of it is maddening.
We were not in a position to decide.
Or where they will rest in peace.
Someone who loves life can't rest in peace.
(SINGING)
We hadn't even discussed these things.
Maybe we had, I can't remember.
It was an hour before I heard
the Islamic Republic
admitted they shot the plane.
(REPORTER):
A top Iranian official
admits the Iranian people
were lied to about
the air disaster
that has left 57 Canadians dead.
It appears there was a
communications breakdown.
(IN FARSI):
Either due to jamming,
or the network was busy.
He was unable to communicate.
He had ten seconds to decide.
He could fire or not.
Contrary to claims
by the IRGC Aerospace
force commander
that the missile unit
had only ten seconds
to decide whether to fire,
it appears that the unit had
at least a 45-second window
and possibly even more time
to evaluate the target
and determine
the appropriate action.
(IN FARSI):
A thought flashed in
my mind like lightning.
If we bury them here,
they will be labelled
as martyrs.
Bury them where they want.
They will be present with their TV cameras.
Death to the US!
At that moment, we
decided to bring them back.
It became my mission.
It helped me to survive
those two weeks in Iran.
It became my reason to live.
Later, it became a fight for justice.
(PLAYING PIANO)
My dear Parisa, I fought hard.
With tearful eyes, a broken heart,
I fought for you.
I wandered the hallways of
their hellish foreign ministry.
I wandered in their wretched morgues.
I pleaded with everyone in that pigsty.
To bring you and Reera back.
To remove every obstacle in my way
and bring you home.
I feared that they would try to stop me.
They might arrest me or the other families.
They murdered and now oppress like always.
Some anonymous people
were watching.
There was so much fear.
Everyone was worried
my plan would be discovered.
I got a call around 5:00 AM.
The Canadian team arrived in Iran.
They told me that they were in Tehran.
We arranged to meet them
at 5:00 PM.
We talked about the meeting location.
They suggested to meet near Pars hospital.
They asked if I knew where it was.
Reera was born there.
I met them at 5:00 PM in front
of the hospital,
where we waited for Reera's birth.
We sat in a cafeteria nearby.
(SPEAKING IN FARSI)
I asked for three things.
First, Parisa and Reera
must be returned to Toronto.
Second, I needed help with my family.
Most of them had visas.
My brother and Parisa's brother didn't.
I asked for visas for
both of their families.
So they could attend the burial ceremony.
And my safety so I can do this.
They agreed to the first two.
But advised me to lay low.
That became my mission.
I kept contact with the
Canadian government.
They told me to hide myself.
I should stay home and they will help me.
The family held a memorial
in Sari. They had to.
That was also being watched.
It was like martial law.
There were agents across the street.
It was at the smallest mosque in Sari.
I did not attend.
When the victim ID list was released,
Parisa and Reera were
not among the first fifty.
I was very sad.
The first 50 must have
been easier to identify.
The day we went to
the coroner's office.
We found the place.
When we entered, the guard was rude.
"Is it the airplane? Go inside."
There was a commotion inside.
Dozens of people were crying.
I waited for the judge.
It took half an hour for this judge...
to grant us an audience!
There was a large table in front of him
covered in fruits and sweets.
Like a sultan's court.
Drinks, tea. A feast for his honour!
I sat across his desk like a peasant.
You have to accept your position
once you enter this establishment.
I said I am taking them to Toronto.
"Oh yeah! To Toronto?" he said.
"Alright."
As he was talking to me,
his finger was in his mouth
dislodging food!
A woman began to protest.
Her family calmed her.
The officials remained quiet.
They knew how guilty they were.
(CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
(REPORTER 1):
Vigils for the crash victims
soon turned
- into anti-government protests.
- (GUNSHOT, SCREAMING)
(REPORTER 2): Iran has turned
a wave of popular supporting
to a tide
of anti-government fury.
(HUBBUB)
DEATH TO THE LIAR
(IN FARSI):
I speak as a mourning family in grief.
As people who are like the walking dead.
I hold out my chest.
And plead to be arrested here.
Execute me right here.
After my child, I want no life.
(SOFT MUSIC)
I sensed that another country far away...
was mourning this loss together with us.
And this was giving me hope.
That I can pursue justice...
when I return to Canada.
(FREELAND):
This is Toronto’s loss.
This is Ontario’s loss.
And this is Canada’s loss.
(EHSASSI): Mothers and fathers,
sisters and brothers,
partners and children,
our hearts ache.
And we are all pained
to the core.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY IN FARSI)
(IN FARSI):
Madam, don't film.
It seems to be
the fate of people
in the Middle East to suffer.
Hundreds of Iranian youth were
shot on the streets of Tehran
for protesting corruption,
crying for freedom.
And their loved ones
were arrested
for mourning their loss.
I wanted to go to the
Canadian delegate's hotel.
(IN FARSI):
Stay with them even in the hallways.
To be with Parisa and
Reera on the same plane
because they will not allow
the transport.
(SOFT MUSIC)
We arrived in Toronto,
we were on our way
from the airport.
The house was all I had left.
(SINGING "HAPPY BIRTHDAY"
IN FRENCH)
(HAMED):
8, 7, 6, 5...
4, 3, 2, 1!
(CLAPPING)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you... ♪
(SINGING FADING OUT)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(BABAK): My understanding
of the word "pain"
changed when I locked eyes
with Hamed at his home
after burying the remains of his
wife and daughter in Toronto.
It was our first meeting
without a commotion around us.
I told him there may
never be the justice
that he and the other families
want and deserve.
But they should never give up
and keep fighting.
The COVID restrictions took hold
and we were left with late-night
phone conversations.
When we had a chance to meet,
I grabbed onto anything I could,
a pocket recorder, my phone,
or some camera,
to record what he was
going through.
Before I knew it,
a documentary was coming to life
without either of us
thinking about it.
One night, we both came
to the conclusion
that no matter
how hard it would be
to find the truth
and get justice,
I will document his journey.
This was the beginning
of an intense friendship
between Hamed and I.
A friendship that we both wish
would never have come about
under these circumstances.
(SIGHING)
(IN FARSI):
They are dried up.
I haven't collected
the letters yet.
They shouldn't get ruined in rain.
I didn't find the time to reply to them.
The flowers and candles.
I couldn't answer them yet.
I don't know when I can.
When?
I don't know if I should
leave them or take them?
(SIGHING)
(CRYING)
I am in agony.
And these thoughts increase my pain.
You want to hold on to the past.
But some things are more powerful than you
and bring you to your knees.
It is unbelievable.
It is twisted.
No one can explain how life changes.
The upstairs hasn't
changed since they left.
(PIANO MUSIC)
I am living every day with their memory.
I am fighting for them every day.
This is how I find the will to continue.
It is all in this house.
When I am away for a few hours...
I miss the house and must go back.
The first thing I wrote when I got out.
Those criminals, the
generals and mullahs...
I didn't let them reach
you and your daughter.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(WOMAN): Since
we’re living in the new age
of virtual press conferences,
I just...
My plan was to launch a lawsuit in Canada
(IN FARSI):
to seek justice.
I was going to fight alone...
And take this to the courts.
But meeting with lawyers,
that was a rude
awakening for me.
They said if I want the truth
and get justice,
the Canadian government must act
to petition the International
Court of Justice.
(WOMAN):
I’ll turn this over to Hamed.
(HAMED): Thank you for attending
our launch of
the Association of Families
of Flight PS752 Victims, today.
I’m Hamed Esmaeilion,
a Canadian citizen
of Iranian descent.
I lost my wife, Parisa,
and my 9-year-old
daughter, Reera.
(HAMED): Today marks
the 160th day since
Ukraine International Airline
flight 752 was shot down
with missiles fired
by the Iranian Revolutionary
Guard Corps.
176 passengers and crew died.
Among them, 29 children,
eight entire families
who have no one to represent
them here today.
The Association pursues
three principal goals:
Keeping the memories
of the victims alive,
supporting the families
of victims,
and most importantly,
seeking justice.
Our first demand
was to have a full investigation
on this atrocity.
(WOMAN): Thank you, Hamed.
(SIGHING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(IN FARSI):
Several months passed and nothing happened.
We tried to pressure
the government,
the foreign minister,
minister of transportation.
We were told that things take time.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
There is little room for hope.
But we must keep trying.
(STATIC)
What is it?
It's a missile.
We must know what happened.
Strange things happened
that night.
There is something about this flight,
that led to their attack.
I mean, there is a mystery
in this case.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
The most important thing is investigation.
We want to know what happened.
If they claim it was
"human error", what caused it?
Keeping the sky open wasn't human error.
They sent bulldozers on the first day.
They removed everything.
(TRUCK BEEPING)
(REPORTER):
All the evidence seems
to have been cleared up.
There are scavengers
picking the scene apart.
There’s no cordon.
There is no security.
Apparently, no investigation.
That’s no way to conduct
the aftermath
of a terrible plane
accident, is it?
Are we in fact relying
on the reporters
to have judgement about
a very technical issue?
(REPORTER): Why is the scene
being bulldozed?
Why do we have bulldozers out
there clearing the evidence?
Normally, you’d pick up
the evidence,
you’d map the area,
clear it off.
This is absolutely...
This is absolutely absurd.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN FARSI):
Madame, don't film.
Okay.
They robbed all of the valuables.
Without exception.
None of the victims'
valuables were returned.
The relatives can confirm that.
(REPORTER): Canada
is moving ahead today
in the investigation
into the flight 752 disaster.
The federal government
is demanding
a significant role in the probe.
And today, the Canadian
investigation moves into Iran.
Getting to Iran, especially
at that time and that moment,
wasn’t very easy.
We had to arrange visas, etc...
We had to go through flights
through other countries,
such as Turkey.
And then, also, arrange security
and assistance for our travels
as well too.
So, it was complicated.
It did certainly
take a few days.
I want to say three.
It might have been four.
The site of the disaster
is in Iran.
The evidence is in Iran.
The witnesses are in Iran.
And the people who are accused
are in Iran.
So nobody outside of Iran
has any direct access
to any of that.
That makes pursuing
a criminal investigation
from outside of Iran
very difficult.
The 752 case is not about air safety.
(IN FARSI):
There is no aviation safety issue
other than a military act
against a civilian aircraft.
There was no technical
issue with the airplane.
There was no air traffic
issue at the airport.
There was no radar or
air traffic control issue.
There was no technical
or air safety problem.
The only issue was that a military,
security system...
Positions an air defence battery
near the airport...
And that is where our story begins.
(CHAMPAGNE):
Iran has a path to choose.
Either they go to the path of
transparency and accountability.
Taking full responsibility.
When you say to the world
you take full responsibility,
that comes with consequences.
They submit to investigations.
We have a right to be present...
in any examination
of the black boxes.
We will not surrender them to others.
Once you’ve had a situation
where they deny that there was
any military involvement.
And then, they reversed
their position.
Then they bulldozed
the crash site.
Then they delayed
the black boxes.
And then, they intimidated
the families and harassed them.
And Canada repeatedly asked
for accredited status
in the investigation.
And Iran consistently
ignored that request.
You’ve got that pattern
of behaviour.
(BABAK): You asked
for accredited status.
What would it have given you?
I could have suggested
they do things,
suggest they release
information.
I could’ve had access
to much more information.
I could’ve asked
for other information
and they had to technically
give it to me.
But limited to that expert role,
and limited to just
requesting accredited
representative status,
I was in this weird
diplomatic holding.
In spite of the letters
that I sent personally
to the head of the AIB
and later on
to the Deputy Minister
of the Civil Aviation
Organization.
In spite of our asking
for a higher status,
in fact, they never answered me.
(BABAK): You were there
for four days.
I think it was
a little more than that.
(BABAK): How many times
did you ask
for accredited status?
- Every day.
- (BABAK): Every day?
I mean, it was
a regular conversation.
What does that mean? How much longer?
(IN FARSI):
Negotiations can't take forever.
There was a clear
promise from Iran to cooperate,
in terms of investigation.
And I think we do not
see enough.
We should do so much better
on that.
And I think such a delay
is a sign of disrespect
towards the grieving families.
We are in close touch
with the association of families
of the flight victims
here in Canada.
And I know
that Minister Champagne
spoke to them yesterday.
Think about the pain they are
going through without closure.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(REPORTER): A report from Iran’s
Civil Aviation Organization
said that air defense
equipment was misaligned
and incorrectly
identified the plane
as a hostile object.
We can speak to Hamed Esmaeilion
who is a dentist from Toronto.
Hamed, you’ve become
a spokesperson
for the victims’ families.
When you hear what
the Iranians have said
in terms of what happened,
does this bring
any sort of closure for you?
Not at all. This report
just raises more questions.
We have families from the UK,
from Sweden, from Afghanistan,
Iran and Canada.
And all of them are destroyed
with this delay
and with this mockery
of the conventions and
all the regulations by Iran.
I think the Iranian officials,
they just try to shape
the public opinion about that
and find a way
to obstruct justice.
The inconsistencies,
inaccuracies and gaps
in the official explanation
create a maximum of confusion.
And thus, seem to be contrived
to mislead in one of more ways.
As for the admitted mistake,
these indicate a reckless,
if not criminal disregard,
for standard procedures
and principle of precaution,
which should have been
implemented to the fullest,
given the circumstances
and the location of the unit.
Those explanations
also point to a deep failure
of the chain of command,
both civilian and military.
Indeed, on the basis
of the information received,
one may even question
whether there was an order
or implicit encouragement
by the chain of command
to the crew on the ground,
to apply lethal force,
without going through
standard procedures
and precautionary steps.
We know what caused the crash.
I mean, this is obvious.
Missiles were fired.
Do you believe it was
human error, as Iran claims?
No, I don’t.
(PHONE RINGING)
(MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello?
(IN FARSI):
Hello, how are you?
(SPEAKING FARSI INDISTINCTLY)
Mr. Esmaeilion, I have only 7 or 8 minutes.
No more,
so I will get to the point.
Okay, go ahead.
(SPEAKING FARSI INDISTINCTLY)
I have things to tell you.
It is up to you to believe me or not.
- Yes.
- I live in...
(BEEP!)
I don't need anything.
No need for money, or to come to Canada.
I have a friend...
(BEEP!)
He works in one of
Iran's intelligence organizations.
He told me things about that night.
He talked to me about that night.
About who they removed from the plane.
He had some documents with him.
I saw those documents.
Photographs from
the command centre.
The papers that were exchanged.
He had a lot of documents with him.
Why was he afraid to
show these to the media?
He said it's not just the Iranians,
the Russians are also after him.
I asked what the Russians
have to do with it.
It wasn't just the Iranians,
the Russians were involved.
He has a lot of documents
about the plane that night.
A lot of documents, a lot of information.
I can tell you that this person
is the black box of that night.
If you are serious
about the truth,
if you really want to know
what happened that night,
this person can give you
all that information.
In any court.
Let me add something else...
(SOFT MUSIC)
I was walking yesterday.
A woman approached me.
There was some small talk.
She had Reera's health card.
It's the only thing left
from Reera...
Was delivered to another family.
The only item.
Hello, how are you?
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Thanks. How did this reach you?
A friend gave it to me.
It's been a few months.
I couldn't reach you.
You had it for a few months?
Very kind of you.
This is the least I could do.
- Thank you.
- Anytime.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(CHILDREN PLAYING)
(CRYING)
In our case, every conceivable
crime has been committed.
Every filthy thing you can think of.
Even torturing family members.
They used the passengers as a human shield.
We believe they fired intentionally.
I will leave it to others to prove.
Every day they said
some nonsense on their TV.
From their leader to some petty officer.
Saying it was a spy plane,
we are happy we shot it down.
We want to stop a big war...
with a war.
This is our only option.
We had to surprise the enemy.
We had to deceive the enemy.
We had to be prepared for retaliation.
We took our game of war to the end.
This was not a battlefield where...
we think we would attack
and that will be the end.
Put yourselves in our place.
We hit the American base.
He claimed to target 52 points.
He reacts.
What do you do?
What will he do in return?
We were the source of
the theory ourselves...
that our missile might have been fired.
Only because it happened at the same time.
And if we were not the source...
for shaping this theory...
no one could find out.
We did not touch anything.
Neither removing the airplane pieces
nor disturbing the scene.
Nor moving the missile unit.
Neither the radar graphs.
I think, now,
the only hope that we have,
unfortunately,
is Ukraine’s criminal case.
Because, for some reason,
we haven’t decided
to join Ukraine
in the joint investigation.
For some reason, we haven’t done
enough in ICAO.
So, Michel, we don’t talk about
conspiracy theories.
Opening the airspace open
that night is a crime.
Bulldozing the crash site
is a crime.
Looting the belongings
of the passengers is a crime.
All of that should have been
addressed in ICAO.
But we failed to do that,
unfortunately.
And we talked to
Mr. Sciacchitano last week,
and when I asked him why he
didn’t address these issues,
he said Canada
hasn’t brought them up.
So he blamed Canada
for not acting
as a principal member of ICAO.
So then, in my opinion,
we have lost one year in ICAO.
And we already lost one year
in the criminal investigation.
So Ukraine probably is
the only hope
for the families now,
if we want to see
these criminals
in an international
court of justice.
We had a meeting with Ukrainian
officials last week as well.
And as a human rights
organization...
Because this association
is a human rights organization.
I just assured them that we are
not gonna sign any document
accepting an apology
or accepting compensation
from the Iranian Government.
If this road is going to end up
to compensation
and an apology from Iran,
we are not in.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(HAMED): Nine months
have passed.
On the morning of January 8th,
a Ukrainian airline carrying
176 passengers
was shot down near Tehran’s
International Airport.
We, the families of the victims,
are still alive.
And our only reason to live is
justice for our lost loved ones.
Let us all join forces and unite
in our belief in justice.
It will not bring
our loved ones back,
or alleviate
our eternal suffering,
but it shall serve
our dedication to the charter
of human rights.
How we can conduct ourselves
in the face of this crime,
how Canada sides its justice
shall be a historic milestone.
Let us make it yet another
milestone for us
to claim that Canada stood
on the right side of history.
Let us demonstrate
Canada’s steadfast dedication
to justice and dignity
of our fellow human beings.
We only live with this hope
in our hearts.
(BABAK): While Hamed and
the families around the world
were struggling to be heard
by the media,
public and political
institutions,
those in Iran
took to the streets,
despite the intense pressures
they were under.
(IN FARSI):
Down with the Islamic Republic!
Justice! Justice! Justice!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
The so-called statement has no legal basis.
And cannot determine the deadline.
If there is any will and intent...
for an impartial,
independent investigation...
based on the law and justice...
the judge must rectify
the shortcomings.
Justice! Justice! Justice!
Where innocent people come for justice...
they shut them up.
They won't let their voices be heard.
They don't listen to their protests.
The judge in charge is hiding.
The prosecutor lies.
The investigator secretly closes the file.
The families are
worried about the investigation,
that Iran is leading
that investigation.
We ask the international
organizations
or TSBs in Canada
if they can take over
or if they can supervise
what is going on.
We had the situation now where,
in accordance with Annex 13,
the state in which
the occurrence happened
has the right to lead
the investigation.
ICAO requires states to have
an independent safety
investigation authority to
investigate aircraft accidents.
(BABAK): Do you think
the air accident investigation
bureau of Iran is independent?
Not structurally.
Because the AAIB is part of the
civil aviation organization.
Which means it’s not independent
of the civil aviation
authority in the country.
To be independent,
it starts with,
not just legislation, but also
structural independence.
The rule that the country
where it happened
should lead the investigation
doesn’t work.
Because you’ve got a built-in
conflict of interest.
The country responsible for the
military that did the shooting
is the country
that’s responsible
for the investigation.
It’s a built-in conflict.
And you will never have
independence and impartiality
in which everyone can have
trust and confidence,
as long as you have
that built-in conflict.
Why should the government in Canada
go as fast as you want?
(IN FARSI):
What happened so far
was due to your persistence.
What would happen if we weren't there?
Without you they'd just offer compensation.
85 Canadians were killed.
Imagine they had no one.
Imagine we didn't exist.
What would you do if you were
Canada's Prime Minister?
(TENSE MUSIC)
(HAMED): I want,
you know, honestly,
I wanted to use this meeting
to send a message
to our Prime Minister.
As you say, all the time,
that all the options
are on the table.
I think, for someone like me,
I have other options
on the table too.
But my first option was waiting
for Canada to act on my behalf.
But we didn’t show
any teeth to Iran.
We didn’t.
And last week, they were rude
enough to say,
"We killed them,
good thing we did."
I prefer to go and stand beside
those poor fathers
and mothers in Tehran,
than to be in safe haven here,
just waiting for our government
to react to any of those
comments that they give
to the families.
I prefer to do that than wait.
But from day one, Mr. Goodale,
we said that Iran
is not gonna cooperate.
When we see the lawyers
of the government here,
they narrowed the reparations
to an apology and compensation.
What about the truth? Truth is
a big part of the reparations.
And we know that we won’t
get it from Iran.
We know that.
We are victims of terrorism.
And we have nowhere to go.
We have to just have meetings,
write letters. And...
I don’t know.
We are depressed.
We are losing our jobs.
We lost our family members.
And what’s next?
So...
You know, I can talk to you
until tomorrow,
but...
(CHUCKLING)
This is my life.
And I am not that kind
of person, who walks away.
I will stand until
the end of this.
And I will die for something
as valuable as justice.
(EERIE MUSIC)
(IN FARSI):
They told you their
neutrality prohibits them...
from responding to your call for justice?
Yes.
This is
the Communications Chief
of the ICAO,
answering to my interview
request for the documentary.
The neutrality of this
organization
prohibits them
from participating
to an interview
for a documentary
about air traffic safety
and flight PS752.
Is that what the world
has come to?
You want to talk to just...
I asked directly for
President Sciacchitano.
ICAO is the organization
which is responsible for
the safety of the skies.
So what happened here,
the International community
and other governments,
they handed over
the investigation
to the murderer.
This is a nightmare
for the families.
This will be
our nightmare forever.
Thinking about those moments.
I just want
to show you something.
This is a (BEEP!)
of a victim.
At the time that ICAO was not
condemning this crime,
this was happening in Iran.
It happened last February.
They lashed him.
And he lost his (BEEP!).
And he was in prison. He’s not
allowed to leave the country.
At the airport,
they downed the plane,
he’s not allowed to leave
the country.
This is the criminal
investigation they are doing.
And this is a picture
of my wife, her OHIP card.
It was found
on the crash site in July,
by a total stranger,
and was sent to me on Instagram.
- (BEEPING)
- (CLEARS THROAT)
(BEEPING)
(IN FARSI):
Hello.
- Hello.
- How are you?
Thank you.
I am calling about your message.
Yes, I am at your service.
There is background noise. Can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you. I am playing
prayers so I won't be heard outside.
Can you explain a little more?
There are two letters. There is a lot more.
About that incident.
But to start our work,
so you can find justice
or whatever else in court,
there is a voice recording
from Shamkhani on the night
of the incident.
He tells the aerospace commander...
when the mission is ordered.
Many people have contacted me.
I am responding one by one.
Put yourself in my place.
I must know...
I must see something.
I can send you an
extract of the first letter.
Because the rest is sensitive.
I will be in trouble.
You are helping us only for money?
I have money trouble. Yes.
I also don't want my
identity to be revealed.
You know what it's like in Iran.
Of course we need the original documents
to use them as evidence.
Of course. I will send you the originals.
No problem.
Very well. I will wait.
- I am at your service.
- Thank you.
Sounded like a military man.
Yes. Religious, military.
$75,000 is not much money to ask.
He is low-balling to lure you in.
It's not because he wants it.
I think he was low ranking,
nothing with authority.
Yes.
(HAMED): I don’t
want to get into details.
I understand the lines
are not secure.
I just want to tell you that
at least two people from
(BEEP!) contacted us.
But the RCMP didn’t show
any interest to check this.
They have the audio files.
They have everything.
When somebody from Iran
contacts me,
and says, "I want to talk to you
and I want to give you
this information,"
what should I do?
The best approach, I think,
is that somebody,
a liaison officer, or somebody,
or a team
just helping me,
or the other family members,
"Okay, this is
the way to do it."
Or, "We need this document
to prove that."
I am not an expert on this.
So that’s why it just puts
this duty on my shoulders
to go and find
the guy in (BEEP!).
Do you think that this letter
is valid, or not?
(IN FARSI):
Will they follow up?
- Will there be a criminal case?
- No.
At the end I said we will go to Ukraine.
- I said we will go to Ukraine.
- Okay.
She said, "Okay, go ahead."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
No one should know we are going to Kyiv.
Nothing to worry
about. Kyiv is a safe city.
The government officials
know about this trip.
There is nothing to worry about.
But no one should know until we return.
I liked this airport.
Now I hate all airports.
It took hold of me since
I entered the airport.
I must go on this trip.
I don't want to get on an airplane.
I don't want to anymore.
We are delayed by one hour.
Exactly like flight PS752.
You've been waiting 15 months
for this trip to Ukraine.
More than that, we wanted
to go since May 2020.
Then with COVID they
re-scheduled for December.
The visit was cancelled at the last minute.
Then they preferred to meet online.
We asked and waited for them to come.
The Canadian Government said no.
And we decided to go. We will go.
(INDISTINCT PILOT
PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
(HAMED): Even now,
the case is moving forward
to go to the International Civil
Aviation Organization.
It’s gonna go there,
but not because of
the first-degree murders.
In an ideal world, the next
morning that this happened,
there should be arrest warrants.
I don’t know.
A number of people
should have been arrested.
I know that nobody is in prison.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(STATIC)
(HAMED): Dear Mr. Esmaeilion,
let us express our gratitude
for your letter
and for your visit to the
Prosecutor General’s office.
Ukrainian prosecutors,
just as you,
are concerned
and will do their best
to establish the objective
truth in the case.
We’d be grateful
if you could provide us
with the information about
preferable time slots next week,
so we can move on
with organizational issues
and agree on a time and date.
We are looking forward to the
continuation of our cooperation
and the investigation
of the PS752 case.
Okay. We are going to have
a meeting with (BEEP!).
(BABAK): Mm-hmm.
(HAMED): GSR Committee
and some lawyers.
(BABAK): Hmm.
(HAMED): Uh...
And now, the third one,
a meeting with the
Prosecutor General’s office
with our lawyers.
(BABAK): This is within
the 24 hours
after your 24-hour
visit to Ukraine.
(HAMED): Yes.
Finally, the Ukrainian Justice ministry is
coming to Canada to begin investigations.
(IN FARSI):
I hired a lawyer when I was in Iran
to receive Reera and Parisa's belongings
if they delivered anything.
He sent me some photos later.
Keys, an iPhone and a watch.
He asked if I could identify any of them.
The phone had Parisa's name on it.
I immediately recognized
Parisa's Apple Watch.
Push the button.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Let it charge.
Did you see?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I need to know if she was alive...
during those 3 minutes and 42 seconds.
If the heart rate was
recorded on her watch.
(NIMA): Is there
any way we can find out
through my Apple ID on the web,
when was the last time
my Apple Watch was backed up?
I know it was two days before.
(IN FARSI):
- On the sixth.
- It was more than two days.
- This is the fourth.
- Here is the sixth.
That is not in Iran.
See if it powers on.
It came on for one moment.
This dilemma has started because
the original iPhone
is destroyed.
Will I be able to keep
my data on the Apple watch?
(TECH SUPPORT):
That’s what we don’t know.
Will it transfer
all of my health data
from my Apple watch without
activating a new Apple watch?
(TECH SUPPORT):
To be honest with you,
I think not...
(IN FARSI):
A faint light is on.
Let's see if it has historical data.
I can't see it on mine.
This couldn't happen in the crash.
I want to know if it comes on.
- Plug it in.
- I have once before.
We need to send it in for repair.
But if you send it in,
they make you sign...
Look it powered on.
- What do you mean?
- It shows 2:41.
The Iran time is 2:41 now.
What is the time in Iran now?
Yes, it is powered up.
Don't press on the screen.
Just move the knob.
- This one?
- Yes.
Come show me how.
- It moves up and down.
- Can you tap on it?
(SPEAKING IN FARSI)
The last message was mine.
She had another message too.
I can't tap the screen for messages.
Put the SIM card in your phone...
See if it is her phone or not.
I want to know if this
is Parisa's phone or not.
(SIGHING)
- It is like bringing the dead to life...
- It's backwards.
Call my number to see if it works.
(BEEPING)
- The card is not working.
- How can it be?
This doesn't belong to Parisa.
(SOFT MUSIC)
I don't know if it was me or Parisa...
It was me, Parisa didn't
ask these questions.
I asked where she wants
to be buried after death.
She said...
"Whatever Reera wants."
(WHIRRING)
When this disaster happened...
I had to answer this question myself.
Where and how.
Reera wasn't there for me to ask her.
But I knew what her answer would be.
It would be in Canada.
And because Parisa loved lakes
and the sea...
I searched to find somewhere near water.
Near a river or a lake.
Now it is near a small lake.
We chose that location.
The symbol on the site was
very important for me...
that it represents three people.
I think all three of us were destroyed.
Two of them left but the third...
is practically gone.
I wanted something beautiful
to be left behind on this earth.
One of them could be the grave site.
People should know about those...
whose lives were unjustly taken.
When I returned from Iran,
I searched her room.
I found her laptop. She didn't take it.
I haven't found the courage to open it yet.
What is the last thing she searched for?
What to write
inside a wedding card.
(IN FARSI):
This is her last search.
"Wishing you a
lifetime of love and happiness.
Your wedding day
will come and go,
but may your love forever grow.
Best wishes on this
wonderful journey
as you build
your new lives together."
(IN FARSI):
This was open.
"Add a phone number and email,
remind me later."
Her mail is open. My God.
(IN FARSI):
(SNIFFLING)
(LIGHT CLANKING)
January 6th.
(SPEAKING IN FARSI)
(CLANKING)
(SCRAPING)
(FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING
ON COMPUTER)
(LAUGHTER)
WINTER
REERA
PARISA
(CRYING)
(SIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CRYING)
(LAUGHTER)
(SNIFFLING)
(PLAYING PIANO)
(IN FARSI):
Remember when you and I began,
you said something that
I completely believe.
There is no justice.
What justice? What will satisfy me?
But it is worth fighting for.
That means if I...
wouldn't pursue this
as one of the families,
I could never forgive myself.
I couldn't, I had no other way.
What is the right way?
Other than crying
out in pursuit of justice.
But the lost right will never be returned.
Ordinary people are helpless...
in getting justice for their loved ones.
There is no light on the horizon.
But we should try, even
with a glimmer of hope.
If I will ever have
peace in my life again...
It is impossible. I don't believe I will.
Tranquility? What does it mean?
I don't know, peace and calm...
Maybe because I have not experienced it
for the past two, three years.
This word is strange to me... Peace.
It means coming home
with peace of mind,
to have things to look forward to.
To think about them and plan for them.
It is impossible for me to recreate that.
No. Never. I am sure.
Because two years have
passed with no change.
I think it will continue like this.
What I can see with the others,
it gets worse for some, but never better.
It stays the same.
(REPORTER): Hamed,
my condolences to you,
as always. It doesn’t matter
how many years pass,
I’m sure the pain is still
a big part of your life.
How has your heart
survived, sir?
Where is my daughter now?
She was supposed to be at
the school in grade 5 right now.
But she’s in a cemetery
in Elgin Mills.
And this is not right.
We deserve to know the truth.
I know I want to know
what happened
to my wife and my daughter.
(REPORTER): Hamed Esmaeilion
is the spokesperson
for the Association
of the Families
of flight PS752 victims.
(CRYING)
(SIGHING, SNIFFLING)
(SIGHING)
(SNIFFLING)
(COUGHING)
(SIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(REPORTER 1): Until early
this morning,
some here in Kyiv doubted
that he would do it.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(SCREAMING)
(REPORTER 2):
Russia has invaded Ukraine.
(REPORTER 3):
Exchanges of fire...
Full-scale invasion
of Ukraine...
The largest invasion
of a neighbouring
country in Europe.
(REPORTER 3): Russian troops are
closing in on the capital.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(OVERLAPPING NEWS REPORTING)
(REPORTER 4): Families
scrambling for safety.
(REPORTER 2): Putin chose
this war, he said.
Now he and his country
will bear the consequences.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(IN FARSI):
I'm reading the news from Ukraine.
Russia has connected Crimea to Mariupol.
They're sending troops there.
There's cholera in Mariupol.
They're opening 10
thousand war crimes cases.
They must investigate them.
There is no end in sight for the war.
Russia has occupied 20% of Ukraine.
War broke out just when
we were getting somewhere.
After 18 months of hard work,
finally convincing the Canadian government.
They weren't opening a criminal case.
The Ukrainian Justice Ministry
team finally arrived
on February 22.
War broke out within 48 hours.
It is not morally right for us to push
a country that has lost thousands...
to prioritize our case for 177 victims.
(SIGHING)
I will not give up.
I told them a hundred
times, I will say it again.
I will not give up.
Despite war, elections,
government change...
COVID, or anything else that may happen.
Every time we were knocked down,
we got back up again.
It happened many times
in two and a half years.
I will not give up.
(WIND BLOWING)
(SCRAPING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(BABAK): As tensions were
growing in the Middle East
in early 2020,
Iranian citizens were anxious,
especially those
who lived overseas.
The passengers of flight PS752
were concerned about disruptions
in their travel plans.
But most of them were unaware
of the outbreak of war
on the morning of January 8th.
176 passengers lost their lives.
They left behind hundreds
of their family members
and loved ones,
friends, associates
and colleagues,
whose lives were shattered
on the morning of January 8th,
as the ill-fated flight PS752
took off from Tehran.
They had no part in the regional
power struggle.
The Iranian Government chose
to keep the skies open
and withhold any information
from airlines
about the rocket attacks
they launched
on the American base
in Iraq at 1:20 AM,
just five hours before
their scheduled flight.
The victims’ families were faced
with extraordinary
circumstances.
Their ordinary lives
entangled in a web
of international diplomacy,
legal complexities,
politics and heartache.
Hundreds of lives suspended
in an emotional limbo
without answers
that appear to be the key
to finding closure
in their loss.
Every single one of the stories
represent a world of hope
lost in a universe of pain.
The closer I got to their grief,
the more helpless I found myself
in being able to understand
how one can survive such a loss.
None of the passengers
or their families
could have foreseen in their
wildest imagination
that they were to become
part of the tragic history
of the Middle East.
This desperate search
for the truth
has come face to face
with reality,
one that we, like the families
of the victims,
must live with for the rest
of our lives.
Only the truth may make
our lives meaningful.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(LIGHT BANGING)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
(STATIC)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(FAINT EXPLOSION)
(STATIC)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(SOFT MUSIC)