♪♪
[notification chime]
- No, I never said I was
the best to play with it.
I just said I was the best
to ever get away with it.
♪ ♪
♪ It's me.
♪ I could sell legs
to a mule. ♪
♪ I could sell red and
orange to a bull. ♪
♪ Ayy-yo, it's nasty crack,
cracking my sack, ♪
♪ getting my back!
♪ Like, how you rap niggas
gonna brag at your raps, ♪
♪ jacking my swag like that,
thinking you Nast like that, ♪
♪ knowing damn well
I get on the track, ♪
♪ and have asthma attack.
♪ Backflipping spaz like that,
fuck up Hollywood, see me, ♪
♪ and see we back to back
and backing Cadillacs. ♪
♪ That's what they
mad like that, ♪
♪ like why they spray
raps like that. ♪
♪ Yeah, that's all
facts, no caps. ♪
♪ You niggas fucking
shitting me? ♪
♪ Me and G, baby, you all
hear back to back, nigga. ♪
♪ Hollywood!
♪ Uh, yeah, all facts, no cap.
♪ Me and Gerald, Nast, ALLBLACK,
Harlem across the map. ♪
♪ Tell us who we
back on, Nast. ♪
♪ Chainlink, they
tap on that. ♪
♪ 10 of us might
have been deep ♪
♪ black on black.
♪ Listen, uh, I'm just doing
what I was born to. ♪
♪ They mad I keep on
fucking off cash, ♪
♪ I could afford to.
♪ $30K on St. Laurent,
I could Dior you. ♪
♪ Between me and Nast, the
body count is World War II. ♪
♪ One night in Atlanta I tapped
him just to be cordial. ♪
♪ Was feeling generous,
had her thinking ♪
♪ she could afford school.
♪ Dover Street in London,
spent 24, I had Floor 2. ♪
♪ I'm $250K any major
market I tore through, ♪
♪ why would I give a fuck
about your money? ♪
♪ Uh.
♪ It's bass for universe
around here ♪
♪ with billion dollar dummy.
♪ If I could make this
shit I would pack about ♪
♪ this whole money.
♪ Something in the water
in a big area, I swear! ♪
[laughs]
♪ Hey, it's something
that you never seen. ♪
♪ Hey--
♪ That's me, I could
sell legs to a mule. ♪
♪ I could sell red and
orange to a bull. ♪
♪ It's me.
♪
♪ Still going to make you do
what the fuck you do. ♪
♪ Thank you for
fucking with them. ♪
♪
♪ I tell a bitch like this,
that's the bitch you catch up ♪
♪ if you let them.
♪ I could sell Frosted Flakes
to Tony. ♪
♪ It's me.
♪ I could sell
legs to a mule. ♪
♪ I could sell red and
orange to a bull. ♪
♪♪
Paris: What happens when
12 strangers chasing fame
quarantine together
during a pandemic?
I'm your host, Paris Hilton,
and I'm so excited to present
"Trap Stars," the hottest
new show on television.
What's up, Trap Stars?
[all cheering]
Welcome to the Trap House.
[cheering]
There's only one rule
at the Trap House,
Trap Stars must isolate and
can't leave the mansion.
Sounds simple enough, right?
Lucas: I mean,
there's worse places
to be quarantining,
you know?
Lindsey: I'm used to going
out and partying and doing
all that fun shit, and
I just really hate being
stuck in the house.
[Tom sighs]
Deadass: I'm just having fun,
I'm here to do my--
[remote clatters]
[Tom sighs]
[ominous bass line]
Tom: Fuck you.
[sighs]
Bitch.
♪
[rain pattering]
[elevator clangs]
[bell dings]
♪♪
[glass clinks]
[Tom sighs]
[security door buzzes]
Lauren: Hey, I'm Lauren.
Mind if I take this off?
Tom: Yeah, you're good.
[Lauren chuckles]
Come on inside.
[ominous music continues]
[door closes]
Lauren: You know, I don't
usually do this dating app
thing and go over to
random guys' houses.
Tom: You're not
nervous, are you?
Lauren: Nervous?
Tom: Nervous, yes.
♪
♪ La-la, la-la.
♪ La-la, la-la--
Lauren: It's nice
to meet you, Tom.
Tom: And it's nice to
meet you too, Lauren.
Lauren: Mm-hmm.
[wet kisses and soft breaths]
Lauren: Wait.
Tom: But I don't like to wait.
Lauren: Mm-hmm.
But get comfortable.
Tom: Yes, ma'am.
Lauren: I'll be back.
Tom: Okay, I'll,
I'll do just that.
[cloth rustles]
[Tom exhales]
♪♪
[exhales]
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello.
Hello?
Yo, who is this?
[glass slams]
Hello!
Hello?
[echoes back]
Is somebody here?
Yo, Lauren, you all right
in there?
Lauren: Yeah, I'll be out
in a minute!
Tom: Hello?
[echoes back]
♪♪
Tom: Lauren, lock
the fucking door!
[water rushes from tap]
[knife shwings]
[Tom gasps]
Tom: Come out, you pussy!
Lauren: God, dude!
[Tom chokes]
[grunts and clatters]
[camera clicks]
[grunting and choking]
[grunting and coughing]
[metal clatters]
[Tom groans and gasps]
[wet thud]
[heeled footsteps]
Lauren: Tom?
Tom, stop fucking around.
[elevator clatters]
What the fuck?
[blood squelches wetly]
[Lauren screams]
♪♪
[SUV honks]
Vicky: Yo, dude!
What's up, dude?
Stacy: You have to drive,
I'm too hung over.
Vicky: Are you
fucking serious?
Stacy: Yeah, man.
Vicky: Oh my God.
[Stacy groans]
Stacy: I'm so
fucking nauseous.
And I'm sorry for
making you isolate.
My roommates are mad
paranoid about COVID.
It's only a week, though.
Vicky: No, I get it, I mean,
I just came from New York.
It's like fucking
Chernobyl over there.
Stacy: Hey, let's just get
this out of the way.
I feel really responsible
for your break-up.
Vicky: No, babe, please don't.
Stacy: No, honestly, I mean,
if I had known your boyfriend
would just break up with
you and throw you out for
webcamming, I mean, I would
have never told you about it.
Vicky: No, babe, honestly,
it's not your fault.
He's literally trash.
Look, I was broke and you gave
me a solution, so I'm over it.
Stacy: You know what?
That's the right
mindset, babe.
Vicky: Plus it was kind of
fun, fulfilling fantasies.
Stacy: You remember my
roommate Desi, you know,
the one from freshman year?
Vicky: Uh-huh.
Stacy: Okay, I heard
that she's on 18 &amp; Over.
Vicky: She's webcamming?
Stacy: Yeah, man.
She was on that shit
fingering herself,
making out with her roommate,
taking naked showers,
doing tons of crazy shit.
Anyways, that bitch is making
$40K a month doing that shit.
Vicky: $40K?
Dude, I can't just go on there
and do crazy shit like that,
do you know what I mean?
Like, I usually just fucking
lay around in lingerie
and try and look sexy.
Stacy: Just get
a little naked,
show a little bit of ass.
I mean, you have nice tits.
It's a no-brainer.
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: You know what?
You're right, I'm just going
to spend the next week
webcamming and making some
money so I don't have
to keep couch surfing.
Aw, he's so cute.
Stacy: That's the
neighbors' kids.
You're definitely not
in New York anymore.
[Vicky chuckles]
♪♪
Stacy: My grandfather was
really into hunting,
in case you can't tell.
Vicky: It's definitely a vibe.
Stacy: All right, here's some
numbers you're going to need.
Sheriff Rodgers,
she's really nice.
She's actually really cool,
I hope you get to meet her.
But I hope you never
have to meet her,
you know what I mean?
[laughs]
Vicky: Okay, you're a
fucking idiot, continue.
Stacy: Okay, all right,
second, Kim and Max Daniels.
They live next door,
they're really cool,
young couple, whatever.
You saw their kids earlier.
And like I said, they're
your only neighbors
for like 17 miles,
there's nobody here.
Call me if you need anything.
Vicky: I will.
Stacy: See you in a week.
Vicky: Bye, dude.
♪♪
[windchimes tinkle,
birds sing]
[windchimes tinkle]
Paris: Meanwhile, on the other
side of the mansion--
Chy: But yeah, he just did not
want to fucking commit to me.
Like, I'm like, yo, I love
you, do you love me back?
The fight over the
video games was crazy.
Kim: We're all just
partying, having fun.
Spence walks in trying to,
like, get her attention.
Spence: It's, it's between us.
Shannon: Come take a shot,
come do a shot!
Spence: It's just--
Kim: This, like,
pissy fucking mood.
Spence: Really?
[Shannon screams]
Shannon: What! What the
fuck is wrong with you?
Spence: You turned off my
PlayStation, didn't you?
Shannon: Hitting me
in front of everyone?
Are you serious?
Paris: That was so beyond!
Shannon: Just go, just go!
Spence: I'm out of here!
Shannon: The fuck!
Kim: Oh my God.
Lucas: Did you really turn his
PlayStation off, though?
Chy: Is that the point?
Lucas: No, I'm just saying,
I'm just saying!
Chy: Is that literally
the point?
Kim: Why don't you go
fucking join him?
Just join him.
[all yelling]
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: What a fucking moron.
- Oh my gosh, what is
wrong with these men!
Are you kidding me?
[power clicks off]
Vicky: Shit!
[plastic buttons clicking]
Fuck me.
[clattering]
[footsteps]
[wind gusting]
[branches creaking]
[clicking breakers]
- So, I love Lindsey.
[door creaks]
- Right now...
- I would say Shannon.
I--
[footsteps]
[notification chime]
- Hey, what's your name?
Take your top off.
[notification chime]
- You're so beautiful.
- Oh my God, you are worth
every fucking dollar.
[notification chimes]
- I, I love you in that wig.
[notification chime]
- I want to get to know you,
like, in a real way.
- How did you get that body?
- You're so special.
[notification chime]
- Babe, I want to see your tits
so fucking bad, please.
[notification chime]
♪♪
[telephone rings]
Vicky: Hello?
Stacy: So, you survived
your first night?
Vicky: Ugh, barely.
I literally feel like
I'm losing my mind.
Stacy: And you just
got there, relax.
So, what are you up to?
Vicky: Oh, you know,
just been webcamming.
[laptop rings]
I just got another one.
Ugh, God, it's that tape guy.
Do you remember I was
telling you about him?
Stacy: Yeah, that weirdo who
puts tape before his camera?
Freak.
Vicky: God, I don't know if I
can deal with him right now.
Stacy: Isn't he your
biggest client?
Suck it up.
Vicky: He kind of went
crazy on me last time.
He takes this role playing
shit way too serious.
Stacy: Whatever,
who gives a shit.
It's not like you're going
to ever meet him anyway.
♪♪
Baby, I thought I'd
never see you again.
ONLY14U: Sorry
about last time.
I g-got a little carried away.
You just felt so distant.
Vicky: I'm sorry, daddy.
ONLY14U: I need to
be able to trust you.
Vicky: How can I make
it up to you?
Tell wifey.
♪♪
[Vicky groans]
ONLY14U: Oh my God.
[exhales]
I got you a ring.
I want you all to myself.
Vicky: Put your money
where your mouth is.
I love pleasuring my husband.
[ONLY14U groans]
ONLY14U: I love it when
you call me your husband,
but now I need
you to prove it.
Make me a video, just for me.
Vicky: I'd love to.
[swing chains creaking]
- Follow me, I love
my followers.
Make sure you follow me
on social media @ben.
Let's go!
Don't vote me out.
America, what's good?
[television chatter]
- I take this quarantine
really, really seriously,
so I'm just trying to set
the tone and, you know,
be a good example.
[television chatter]
- I want to prioritize my--
[Vicky sighs]
[floorboard creaks]
♪♪
[windchimes tinkle]
[door slams]
♪♪
♪ No matter what,
Can never play myself. ♪
[Vicky sighs]
[telephone dialing tones]
Stacy: Hey, it's Stacy.
Leave a message.
Or don't, whatever.
[beeps]
Vicky: Are you ignoring
me because you're having
mind-blowing sex
with your boyfriend?
You lucky bitch.
I'm here all alone without
any Wi-Fi and I'm starting
to get really
fucking horny.
[knocking on door]
Handyman: Somebody
call the handyman?
♪ Will you be my drugs,
Will you be my therapy? ♪
Okay.
♪♪
[coffeemaker percolating]
[heavy footsteps]
♪♪
Vicky: Hey, do you want
some coffee or anything?
Handyman: Oh, I'm all right,
sweetie, thank you.
Appreciate it, though.
Are you, you all
alone up here?
Vicky: Yeah, unfortunately.
Handyman: Must
get lonely, huh?
So, where are you from?
Vicky: Near here.
Handyman: Really?
You don't look like
you're from here.
Vicky: Well, I mean, I've
been living in New York
the last couple of years.
Handyman: Oh, cool.
So, it looks like your
cable got cut here.
I'm going to have to come back
in a couple of days,
run some wire.
I put these temporary
guys in here,
it should help with
your Wi-Fi for now.
Vicky: Wait, okay,
so, the line got cut.
Does that mean that
someone did that or...
Handyman: Around here?
No, no, it was probably
just some curious animal
or something, you know?
Lot of creatures around here.
Anyway, we'll get you
set up, you'll be fine.
Vicky: Okay.
[tools clanking]
[windchimes tinkling]
Handyman: So, uh...
you want anything else?
Vicky: No, just want
to get that fixed.
Handyman: Well,
I'll see you soon.
Chy: I think Lucas is cute.
Shannon: A slick back,
and he can dress!
Lindsey: If I had to guess
who has a crush on me,
maybe it might be Deadass?
Deadass: I feel like
making my move on Lindsey.
Lindsey: He does look
over at me pretty often,
and every time I go to the
bathroom he's kind of,
like, within 20 feet.
I think he likes
to hear me pee.
Deadass: I've been working
on a piece all day.
Lindsey: Oh yeah,
anything good?
Deadass: Yeah, um...
actually, I've been
making stuff about you.
Lindsey: How, how
old are you, anyway?
Deadass: I look older without
my glasses on, but, you know,
I kind of look
young right now.
Lindsey: Oh really?
Deadass: Yeah.
Lindsey: You look older
without your glasses on.
I'll take them off.
Deadass: I kind of want
to kiss you right now.
♪♪
Lindsey: I just made
out with Deadass,
and it wasn't as bad as
I thought it would be.
He was a little smaller
and I wasn't used to it,
but he wasn't bad.
Deadass: I know she's
in love with me.
Lindsey: Wait, you
forgot your glasses.
[laptop rings]
[water splashing]
Jazzy Lou: Vicky,
Vicky, my love!
Vicky: Jazzy!
[notification chime]
Oh, thank you
for the donation.
So, how are you?
How's the wife?
Jazzy Lou: Well, I got to tell
you, be honest with you,
I mean, this whole
isolation trip, I mean,
we've been fighting
all the time, man.
I mean, I don't even
know what to do anymore.
I mean, I feel invisible here.
Vicky: It's going to work out.
People are going crazy
in quarantine right now.
And you know why
she'll come around?
Because look at you, you
are one handsome man.
Jazzy Lou: Oh, come on, you
didn't have to say that.
But enough about me, I want to
know what's going on with you.
Vicky: I'm fine, just want
this year to be over.
Jazzy Lou: So, so,
did you move out?
Vicky: Yeah, I moved home.
Jazzy Lou: Well,
I'm really sorry.
It hurts me to see you sad.
You know I'm a fan, right?
Or a friend.
[laughs]
Listen, I got to start dinner
because my wife doesn't cook.
I'll see you later.
[clattering]
[notification chime]
♪♪
[Vicky moans]
[moaning]
Vicky: I want you so bad.
[rock music plays]
♪♪
[knocking on door]
[muffled music]
♪♪
Vicky: Yo.
[Pizza Boy screams]
Sorry about that.
Pizza Boy: Oh, Jesus
fucking Christ,
you scared the shit
out of me.
Vicky: Sorry.
Pizza Boy: It's, it's
going to be $21.50.
Vicky: All right.
You know what, just,
here, keep the change.
Thanks for coming
all the way out here.
Pizza Boy: Say, I kind
of got to take a leak,
you know what I mean?
You mind if I use
your bathroom?
Vicky: Dude, come on, can't
you just piss in the woods?
Pizza Boy: Can I piss
in the woods?
Do I look like an
animal to you?
[Vicky scoffs]
Vicky: You know what,
fine, just hurry up.
[Pizza Boy groans]
[water tinkling]
Pizza Boy: Hey, you know,
I think I've heard
about this place before.
Vicky: What?
[ominous tone]
[toilet flushing]
Pizza Boy: Yeah, this is
definitely the place.
Vicky: Okay, what are
you talking about?
[Pizza Boy groans, sighs]
Do you mind?
[Vicky scoffs]
Pizza Boy: Mm, you don't
have COVID, do you?
Vicky: Dude, no.
Pizza Boy: Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah.
Rumor has it, about 20 years
ago a guy marches into town,
breaks into this very
house and tortures
this fucking family
for about two weeks.
He was playing mind games,
tormenting them.
Real sick individual,
you know?
Finally, once he gets
his rocks off,
he sits the parents down
and forces them to watch
as he chops up the little
kids into bits and pieces.
I mean, some real fucking
Buffalo Bill shit.
I mean, I'm surprised you
haven't heard about it.
Vicky: Are you sure
it was this house?
My friend's family
has had this place--
[cell ringing]
Pizza Boy: Hello,
Sorriso's Pizza.
Oh yeah, Mr. Burns,
I'm already in the car.
I'll see you soon.
I got to split, but thanks
for the hospitality.
Vicky: Hey, are you
sure it was this house
the family was killed in?
Pizza Boy: Hmm, it might
have been a few towns over.
Thanks for the tip.
Yeah, I'm on the way, man.
I told you, 30 minutes
or less, I promise.
Bye-bye.
This fucking guy.
What the fuck is that?
♪♪
[grunts]
Vicky: Whoa!
What the hell, dude,
what are you doing?
Sheriff: Sorry, didn't
mean to scare you.
I was calling after you and
you had that shit in your ears,
you couldn't hear me.
Jesus Christ.
I'm Sheriff Rodgers and this
is my nephew, Deputy Wayne.
Deputy: Ma'am.
Sheriff: He's a rookie cookie.
He's just in training.
So, what are you doing
up here in these parts?
Do you know the Stewarts?
Vicky: Yeah, I'm staying
there for the week.
What are you guys
doing out here?
Sheriff: Well, we were heading
over to the neighbors
and saw you running like
a God damn gazelle.
Just wanted to make sure you're
not running from something.
Deputy: Getting eaten
alive out here.
Vicky: Is, are the
neighbors okay?
Sheriff: You know, we're going
to check on the neighbors
because their relatives
were calling us
saying they couldn't
get a hold of them.
So, just checking in.
Vicky: All right, well,
I hope everyone's okay.
Sheriff: You know, we should
probably get you back.
We'll drive you.
Getting dark.
[handcuffs clink]
Deputy: You know, they recently
found a young girl's body
not too far from here.
They found a dozen other bodies
killed the same exact way
all across the country.
Real gruesome.
They're calling him
the Crowbar Killer.
And all his victims were young
females around your age.
First he kills
everyone around her,
then he saves her for last.
Well, actually, I think
we're dealing with
a classic serial killer.
Sheriff: Would you
cut that out?
You're scaring the
bejesus out of her!
Vicky: Wait, wait, wait,
why is my door open?
Sheriff: You two
stay in the car.
[door thunks]
[wind gusting]
[night bird calls]
[locks click]
[woman screams]
Vicky: Wait, did
you hear that?
Deputy: Whatever,
she said stay in the car.
Hey, where the fuck
are you going?
Vicky: Dude, if she's in
trouble, we have to help her.
Come on!
[doors slamming]
Do you have a gun?
Deputy: Fuck no, they
don't give me that shit.
Vicky: Fuck!
♪♪
[clicking and pinging]
Come on.
[pinging continues]
Sheriff?
[pinball game pings]
Deputy: Fuck this shit,
I'm getting out of here.
Vicky: Oh!
Deputy: Oh shit!
[Sheriff laughs]
Sheriff: Relax, it's me!
Vicky: That is so not funny.
Sheriff: Oh, come on,
come on, that was funny.
Deputy: Jesus Christ, you
nearly scared my sac off!
Sheriff: Yeah, I should
have listened to your mom,
you are not
cut out for this.
Vicky: Okay, stop!
Who was in my house?
Sheriff: I checked the house,
the house is secure.
I think your door just blew
open from a gust of wind.
Vicky: Oh, that's
real comforting.
Sheriff: I mean, your
lock's pretty old.
Let's go.
Deputy: Happy Halloween.
Sheriff: Make sure you
get that door fixed.
[motor rumbles]
Jazzy Lou: Here we go!
Vicky: Do I just start
going back and forth?
Jazzy: You go
back a little bit,
you go forward
a little bit.
Vicky: Like this?
Jazzy Lou: Turn to your right.
Beautiful!
Vicky: Is that it?
Jazzy Lou: Now you're talking.
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: You're really good!
Jazzy Lou: And now get ready,
make believe you're holding
my hand right here.
Vicky: Okay, but don't
drop me, all right?
Jazzy Lou: Turn to your right!
Yes.
It's all hips, all
hips, all hips.
[laptop rings]
There you go.
Vicky: Um, hey, Lou, I had a
blast, but I have to go, okay?
Jazzy Lou: Okay, but I'm
going to keep dancing,
because once Jazzy is
lit, I'm good to go.
Vicky: All right, bye.
Jazzy Lou: Peace!
[notification chime]
Vicky: Hey, baby.
Just give me two seconds, I'm
going to go get ready for you.
ONLY14U: Hurry up, your
husband's in a spending mood.
[breathing]
Oh my God.
[breathing continues]
You're so beautiful.
I n-n-need you to
make me another video.
Vicky: Did you like
my last video?
Or was the mask too much?
ONLY14U: I n-need you to
do it again, without the mask.
I need to see your eyes when
you tell me you love me.
Vicky: But you
already know that.
I love my future husband.
Show me.
Put your money
where your mouth is.
ONLY14U: How much will
it take to make you mine?
Vicky: Mm...
This much?
ONLY14U: I can't wait
to put this ring on yo--
Vicky: Fuck!
[wind gusting]
[breaker clacks]
[door closes]
[rustling]
[footsteps]
Fuck!
Sheriff, it's me, Vicky.
You were in my cabin earlier?
There's someone
outside of my house.
Sheriff: Okay, go hide
somewhere safe.
I'm headed over.
Vicky: Okay, but how long
is this going to take?
Sheriff: About 30
minutes, go hide.
Vicky: Please, please,
please hurry!
Max: Hey.
[Vicky screams]
Fuck, what the fuck!
Vicky: Who are you?
Max: I could ask
you the same thing!
Vicky: I said, who
the fuck are you!
Max: I'm their neighbor,
okay, Max Daniels.
Vicky: Oh my God,
you're the neighbor.
Max...
I am so sorry.
You were in the house--
Max: I'm sorry,
the door was open,
I thought they were here.
I...
oh my God.
I was hunting yesterday,
I heard music coming
from the cabin.
I just figured that
Stacy was in town and...
Actually, that's why I came.
We like to smoke together.
Don't judge.
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: Well, I could definitely
use a joint after that.
Oh my God, oh my God,
I am so sorry.
I'll, I'll r-roll one up
while you get changed.
Vicky: Okay.
Really sorry about that, Max.
I'll get something
for that cut.
Max: Shit!
[notification chime]
[laptop rings]
Vicky: Hey.
All right.
Let's get that cleaned up.
[Vicky sniffles]
[Max hisses]
I know, I know, I know.
It's almost over, I'm sorry!
There, is that better?
[Max snorts]
Max: Yeah.
Vicky: I'm sorry for
slashing your face.
Max: It's okay.
Vicky: Ugh, I've
just been paranoid.
I mean, I met these cops
earlier today and they were
telling me about that
girl who got killed
not too far from here.
You know, the Crowbar Killer?
Max: Oh yeah, is that what
they're calling him now?
Vicky: Yeah, I guess.
I hope they find him.
This year can't
get any crazier.
Max: I hear that.
[joint sizzles]
- Because they're out
of control.
[Kim screams]
Kim: The pool guy
has drowned!
- Oh my gosh, oh my
gosh, oh my gosh.
Lucas: I couldn't
give him CPR.
He goes to a lot of pools,
I don't know if
he has COVID or not.
Max: Is this real?
Vicky: Yes, and I'm, like,
the biggest fan of it.
Hey, I saw your kids
the other day.
They were really cute in their
little Halloween costumes.
Max: Yeah.
Unfortunately, they're gone.
Vicky: Gone?
Max: Yeah, my ex has them
for the next two weeks.
Vicky: Oh, right.
Max: We split up
about six months ago.
Vicky: I'm sorry.
Max: Oh God, I'm
killing the mood.
[knocking at door]
Vicky: Oh, fuck.
I have to handle that.
Sheriff: Everything
okay, ma'am?
Vicky: Yeah, yeah,
everything is fine.
Sorry for the false alarm.
Sheriff: You sounded pretty
scared on the phone.
Vicky: No, no, no,
I know, umm, I'm fine.
Sheriff: Mind if we take
a look around?
Vicky: I've actually,
I have company.
Sheriff: You have company.
I don't see any
cars out here.
Deputy: Wait, are you
fucking the neighbor?
[Vicky scoffs]
Vicky: Look, you guys, I,
I'm really sorry for making
you come all the way up here.
Sheriff: Well, you tell your
friend to call his family.
They're worried about him.
Vicky: Yeah, of course.
Bye.
Sheriff: Home wrecker.
Max: Everything okay?
Vicky: Yeah, yeah,
everything's fine.
I just panicked earlier
and called the cops.
But they're gone now, so.
Max: Well, it's
getting late,
I should probably
be heading back.
Got to feed the doggo.
Vicky: Oh.
Okay.
Thanks for the hang.
Have a good night.
Lindsey: I was so nervous
when Paris called
the meeting for the house.
Paris: Hey, guys.
All: Hi!
Paris: I bet you guys are
wondering what I'm doing here.
- Yeah.
Paris: Lindsey's boyfriend
just got released early
from prison because of COVID and
he will be joining our cast.
Lucas: Lindsey has a boyfriend?
Chy: Lindsey has a boyfriend?
[motorcycle engine revs]
Lucas: Why is he smashing
that ass, then?
Lindsey: Baby!
Oh, I'm so happy
you're out of prison!
I'm a little bit worried
about what might happen
between Deadass
and my boyfriend.
Paris: Welcome to
the Trap House.
Deadass: Why would
she lie to me?
♪♪
Paris: Stay tuned for more.
♪ Looking at my phone,
Nowhere to go. ♪
Tracy: Hey, just
checking in, bitch.
You're probably bored
as fuck out there.
I left you something I scored
off of some bros in San Fran.
It's in the kitchen.
Just three more days and
I'm picking your ass up.
♪ Oh, every time I
open up my eyes... ♪
♪ It's a nightmare.
♪ I wish that you
were right there. ♪
♪ I try to hold back
the tears I cry. ♪
Spence: The fuck is this?
This is, this is disgusting.
Chy: I literally wanted
to fucking strangle him.
Spence: Yeah, I would like to
order a large pizza, please.
Chy: Are you fucking--
Paris: They actually
have really good pizza.
Even if it smells good,
just eat it.
Like, you're going to
order pizza
right after this beautiful--
[ATV motor rumbling]
Vicky: Hello?
Max: Come on, I brought
an extra helmet.
[Vicky chuckles]
♪♪
[motor revving]
♪ Think you love me,
tell me I'm your girl. ♪
♪ Oh so quiet, in my
own little world. ♪
Max: It was fun,
though, right?
Vicky: Dude, you drive
really fucking fast.
Max: That's half the fun.
Here, let me take your coat.
Vicky: Oh, okay, thank you.
Max: I'll make us a drink.
Vicky: Okay.
You have a really nice place.
Max: Thanks.
You want ice?
Vicky: No, I'm good.
Max: You know, I feel like
such a bad influence,
first with the weed,
now with the booze.
It's a stiff one.
Vicky: I can take it.
Wow, this is delicious,
what is this?
Max: Well, since the split,
I've really got into
different craft drinks.
I'm no mixologist, but thanks
for being my test dummy.
It's called a
Downhill Daring.
Vicky: Hey, think fast.
[football thumps]
[scoffs]
Buddy, I thought that
you played football.
Max: I did, I was the kicker.
Vicky: Ah, got it.
[Max snorts]
Cassius: Feeling tense, huh?
[Max and Vicky laugh]
Vicky: I honestly can't believe
that you watch this.
Max: Ever since you showed me,
I've been hooked.
I mean, these people
are so insane.
Vicky: I know, I'm addicted.
[Max laughs]
Vicky: Hey.
Max: That's a good boy.
Come on, get out of
here, leave her alone.
Go, go, go.
Vicky: Aw, he's so sweet.
Max: He is.
[Vicky sighs]
Vicky: Wait, who is
this with your kids?
Max: That is my ex and the man
who is now sleeping with her.
Vicky: I'm sorry,
I'm being nosy.
Max: No, no, it's okay.
I leave it out for when
the kids come to visit.
You know, I want them to think
that we're all okay, you know,
that I'm happy for their
mom and her new boyfriend,
when I'm really not.
Son of a bitch took
my wife, my kids.
That's why I got Jason,
so I wouldn't be alone.
Vicky: And I'm not trying to
be insensitive by any means,
but just, six months to already
have a new boyfriend, it's--
Vicky: Well, she signed
the papers six months ago.
This nightmare has been
going on much, much longer.
Can we not talk about my ex?
Vicky: I'm sorry, I'm being
totally fucking annoying.
Max: It's okay.
Vicky: I'm a little drunk.
I just want to say
that I hear you.
My ex and I, we recently
split, as well.
And on top of all of that, he
kicked me out of our place, so.
Max: Wow.
You want to talk about it?
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: No, definitely not.
Max: Okay.
So...
what do you want
to talk about then?
Vicky: It's just been so weird
with Corona and quarantine
and moving from New York,
going through a break-up.
I just feel like my
life is falling apart.
But now I'm finally starting
to feel like myself again.
Max: Amen to that.
♪♪
I can't.
It's too soon.
[motor rumbling]
Sorry if I made it
awkward back there.
I think you're
really beautiful.
Vicky: I think you're
really handsome.
Max: That was fun.
Vicky: Yeah.
It was.
Good night.
Max: Bye, good night.
[wind gusting]
[footsteps]
[Vicky screams]
[man yells]
[Vicky pants]
♪
[panting]
Ahh! Ahh!
Jake: Hey, hey, whoa, hey!
Vicky: Don't come any closer,
I'll fucking kill you!
Jake: Chill!
Vicky: I said, step back!
Jake: I think there's been
a little misunderstanding.
Vicky: Why are you
at my cabin?
Jake: It's my uncle's
fucking cabin, man.
Vicky: What fucking uncle?
Jake: Look, you must be friends
with my cousin Stacy, right.
Vicky: You can't fucking
prove that, do better!
Jake: Oh, come on!
Vicky: Do better!
Jake: When we were 12, I
accidentally pushed her
off the porch steps, that's why
she has that scar on her nose.
Look, I'm a truck driver, I work
for a fucking carrier service.
Been on the road for the past
three days, I got tired.
I usually crash here if
I'm working the coast.
Vicky: If you're a truck
driver, where's your truck?
Jake: It doesn't make it up
these roads, it's too muddy.
It's down the road.
Fucking-a.
You scared the shit out of me!
I fucking pissed myself.
Fuck it, whatever, I'm
going back to the cabin.
[howl in distance]
[footsteps]
Vicky: I'm sorry
about earlier.
Jake: No, I'm sorry.
I almost took your fucking
head off with that bat.
[Vicky scoffs]
It's my bad.
Vicky: You don't have COVID or
anything like that, do you?
Jake: No, I got tested before
I hit the road, so.
You're kind of the first person
I've talked to in like a week.
Vicky: Cool.
How did you walk all
the way out here?
I mean, it's kind of far
from the main road.
Jake: I hiked in.
I know these woods like
the back of my hand.
Been coming here since
I was a little kid.
Vicky: So, you just truck
up and down the coast?
You have, like, no
family or anything?
Jake: I'm a little
bit of a loner.
I got something for you.
♪♪
Vicky: Sorry.
Jake: Sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you, I just--
See, that's me and that's
Stacy when we were kids.
All right?
I'm not some fucking lunatic
that's going to kill you
while you're sleeping.
Yeah.
If you don't mind me,
I think I'm just going
to crawl back into my
little imagination here.
♪♪
What do you got here?
Vicky: DMT and salvia.
Stacy, like, scored it off
some Silicon Valley dude.
Jake: Hmm.
Fuck it, let's smoke them
both at the same time.
[Vicky laughs]
Vicky: Okay, so, what's
the difference between
DMT and salvia?
Jake: You've never smoked
this shit before?
Vicky: No.
Jake: All right.
So, both, you know, they're
both pretty fucking awesome.
But with salvia, you can
experience cartoon-like visuals,
uncontrollable laughter,
feeling of being stretched
or twisted and, my personal
favorite, believing that
you're in more than once
place at the same time.
Vicky: Holy shit.
Jake: Yeah.
Vicky: Okay, what about DMT?
Jake: Okay.
Now, with DMT, the
hallucinations are
a little more visual.
So, objects can sometimes
turn into animals.
And...
the trip is really short, but
sometimes it can feel like it
lasts forever, even longer.
Vicky: Well, fuck.
Um...
all right, let's
flip a coin for it.
[music plays on cell]
Good song.
Heads I do DMT, tails
salvia, vice versa.
Jake: Okay.
Vicky: Fuck, I'm doing DMT.
Jake: All right.
Vicky: I'm scared!
Jake: Why, come on,
don't be scared.
Come on, we'll do them at
the same time, all right?
So, you really don't
need too much.
Go on, get in there.
Vicky: Oh my God.
Jake: All right.
On the count of three.
Vicky: Okay.
Jake: One...
two...
three.
Hold it in.
Hold that shit in.
♪♪
♪ Nothing's gonna
hurt you, baby. ♪
♪
♪ As long as you're with me
you'll be just fine. ♪
Jake: Oh.
[groans]
Oh, whoa.
♪ Nothing's going to
hurt you, baby. ♪
[laughs]
What the fuck was that?
Oh, oh.
♪ Nothing's going to
take you from my side. ♪
Oh, fuck.
Vicky: Oh my God.
Jake: Oh, you okay?
[both laugh]
Vicky: Oh my--
Jake: Oh! Holy shit.
Are you okay?
Vicky: Yes.
Jake: Oh, fuck.
♪♪
♪ Nothing's going
to hurt you, baby. ♪
♪
♪ As long as you're with
me you'll be just fine. ♪
♪
♪ Nothing's going
to hurt you, baby. ♪
♪
♪ Nothing's going to
take you from my side. ♪
Shannon: Oh, could COVID
just be over already?
Us being restricted in this
house and not being able
to go out and do anything, I
feel like it's so ridiculous.
- If I had anything to say
to America right now,
I would just say, like,
you don't even understand
how hard this
has been for us.
Like, you don't understand.
Cassius: Yo, Lindsey.
Where you going, man?
Lindsey: I'm just
going to go to bed.
Why don't you
sleep down here?
Cassius: Sleep down here?
Lindsey: Yeah, why don't
you sleep down here,
there's another
room for you.
Kim: To America, I just want
to say wear your masks,
stay home, stay safe, and
just do your part, okay?
Woo!
Paris: I cannot believe
that she just did that.
[sheets rustle]
[footsteps]
[rustling]
[wind gusting]
Vicky: Jake?
♪♪
Handyman: Oof.
Vicky: What the fuck?
Handyman: Sorry, I didn't
mean to startle you.
[Vicky sighs]
I just, I got an early start,
so I didn't want to wake you up.
But, oh yeah, sorry about
the blood on the porch.
There was a deer in the middle
of the road this morning,
so I had to pull
the fella off.
Anyway, I changed
out the old wires,
and your Wi-Fi
should be good to go.
So, all I need is
your Hancock here.
Vicky: Did you just see
a guy here earlier?
He has long hair.
Handyman: No, no,
it's just you and me.
All right.
You have a good one.
Vicky: Yeah.
[truck door closes]
♪♪
[police siren chirps]
Handyman: Shit.
♪♪
You're not Sheriff Rodgers.
[Vicky sighs]
♪♪
[laptop rings]
[notification chime]
Jazzy Lou: Oh my God, you look
so pretty, look at you!
[Vicky scoffs]
Vicky: Do you really think so?
I mean, I can put this wig
on if you want me to.
Jazzy Lou: No, no, no, I love
you just the way you are.
Hey, you never going to
believe what happened
after the night that
we were dancing.
My wife, she heard the music,
she came upstairs,
we danced all night!
I didn't know my girl was
so much into Marc Anthony.
Vicky: See, what
did I tell you?
I'm happy for you guys.
Jazzy Lou: All night.
Oh yeah, I think
we in love.
Uh-oh.
What happened?
♪♪
Vicky: I'm sorry, I'm
just, I'm really tired.
But I'm happy for you.
You deserve something real.
[laptop rings]
[notification chime]
Vicky: Hi, hubby.
ONLY14U: You lying,
cheating little slut.
Vicky: Please don't
talk to me like that.
ONLY14U: I can't believe
I've been saving myself
for a whore!
Vicky: I said, don't talk
to me like that!
[laughing]
ONLY14U: Okay, wifey!
♪♪
[shovel scraping]
[Vicky gasps]
Max: Is someone there?
[rustling]
[Vicky pants]
[Vicky pants and gasps]
Max: Hey.
[Vicky screams]
What are you doing?
Vicky: Why are you chasing me?
Max: Chasing you?
Why are you running from me?
Vicky: Have you seen Jake?
Max: Who?
Vicky: Stacy's cousin.
Max: No.
Are you sure you're okay?
Vicky: What were you digging?
[Max scoffs]
Max: A grave.
Vicky: What?
Max: I found a deer on
the side of the road.
The odor of a decomposing
carcass tends to attract bears.
Poor thing.
Mind helping?
[shovel scraping]
So, how was the
rest of your night?
Vicky: I was with
you last night.
Max: No, I mean after
I dropped you off.
Vicky: After you left,
Stacy's cousin came over
and we just hung out.
Max: Oh.
Fun.
[shovel scraping]
[Max grunts]
It's a sin to leave the
dead without a grave.
Hey, would you grab my smokes?
Vicky: Yeah, sure.
Where are they?
On the bag.
Right next to you.
♪♪
Vicky: Oh my God,
are you okay?
Max: My ankle!
[groans]
Would you give me a hand?
Please?
♪♪
Thanks.
Vicky: Here you go.
Max: I don't know about you,
but I'm starving.
How about I cook us dinner?
Vicky: Come on,
you're, you're hurt.
Max: I'm used to being hurt.
[Vicky sniffles]
Vicky: Is there a sweater or a
blanket that I could borrow?
Sorry, I'm just freezing.
Max: Yeah, go upstairs.
A bunch of my ex's
stuff in the room.
I'll fire up the stove.
Vicky: Okay.
Max: Sorry.
Vicky: Sorry!
♪♪
[meat sizzles]
[dog barks]
[loud thumps]
Vicky: Fuck!
[thumps and creaking]
♪♪
[creaking floorboards]
♪
Max: I think you're
really beautiful.
Mmm.
♪♪
Stacy: Kim and Max Daniels.
They live next door, they're
really cool, young couple.
Max: Unfortunately,
they're gone.
Vicky: Gone?
[footsteps]
Max: Dinner's ready.
♪♪
So, tell me more
about you, Vicky.
Not to pry, but when I was at
your place the other night
I noticed you had a
webcam site open.
If you don't mind me asking,
what do you do on there?
Vicky: It's not a big deal.
It's like, umm...
Sharing content.
Stuff like that.
Max: Uh-huh.
Hmm.
18 &amp; Over, that's
what you're on, right?
Vicky: Mm-hmm.
Max: I've heard that site's
become such a popular hub
for sex workers that it's
saturated the market.
I didn't even know
that was possible,
oversaturating the
world sex market.
[laughs]
What a world we live in!
Those poor suckers.
[Max chewing]
Can you believe there's
whores tricking men into
falling in love with
them for money!
[chewing continues]
Vicky: What did you
put in my drink?
Max: Promises, promises.
All I hear is false promises.
But you're all the
f-f-fucking same.
Every...
last...
one of you.
[clock ticking]
Paris: Guys, I
have some bad news.
One of you will
be going home.
One of you was beyond
and put us all at risk.
Kim, you're going home.
Spence: Really,
after all that?
Kim: I was at a protest!
Paris: No, bitch,
you were at a party.
Lindsey: The fuck was she
thinking, going to a party?
Deadass: She's literally
the one that always has
a visor on her face!
Kim: It's just not fair, okay!
Paris: Bye.
- It's okay, it's all right,
it's all right.
Come on, then, it's fine.
- It's so sad.
[Kim coughs]
Lucas: Oh my God, get away!
- Get out!
Kim: I don't think it's fair.
Like, give me a warning.
I'll take another COVID test!
Paris: So, that's
what happens when you
don't follow the rules.
Actually, it was
just one rule.
All you guys had to do
is stay in this mansion.
Believe me, life
could be worse.
Everyone in America is doing
the same thing right now.
You're all very lucky to
be here, so act like it.
[handcuffs clang]
Max: Hi, sleeping beauty.
[Vicky gasps]
Vicky: What did you do to me?
Please, please, get me
out of this.
Why would you do this?
Max: Are you really
asking me why?
Do you have any idea what
I've d-done to be with you?
Vicky: Please, please, you
don't have to do this!
Max: You said you
wanted to marry me.
You said you wanted a ring.
I got you a ring.
I want you to put your money
where your mouth is...
wifey.
[Vicky sniffs]
♪♪
Vicky: Baby, did you really
do this all for me?
Why don't you
uncuff me first?
If you want to
propose to me...
I want you to
do it right.
How can you love me
if you don't trust me?
Max: Trust is important.
♪♪
[handcuffs click]
This was my grandmother's.
I told my mom all about you,
and she gave it to me for you.
Vicky: It's beautiful.
Max: Vicky, will you m-m...
marry me?
Vicky: Yes.
[Max's breaths trembling]
Max: Holy shit.
She, she said yes.
She said yes.
♪♪
You're a fucking liar.
You're just trying to use me.
♪♪
Vicky: Am I?
Max: Oh my God.
♪♪
[kissing wetly]
Vicky: I've always wanted
you to be my husband.
[kissing]
Baby, close your eyes.
Because I'm going to blow
your fucking mind.
Fuck you!
[dog barking]
♪♪
♪
[Vicky screams]
♪♪
[panting]
[motor rumbles]
♪♪
Ahh!
No, no, no!
Jake: Hey, hey, hey! Vicky!
Vicky: No!
Jake: Vicky, Vicky,
hey, hey, hey!
It's me, it's me.
Vicky: Jake, Jake!
Jake: Come here, come here.
Vicky: Jake!
Jake: What happened,
are you okay?
Vicky: No, he's going
to kill me!
Jake: Who's going to kill you?
Vicky: No, we don't have time!
Vicky: Jake, please,
listen to me, he's not Max.
He killed the whole
family, come on!
Jake: Come here, talk to me!
Vicky: Stop, shh!
He's here.
Come on, Jake.
Jake: Who is that?
Vicky: Please, trust me,
we have to go!
Jake!
Jake: Go, go, go, now,
go, get out of here, go!
♪♪
Who's there?
[knife snicks]
[running footsteps]
Where the fuck are you?
Come on!
Let's fucking go, huh!
[running footsteps]
Where the fuck are you,
you fucking-- Ah, fuck!
[grunts and pants]
Ahh, fuck!
Max: Hiya, Jake.
Jake: What the fuck!
[metallic clang]
Vicky: Sheriff,
it's me, Vicky.
The Crowbar Killer,
he's here!
Please, please, you have
to come here now!
Please help me, please!
Can you hear me?
Help, please!
Lou.
Jazzy Lou: Hey, Vi--
Vicky: I'm at 56 Woodland Drive
in Weed, California.
There's someone trying to
kill me, please, please,
call for help!
Jazzy Lou: I'm calling them
now, I'm calling them now.
[clanking]
[disconnected phone tone]
Max: Honey...
I'm home.
[heavy footsteps]
I know I'm not the most...
traditional guy.
But I...
do expect to be with my future
wife the night we got engaged.
[laughs]
Can we just talk about it?
Jazzy Lou: What the fuck!
You fucking touch her!
I'll come find you!
I just called the cops,
you crazy son of a bitch!
Max: Ahh!
[electricity crackling]
I killed that ungrateful
boyfriend of yours.
You know he wasn't
right for you.
You should be thanking me,
you know.
What else do I have to do
to prove my love to you?
Tell me!
[glass shatters]
[liquid dripping]
That wasn't very nice.
[grunts]
[Vicky grunts]
[both grunting]
[Vicky gasps]
Max: Got to tell you, honey,
you have been just as
disappointing as the rest
of those lying bitches.
♪♪
Jake: Vicky!
Max: Are you fucking
kidding me right now?
Jake: Let's go, mother fucker.
Come on.
[grunting and yelling]
Max: God damn it!
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[meaty clang]
[grunting]
Sorry, buddy...
nobody likes
a third wheel.
[heavy thud]
[Max grunts and yells]
[Jake screams]
Jake: No!
[both grunting]
[both yelling]
[Max yells]
[grunts]
[Max grunts and pants]
I always knew you'd stab me
in the back, you b-b-bitch.
[Vicky yells]
Vicky: Fuck you!
[splashing and crackling]
[sizzling]
♪♪
It's over.
[police siren wailing]
Lindsey: I can't watch,
I can't--
[Vicky breathes shakily]
[Chy cackles]
- Oh my God, girl, just--
Shannon: Yeah, right?
Spence: I knew it was
him the whole time.
I knew it was him
the whole time!
- You did not,
you did not!
Chy: Listen to what
he's saying!
Spence: Max, Max, Max, I knew
it was him the whole time.
Lindsey: Why did,
how did you know?
Chy: Literally why are
you throwing popcorn?
It's already a mess in here.
Cassius: Hey, yo, who
was the Crowbar Killer?
Lindsey: Max, you
fucking idiot.
[laughter]
Chy: But I thought for sure
it was Jake.
Like, literally, he was too good
to be true, too nice, too much.
Cassius: Have you ever
webcammed, yes or no?
Spence: Of course, of course,
newsflash, look it, look it.
Of course.
Chy: Nobody asked you,
you analytical asshole.
Lindsey: I can't believe
that we're in a movie.
A freaking movie!
Shannon: Seriously, though?
Spence: Aren't you guys seeing
what I'm seeing here.
They're exploiting all of us.
They're exploiting us!
- I think you're
being overdramatic.
- Uh-uh--
Shannon: You're so loud!
Spence: Your face is loud!
Shannon: Oh!
Spence: That's right,
you heard me.
[Chy cackles]
Shannon: And, girl,
you're laughing!
You're laughing!
And you better shut up.
Eat your cereal.
Eat your cereal and shut
up, please, thank you.
Thank you!
You know what, fuck
you guys, I'm done.
Spence: Do it again!
Shannon: Bye!
Chy: This is why
nobody likes you!
Spence: All right,
you know what--
Chy: Fuck you!
Lucas: It's just
a stupid movie.
Let's just get a drink--
Chy: And this movie is the exact
reason why I'm not joining
18 &amp; Over.
♪♪
Lindsey: I wonder
if they do a sequel
if they'll bring us back.
♪♪
Deadass: Yo!
Yo!
You all want to
hear my new song?
All: No!
♪♪
Paris: And the world premier
of Deadass The Band
only on "Trap Stars."
♪♪
♪ Who these bros at the party?
♪ I don't fuck with them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I don't need them.
♪ Who these bros
At the party? ♪
♪ I know none of them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I ain't fucking them.
♪ I don't need that shit, you
know that I don't need it. ♪
♪ Who these bros on the
lawn acting all wrong? ♪
♪ Who these hos at the pool?
♪ They about to drown.
♪ The cops at the party,
time to run away. ♪
♪ We're splitting up,
now it's a getaway. ♪
♪ I just went through this
shit just the other day. ♪
♪ Pssh, same shit,
just another day. ♪
♪ Hey, everybody get
close to the ground. ♪
♪ Got to get real
♪ Everybody get close
to the ground. ♪
♪ Got to get real close.
♪ Who these bros at the party?
♪ I don't fuck with them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I don't need them.
♪ Who these bros at the party?
♪ I know none of them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I ain't fucking them.
♪ I don't need that shit, you
know that I don't need it. ♪
♪ All these bros in my face
fucking up my day. ♪
♪ Hos in my room
trying to hide away. ♪
♪ I'm like, fuck that shit,
you know that ♪
♪ we get real close
to the ground. ♪
♪ Everybody real
close to the ground. ♪
♪ I'mma get it real
♪ Everybody real
close to the-- ♪
♪ Everybody get close
to the ground. ♪
♪ Got to get real close
♪ Everybody real
close to the ground. ♪
♪ Got to get real close
to the ground. ♪
[cheering and clapping]
- My fucking knees.
[laughter]
Literally, I'm looking
back thinking everybody's
struggling like me, she's
on the fucking--
[laughter]
♪ Who these hos at the party?
♪ I don't fuck with them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I don't need them.
♪ Who these bros at the party?
♪ I know none of them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I ain't fucking them.
♪ Who these hos at the party?
♪ I don't fuck with them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ No, I don't need them.
♪ Who these bros at the party?
♪ I know none of them.
♪ Who these hos at the crib?
♪ I ain't fucking.
♪ I don't need that shit, you
know that I don't need that. ♪
♪ I don't need that shit, no,
no, no, I don't need that. ♪
♪ Who these bros on the
lawn acting all wrong? ♪
♪ Who these hos at the pool?
♪ They about to drown.
♪
♪ Yeah, hey, yeah.
♪ Raging waters,
♪ deeper I go
in the pool. ♪
♪ Hey.
♪
♪ Sinking to the bottom,
trying to get close to you. ♪
♪
♪ No dream is as good as you.
♪ Recreations are just
beautiful illusions, ♪
♪ yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah.
♪
♪ Working up to look at you
♪ It's all clear, I lost
all of my confusion. ♪
♪
♪ What if this moment, what
if this moment never ends? ♪
♪ My eyes wide open,
I don't want to fall ♪
♪ too far from heaven.
♪ 'Cause I don't want to sleep
when you're beside me. ♪
♪ So, every time you
aren't beside me, ♪
♪ I'll be awa-a-ake,
I'll be awa-a-ake. ♪