[fire crackling]
[wind blowing]
[waves crashing]
[♪♪♪]
[birds chirping]
CONSTRUCTION WORKER 1: [speaks indistinctly] ...that dry wall again.
-[workers speaking indistinctly] -[cell phone ringing]
JULIE: Hi. I've got a surprise for you.
[chuckles]
JULIE: No.
What if you've been hounding me for like over a year?
[chuckles]
I'm serious. An actual lipstick carousel?
I found it on a state sale.
I told you it was gonna be a blessing to move up here.
I still need to check the state of the motor
but it's in pretty good shape.
I'll text you some pictures.
Or, you know, you could use it as an excuse
to come up and see the house.
Well, you got to come up and visit sometime.
I'm telling you, this house...
something about it just drew me to it.
Okay, yeah. I gotta go. I'll text you pictures later.
-Bye. -[thuds]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh... [chuckles] Hi.
Do you like your new home?
Yeah.
[sighs] Me too.
-[indistinct chatter] -[buzzsaw buzzing]
[thuds, clanking in distance]
[music playing over player]
Oh, Oh. Ma'am, ma'am! You can't be in here.
Uh, the floor's not safe.
Oh.
DANIEL: I'm just trying to establish
what kind of time frame we're talking about here
since we have the baby on the...
-Ah... -Hey!
-JULIE: Hi! -DANIEL: Did you just get in?
Yeah. I tried calling you.
Oh yeah. No, sorry, we just--
ah, it's just plumbing Armageddon situation.
-That sounds promising. -Not really.
How bad is it?
CONSTRUCTION SUPERVISOR: It's not great.
The amount of rock that I can see in the sub floor--
The drain's probably been leaking for years.
And they didn't find any of that in the inspection?
CONSTRUCTION SUPERVISOR: They probably missed it.
But look we can handle the re-pipe.
But you're gonna need a structural engineer
to take a look at that floor.
JULIE: Anyone you recommend?
CONSTRUCTION SUPERVISOR: Uh, I can make some calls.
-Thanks. -I'll get on that.
Yeah, so that's my day.
Miss, miss? Found this lodged in the drain.
JULIE: Oh.
I know how you gals,
you're all sentimental about your jewelry. [chuckles]
[Julie chuckles]
-It's not mine. -DANIEL: Nice bloke, though.
-Yeah. -DANIEL: Yeah, come on.
JULIE: Let me get you that suit.
JULIE: [gasps] Hi, Lou.
DANIEL: Ah, this is unbelievable. This is nonstop.
As soon as we finish one thing, something else explodes
or rots or leaks.
It's like we're living in a in a never-ending game of the--
you know what's the thing where it pops up and you--
-Whack-A-Mole? -DANIEL: ...and you whack 'em.
You sure it's a Whack-A-Mole?
-Ah! -[Julie chuckles]
DANIEL: Why can't anything be easy?
Hey, I'm easy.
[Daniel chuckles]
[groans]
House is disintegrating around us
and you are cracking jokes.
Hey.
It's an old house.
We knew what we were getting into.
DANIEL: Hmm.
It'll be great once it's done.
You'll see.
We'll get through it.
DANIEL: You're right. We always do.
CONSTRUCTION WORKER 3: Hey yo, watch out!
[loud thud in distance]
-No. No, no, no, no, no, no. -[laughs]
[grunts, laughs]
[groans]
[♪♪♪]
[boys laughing in distance]
[wind howling]
[Lou growling]
JULIE: Lou?
[snarls]
[♪♪♪]
BOY 1: Ssh.
[speaks indistinctly]
BOY 1: She's looking for you.
[shrieks] Oh, my God.
-You scared the shit out of me. -You scared the shit out of me.
You wanna put me in premature labor?
Come here. I wanna show you something.
Huh?
What do you think?
Yeah, nice work, Professor.
Ahan. Who says intellectuals can't be all manly?
-[drill whirrs] -[groans]
Ooh. And all that. Check this out.
Baby TV, over here is up and running.
We are live.
As you can see a motion detector
and oh, a microphone.
Hey, baby.
VOICE OVER MONITOR: Hey, baby.
And it's all operated wirelessly.
-Pretty cool. -Pretty impressive, right?
Here. What?
You're forgetting something.
Oh shit. Is that the--
I need to shower or we're gonna be late.
You're going-- you gonna wear that?
-Yeah, you don't like it? -No, I love it. Beautiful.
-Just to impress, right? -Fetching.
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct chatter]
Looking gorgeous.
Remind me again who we're supposed
-to be impressing tonight? -Uh, Dean Whittier.
Is that the guy with the moustache?
No, no, that's Barkley. That's uh... that's the chair.
Oh, God. Everyone in Academia looks the same.
It's all smoking jackets and facial hair.
[chuckles]
Just look for the guy with the mole.
So, tell me how did you two meet?
We met the old-fashioned way.
-Yeah... -We met at a bar.
Right.
I was out one night having drinks with friends
and I spot this guy alone, sitting at the bar.
I just got in the country and so I was...
So, he finally works up the nerve to come over
and he offers to buy me a drink.
Well, I actually bought a round of drinks for her
and her mates.
-It was all a trap.... -[Mrs. Whittier chuckles]
Which was a rather steep investment on my part
-during that time. -Oh, okay.
Apparently, I was worth the splurge.
DANIEL: Well, apparently. I was a little tipsy.
-And we get to talking. -That's right,
and she tells me about her antiques business, right?
Hm-mm.
And, he mentions this old watch he has
and he's been meaning to get it restored.
So, I said I'd take a look at it.
Which was a lie, of course.
-There was no watch. -No watch.
And I just wanted to see her again.
So, I spend the next 24 hours scouring all of lower Manhattan
trying to find a watch. I find one, I bring it to her.
-Total fake. -Total fake.
JULIE: Hm-mm.
It wasn't my proudest moment,
-but still works. -[Julie chuckles]
And I got a date out of it, didn't I?
[indistinct chatter]
JULIE: Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct chatter]
Tuna tartar?
JULIE: I wish. Thanks.
Don't worry.
You'll be eating it all again soon enough.
My downfall was always the cheese.
So, where'd you end up settling?
We bought a house by the lake.
Oh, it's stunning up there.
John and I have toyed with the idea
of moving up there for years.
-Which property? -8317 Lake view.
Oh yes.
I knew a man who lived up there many years ago.
Unfortunately, his wife became quite ill.
Anyway, you must be over the moon.
-It's your first? -Ah.
-Yes. Yes, it is. -Brilliant.
A new job and a baby on the way.
So much to celebrate.
DANIEL: Cheers.
[♪♪♪]
DANIEL: You heard Bartlett raving about my work
on the advisory committee?
I mean, I'm telling you Jules, there's a real opportunity here.
I'm gonna play my cards right
and I could be running the department
in, I don't know, five years.
Huh? Everything okay?
-Yeah. -Yeah?
[chuckles]
You barely said a word the whole drive home.
You told that woman this was our first.
[scoffs] What would you have me say?
I passed it as an exactly cocktail conversation, Jules.
You don't have to lie about it.
Well, she asked a simple question.
I... I gave a simple answer.
[scoffs] Right.
God forbid, you upset our fancy new friends.
Hang on, Jules. Jules, Jules.
It's not like that. You know it's not like that.
There's people in the department,
people that were way before,
that know what we went through.
I mean, isn't this meant to be a fresh start for us?
You know, giving this a fresh go.
How are we gonna do that,
if we're just clinging on to the past?
Daniel, he was your son.
It's like sometimes you forget he even existed!
And you forgot he ever died.
No. Jules, please stop. Please, just talk to me. Wait.
[Julie gasps, whimpers]
DANIEL: Jules! Jules.
-Vitals? -BP of 149 over 90.
I need a Doppler and an IV.
How far long is she?
NURSE 1: Thirty-two weeks.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
GYNECOLOGIST: Good Julie, one more. One more, one more.
[Julie screaming]
Go, go, go.
[Julie screams]
GYNECOLOGIST: One more. I know you're tired.
- Go, go, go. - One more, one more.
[Julie screams]
Got ya. That's it, that's it.
[pants]
GYNECOLOGIST: Start compressions.
-Why isn't he crying? -It's fine. Jules, it's fine.
Is he okay? What is happening?
-DANIEL: What's happening? -It's alright.
-JULIE: Can I see him? -Just try to relax.
Why isn't he crying? I can't hear him.
GYNECOLOGIST: Let's go again. Right now.
-What's going on with my baby? -He's fine, right?
GYNECOLOGIST: Julie, I'm so sorry.
[screams]
[cries]
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct chattering in distance]
[indistinct announcement over PA]
Hey.
You're in the hospital.
You had a bad fall.
-Is she.... -She's okay.
Baby's okay.
You suffered what we call a partial placenta abruption.
Abruption? What's that?
It's when the placenta becomes partially detached
from the uterine wall.
Is it dangerous?
Well, it can be life-threatening if the placenta fully separates
but as you can see, the tear appears fairly minimal.
And so far the situation seems to be stabilized.
Bleeding stopped
and your baby's got a good strong heartbeat.
However, it is standard practice to exercise caution.
What does that mean?
It means I want you on bed rest.
Strict bed rest for the duration of your pregnancy.
No driving, no lifting, no cooking.
Other than the occasional trip to the bathroom,
you need to be in bed idle.
You're saying you want me in bed
for the next eight weeks?
DR. MEADOWS: I know it's not ideal.
But we don't want you going into early labor.
Anything before 37 weeks is considered preterm
and can put the baby at risk of low birth weight
or respiratory distress.
We're in the middle of a renovation
and we're overseeing everything.
I would strongly recommend
putting any major projects on hold,
until after the baby comes.
Do you have any family or friends in the area?
Anyone who can help you out?
Not since we moved, no.
DR. MEADOWS: Well, if you need support,
we'd be happy to offer a referral.
Any other questions?
When can I go home?
[♪♪♪]
DR. MEADOWS: To avoid preterm labor,
you need to follow a few simple rules.
One, you need to remain in bed 24 hours a day.
Two, you're allowed brief trips to the bathroom
and one ten-minute bath every three days,
no more.
And finally, the most important rule.
It's crucial that you avoid stress.
Anything that raises your blood pressure
not only endangers the health of your child,
but could re trigger the mental dissociation
you experienced after your last pregnancy.
My advice, try to enjoy the R&R.
DANIEL: Alright. Here we go.
[vrooming]
The brakes.
And easy. Easy does it.
Let me take this.
Alright, there we are.
I'll get the shoes.
Yeah, gonna get rid of these.
Right. Let's get you on the bed.
-Alright, you good? -Yeah.
Alright.
Right. Now, you ready for this?
Because I have you all hooked up.
-I'll supply it. -Got you some lotion,
-got your some prenatals. -Oh.
DANIEL: I know what you're thinking. How you're gonna reach them.
Well, I got you this cool grab stick.
You can just, you know, try it out.
JULIE: Nice.
Here some trashy magazines, I know you love those.
Read it to your heart's content. An iPad, your laptop and uh...
oh, vintage entertainment system.
Very vintage but courtesy of the English's department's
-uh... supply closet. -Wow.
DANIEL: It's old but antique, maybe, you know?
Maybe it's worth a fortune.
No?
Mini fridge, stacked full of amazing awesome shit.
Because that's kind of a husband I am.
Oh, and the best part.
-Walkie talkies. -Walkie talkies.
One for you.
Eighteen channels, 23-mile radius.
So, we can communicate anywhere in the house.
Anywhere.
Or we could you know, text.
Yeah, but what's the fun in that?
Try it out. Go on, turn it on.
RADIO CHANNEL VOICE: Attention all units...
Ssshhhh. No, no, just um...
Get to change the channel. We can ignore that.
Just uh, uh... next, next channel. Shit.
Got it? Break a break.
It's big daddy, come in hot mama.
Got any request?
Ah, sure could use a cup of tea, big daddy.
DANIEL: Ten-four. Hot mama.
Shot of hot liquid lightning comin' up.
Over and out.
-Go say over. -Over and out.
Nice. Alright.
Oh, and uh... don't you go anywhere.
[inhales, exhales]
[♪♪♪]
[vacuum vrooming]
[music playing]
TV COMMERCIAL: Three times faster than our leading competitor,
Our little one...
[sighs]
[exhales]
[baby crying]
[boys laughing]
[♪♪♪]
[thud]
[boys laughing]
[breathes heavily]
Mommy must be hearing things.
...The breeze.
The winds now fasting up to 39.
So, this just gives you the idea
that the winds are going to...
Looks like we have some weather rolling in.
Maybe they'll cancel your classes
and we can bed rest it together.
What do you think? Binge-watch Grey's Anatomy ?
-[Daniel chuckles] -Eat our weight in popcorn.
[chuckles]
-Are you listening to me? -DANIEL: Yeah no.
Um, this funny thing happened in our faculty.
Meeting today, and I'm just texting...
Hahaha. LOL.
What happened?
-DANIEL: With what? -In your meeting?
Oh. Well, you had to be there.
Otherwise, it's just... stupid.
-What's that? -What's what?
DANIEL: That, the package right there.
Oh, that's just some stuff that I ordered for the house.
Did you... did you go downstairs
and get it?
Jules, you know what the doctor said.
-You can't -I was careful.
Doesn't matter!
There are rules. You can't get up.
You can't just... just move around.
-He made it very clear... -Jesus! What are you?
My frickin' jailer.
JULES: "I can't get up. I can't walk around."
I can't go outside.
I can't continue with this renovation
cause God forbid the fumes and the noise,
might cause me undue stress.
Getting that stupid box was the highlight of my day.
I just...
[exhales] It sucks.
I get it. I do. I...
[exhales]
I am sorry. Alright.
Hey. I am sorry.
I just don't know I... I worry, you know?
Thank you.
Thank you for doing this for us.
And thank you for being on your best behavior.
Your mommy and I really appreciate it.
I love you.
Goodnight.
Night.
[sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[grunts]
[thud]
[thud, clanks]
[indistinct whispering]
-Hm? -Wake up, wake up. Wake up.
-What? -There's someone in the closet.
What?!
[screams] Fucking shit!
Daniel.
[♪♪♪]
Oh. You scared this shit out of me.
[pants]
-You sure you're feeling okay? -I....
Jesus.
It's probably just your sleep mind, alright?
Let's get some rest, love.
Come.
[thunder rumbling]
[♪♪♪]
You were supposed to pick them up from school!
Where were they, Todd?
Girl, you need that kick that man to the curb.
[clinks]
[indistinct argument over TV]
[boy 1 laughing in distance]
JULIE: Hey there!
What you doing?
Ssh.
Haw. Hide and seek?
Where's your mama?
[♪♪♪]
-[thuds] -[gasps]
[loud thumping]
[♪♪♪]
[beep]
[Lou meows]
Goddammit, Lou.
Lou! Get off! Off! Yes, off!
[sighs]
[♪♪♪]
[pants]
9-1-1 OPERATOR: 9-1-1, what's your emergency?
Please help. There's someone in my house.
9-1-1 OPERATOR: What's your address, ma'am?
8317 Lake view. Hurry please.
9-1-1 OPERATOR: We have a unit on the way. Are you in a safe place?
I'm in my bedroom.
9-1-1 OPERATOR: And where is the intruder?
Down the hall.
9-1-1 OPERATOR: Is your bedroom door locked?
No.
9-1-1 OPERATOR: Ma'am, can you get to the door?
[breathes heavily]
9-1-1 OPERATOR: Ma'am?
Yes.
[breathes heavily]
9-1-1 OPERATOR: Ma'am?
-[breathes heavily] -[loud thumping]
-[♪♪♪] -[ceiling creaking]
[police siren blares]
DANIEL: Jules?
Hey. You alright?
You okay? Yeah?
Daniel Rivers.
Deputy Gates. We spoke on the phone.
Alright, yes. Any more news?
No. Still unable to locate a suspect.
Did you get a look at the guy?
DEPUTY GATES: Didn't turn up a child, either.
A child?
DEPUTY GATES: Your wife thought she heard a child in the house.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Well, looks like we've got everything we need.
If there's anything else we can do,
just give us a call.
Right, yes. Of course, thank you Officer.
Here, I'll walk you out.
[♪♪♪]
DANIEL: Sorry for wasting your time.
[indistinct chatter]
[speaks indistinctly]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Go ahead and say it. I know you're thinking it.
Should I be worried?
JULIE: There's just a misunderstanding.
You don't believe me?
[Daniel sighs]
What am I supposed to think, Jules?
Mental dissociation or a fixation on a child?
-I saw something. -DANIEL: That wasn't there.
I feel like we're on a verge of something here. We--
I need to know that the past is behind us.
I need to know that you're not relapsing.
It's not like last time.
[sighs]
I'm calling Doctor Meadows.
I'm going to bring you someone in.
-I don't need a babysitter. -DANIEL: It's not for you.
It's for her.
[door opens, closes]
[music playing]
JULIE: ...Okay?
GYNECOLOGIST: I'm sorry.
[♪♪♪]
[sobs]
[robot vacuum whirring]
[♪♪♪]
[whimpers]
Can baby sister come out to play?
[giggles]
[sighs]
Andrew?
[tablet beeping]
Andrew? Is that you sweetie?
It's mommy.
Can you come back please?
Please? Can you hear me?
DANIEL: Jules?
Hey. I heard the door slam.
-You alright? -Yeah.
I was just trying to Facetime with a friend.
It's not working.
DANIEL: Right.
[♪♪♪]
DANIEL: Hey. Hi, I'm Daniel.
[speaks indistinctly]
One-nineteen over 80. Very good.
Delmy.
I never heard that name before.
It's pretty.
It was my grandmother's.
A fine German name, as my father would say.
May I?
[♪♪♪]
DELMY: One-forty. It's perfect.
How have you been sleeping?
Hm, not great.
DELMY: That's the irony of bed rest.
All the time in the world to sleep
and unable to do it.
Do you have kids?
Um, my husband and I tried
but my body just wasn't equipped for it.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
No, please.
Sharing my journey is important.
In my experience there's more than one path
into motherhood.
I consider myself a proud mother of the countless babies
I've helped bring into this world.
Daniel told me about your son.
He also told me about Oakview.
How long were you there?
Six weeks.
DELMY: Post partum depression?
Post partum psychosis.
I kept seeing my son.
My mind wasn't ready to let go.
I know it's difficult bringing a stranger into your home.
But I want you to know I'm here for you.
Whatever it is you're feeling,
whatever it is you're experiencing...
you can trust me.
I appreciate that.
You should get some rest.
[♪♪♪]
DELMY: Easy.
There you go.
[inhales, exhales]
I can manage from here.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll be in the other room if you need me.
Oh God, no. I thought she'd never leave.
[breathes heavily]
[gasps]
BOY 1: Baby sister coming.
[grunts, groans]
Delmy!
[monitor beeping]
Well, probably just a Braxton-Hicks contraction.
Is it uncommon?
Just the body's way of preparing for birth.
She's alright?
The baby's fine.
To be honest, it's you who I'm concerned with.
I understand you've been having some uh...
some experiences.
The insomnia has just been messing
with my head a little.
Tell me about the boy.
How old was he?
Four, maybe five.
DR. MEADOWS: The age your son would be now?
Perhaps your mind remains unwilling to let go,
even after all these years.
Would you uh...
would you mind giving us a moment?
Uh, yeah.
Julie, no one ever said that bed rest would be easy.
And more often, than not the psychological challenges
outweigh the physical ones.
Especially for someone like me.
As I see it, we have two options.
We can move you to the hospital.
That would allow to finish your pregnancy
under the supervision
of a highly qualified medical staff. Two--
No.
No more hospitals.
DR. MEADOWS: The other option is you remain here at home.
My caveat being you have to restart your medication.
What about the baby?
DR. MEADOWS: You are 35 weeks along.
The meds would have little to no impact
on your baby's development.
Right now, the most important thing
you can do for her, is to take care of you.
Try to get some rest.
[♪♪♪]
DR. MEADOWS: It could be an isolated incident.
Or, it might be a precursor
to a more significant psychological break.
And she clearly thinks
she's seeing your previous child.
The medication should alleviate her symptoms,
but if they do persist,
you may want to consider admitting her
to a mental health facility.
It's for the best.
Good girl.
[♪♪♪]
[ball jiggles]
Lou.
You wanna play, buddy?
Alright.
[chuckles]
Alright, you ready?
You ready? Here you go.
[♪♪♪]
[boys laughing]
[breathes heavily]
You see him, too?
Andrew?
[boys laughing]
Sweetie, are you there?
Baby sister wants to see you.
Don't you want to come out and play?
[breathes heavily]
Are you here to see baby sister?
You should leave.
What do you mean? Why?
She wants baby sister.
Who? Who wants baby sister?
DELMY: You almost done in there?
Just a few more minutes.
No. No, wait. Please don't leave.
I want to know who wants baby sister.
Don't want you pruning on my watch.
Here we are. Nice and warm.
We gotta take care of our baby.
Did you feel that? She kicked for me.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Must not forget your pill.
JULIE: I'm just asking you where you found her?
DANIEL: Well, I got her number,
I told you from the hospital.
I told you that.
Right. But did you call her references?
Did you do a background check? Anything?
Meadows recommended her,
so, I didn't think it was necessary.
I mean, she is... lucky she was even available.
I want her out of the house.
-DANIEL: Are you serious? -Yes!
Delmy is a godsend.
-I don't trust her. -DANIEL: Why?
I just don't.
That woman, she's the reason I'm able to go to work
and not endlessly worry about you all day
being here by yourself.
So, if I'm gonna let her go or even consider that,
then I... I think I deserve some kind of explanation
or reason why something.
Fine.
[sighs]
DANIEL: Go on.
The boy I've been seeing, he's not in my head, Daniel.
What are you talking about?
I've been hearing him in the nursery
through the baby cam.
Daniel...
-it's our son. -DANIEL: Stop it, Julie.
-It's Andrew. -DANIEL: Stop it, Julie.
JULIE: And I know it sounds crazy, but he's reaching out.
DANIEL: Jules, Jules, please. Please don't do this.
-He's trying to warn us. -Please...
JULIE: He's trying to warn us about Delmy.
-What are you talking about? -She wants our baby.
And that's why he's reaching out.
-He's trying to protect us. -Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it! Stop!
Our son is dead. He's dead.
You think I don't know that?
You think I don't know that?!
You think that fact doesn't burn a hole
in my heart every goddamn day!
I was the one that held him!
Praying for him to breathe.
So, you don't have to tell me that he's dead, Daniel.
I was there.
-[knocking on door] -DELMY: Everything okay?
-We're fine! -DANIEL: Yeah.
-JULIE: Daniel-- -Just...
[indistinct chattering in distance]
You two are getting friendly.
Have you been taking your medication?
-Have you? -Don't you dare blame this
on some fucking chemical imbalance?
You're seeing our dead son, Julie.
So, just for a second here.
Imagine though what it's like from my perspective.
I know what that's like!
I am well aware of what you think of me.
I hear the whispers, I see the look on your face.
That awful mix of pity and fear.
I know you think I'm cracking.
That I'm on some hormonally fucked downward spiral
but I'm not.
And if I were you, I...
I'd probably be on the verge of hospitalizing me too.
But it's not in my head.
It's not.
Daniel... our son.
Our son, he's reaching out.
He's trying to communicate with me.
And instead of your judgment,
I could really use your support right now.
I'm sorry, Jules.
I think you need more than my support.
[♪♪♪]
[toilet flushing]
[indistinct chattering in distance]
Okay, call me then.
Nice and strong.
-You should eat something. -I'm not hungry.
You know we all want what's best for you, right?
I lost my first child at 18 weeks.
Pregnancy was going alone fine
and out of the blue, my water broke.
An incompetent cervix. That's what they told me.
I managed to conceive three more times
but never carried any to term.
I felt so hollow, so alone,
kept... asking myself what I'd done to deserve it.
And I remembered a story I'd heard as a child.
About a family who lived up around this lake.
Three small kids,
mother pregnant with the fourth.
She and her husband were on the way to the hospital
in early labor when their car skidded on some ice.
Crashed into a tree.
The impact taking the life of their unborn daughter.
The woman was inconsolable.
Every night, her cries could be heard
around the lake lamenting the loss
of her baby girl.
She didn't eat, barely left the house.
The faces of her three living children
just reminded her how she'd failed as a mother.
How she could never truly protect them.
And eventually, it just became too much.
She took her own life?
That story reminded me that I wasn't alone.
That mothers have been bearing the burden of loss
since the beginning of time.
But it's what you do with that pain,
that defines you.
A mother's grief is a powerful thing.
You either learn to make peace with it
or it eats you alive.
What was her name?
The mother?
Oh um, Kinsey, I think. Melandra Kinsey.
You should try and get some rest.
[♪♪♪]
M. K.
COURIER ARCHIVES SPOKESMAN: Courier Archives.
Hi. Uh, I was wondering if you could help me.
I'm trying to track down an old news story
that your paper may have covered.
COURIER ARCHIVES SPOKESMAN: How far back you're talking?
Um, late 60s, early 70s.
COURIER ARCHIVES SPOKESMAN: Uh, doubt it.
Our digital archives only cover the last few decades.
Unless it was a major news story.
What are you looking for exactly?
Uh, it was a suicide.
A local woman named Melandra Kinsey.
COURIER ARCHIVES SPOKESMAN: Let me get your email. I'll see what I can find.
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct chatter over TV]
[cellphone dings]
[door squeaking]
[♪♪♪]
Andrew, sweetheart.
I need to ask you something important.
Hi, sweetie.
The person who wants baby sister,
is it someone named Melandra Kinsey?
Andrew?
Where'd you go?
[gasps]
[♪♪♪]
[door squeaking]
[loud thumping]
[Lou snarls]
[breathes heavily]
[grunt, groans]
[indistinct whispering]
Delmy! Delmy, need help.
[grunt, groans]
DELMY: What is it? A contraction?
How many have you had?
[breathes heavily]
Julie?
There was someone.
How long?
Twenty, 30 seconds.
DELMY: It could be early labor.
Let's start monitoring and see if it progresses.
Wait!
I'm just gonna get my kit and throw on some clothes.
No, no. Please don't leave.
DELMY: There's nothing to fear.
You're bringing a baby into this world.
I'll be right back.
[breathes heavily]
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct whispering]
Oh, my God.
DANIEL: Ah. You're having contractions?
DELMY: It's early stages
but if she progresses we'll head to the hospital.
It's happening, Jules. We're havin' a baby.
Baby sister coming.
You okay?
We have to go.
-DELMY: Nooo. No, no, no. -Hey, hey, hey Jules. Relax.
DELMY: No need to rush. It's an early labor.
No, it's not safe. We need to leave.
-No, no Jules. Jules relax. -Wait.
Let me go.
Julie, you need to listen to me. It's very important.
-Relax. -No, there's no time.
There's no time. She's already here.
-Who? Who's here? -Melandra Kinsey.
Julie, Melandra Kinsey's just a story.
No, she's not! No, no, no.
I found her name in the change of title.
She lived here.
Look. This was her bracelet, Daniel.
DANIEL: Jules, Jules.
-She killed herself. -Please sit down, Jules.
And not just that. She killed her three kids.
DANIEL: Love...
She couldn't cope with the grief
-of losing her baby girl. -Can you--
And... and she took them with her.
Just sit down please.
She drowned them all in the bathtub.
It was a long time ago.
You knew?
You loved the house.
I just wanted you to be happy
so, I was protecting you as well.
For what? Lying?
By deliberately withholding the truth from me.
Cause I was scared!
Do you know what it was like for me?
Coming home and finding you in a pool of blood.
Watching you struggle day in and day out
after Andrew dies, and... and I just... I can't...
And I can't help you.
This house made you smile again, Jules.
Made you happy.
JULIE: But you didn't believe me.
I told you that there was something
going on in this house and you wouldn't listen.
Neither of you. You both made me think
-that it was all in my head. -Just--
Because it is all in your head. Hey love. Just--
No, it's not Daniel. It's not all in my head.
It's not. Melandra Kinsey is here.
-Please. Julie. -She's in this house.
Julie. And she wants our baby!
-Julie. -[objects clattering, squeaking]
[Julie screams]
[♪♪♪]
-[objects shattering] -[lights flickering]
[breathes heavily]
DANIEL: Jules.
[thud]
[wind blowing]
[indistinct whispering]
[thud]
What the hell.
[gasps]
[thud]
Better hide. Mommy's coming.
[boys chuckling]
Get the chair. Get the chair. We're getting out of here.
Come with me. You alright.
[grunts]
[boys chuckling]
Leave her alone!
-[window shatters] -[Julie gasps]
JULIE: Daniel.
DANIEL: Let's go!
Come on.
[pants]
[screams]
[breathes heavily]
Daniel. Oh, Daniel.
Honey. Daniel?
Hey, Daniel.
[whimpers]
[door bangs]
[doors banging]
Fuck you!
[sobs]
-[water dripping] -[pants]
[screams]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[breathes heavily]
Hello.
Can anybody hear me? Hello?
[radio static]
My name is Julie Rivers. I live in 8317 Lakeview Drive.
I need help. I'm in labor.
[♪♪♪]
[groans, screams]
GYNECOLOGIST: Great, Julie.
We're doing this right now, sweetheart.
Okay, don't think. Just push.
[Julie screaming]
Push. Give me everything you got, Julie.
Keep going, keep going. You're right there.
[Julie screams]
GYNECOLOGIST: That's it, that's it. That's it.
[breathes heavily]
[baby crying]
[baby cries]
Hi.
It's okay, its's over.
[Melandra snarling]
[♪♪♪]
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
-[indistinct whispering] -[floor creaking]
You don't get this one, bitch!
[grunts]
[thuds]
[baby coos]
DANIEL: Jules!
Jules!
Jules! Jules!
[grunts]
Okay.
[baby crying]
Come on. Oh, come on, please!
[screams]
Don't. Stop.
-Take her. -DANIEL: No. No.
JULIE: Just get her out.
Go.
I'll come right back.
[baby crying]
[Daniel grunting]
[Melandra snarling]
[baby crying]
-[Daniel grunting] -[baby crying]
Get away from her.
[Daniel grunting]
[chokes]
This is my child!
Get out!
[Melandra screams]
[pants]
[baby crying]
Daniel, you okay? Daniel?
[ambulance sirens blaring]
Help! Help! Please, my wife.
Jules. Jules.
Hey, hey. Jules.
Hey! In here!
MALE PARAMEDIC: Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go right.
FEMALE PARAMEDIC: Sir, I need you to clear the scene.
-Sir, what's her name? -Julie, Julie.
Julie? Julie?
How long has been down?
A few like... A few minutes, five minutes.
FEMALE PARAMEDIC: [speaks indistinctly]
Don't have a pulse. Start compressions.
Julie?
[♪♪♪]
[cries]
[baby crying]
He's calling for you.
[Andrew crying]
[♪♪♪]
Andrew.
-[Andrew coos] -[chuckles]
Hi, love.
Alright. Mommy's got you.
FEMALE PARAMEDIC: Let's go again. Clear.
[Julie gasps]
Picking up a faint heartbeat. Let's do some compressions.
Julie, can you hear me? Julie?
You stay with us. Come on, Julie.
Please. Jules, Jules.
Please come back to me.
I love you. I love you so much.
[baby cries]
-DANIEL: Come on. -Julie.
Will you take care of him?
Of course.
Goodbye, my love.
We'll be waiting for you.
[sobs]
FEMALE PARAMEDIC 1: Come on. Stay with us. Come on, Julie.
Picking up a faint heartbeat.
Going one more time.
-Clear. -[Julie gasps]
[baby giggling]
[♪♪♪]
[indistinct yelling]
[Daniel grunts]
Yeah.
Again. Ready?
[gasps]
[birds chirping]
Mommy.
[Julie chuckles]
[Daniel chuckles]
-Daddy, can I get one? -Hm-mm.
Mommy get one.
-Yeah. -Ah.
Um.
You want it?
-Yeah! -Yeah.
[♪♪♪]