[soft pensive music]
[train horn blares distantly]
[birds twittering]
[car alarm chirps]
[girl] My...my name
is Chloe Albright.
I am a second-year
medical student.
Yes, of course. Yeah.
No, I just... I, um...
I don't understand
this foreclosure notice.
Yeah, no, I spoke to
the regional manager, actually,
on...on March 25th
and then again on May 17th.
What?
No... No, no, no. I...
Yeah, no, I know that,
but my student loan
got suspended
and my dad's life insurance,
it never paid out.
Why?
Because suicide isn't covered.
Look, um...
This...this house is all that
my brother and I have left, OK?
No.
No, you...you cannot
take it from us, OK?
If you evict us from our home,
then we will have
nowhere else to go.
Hello?
Damn you.
[slams phone]
[sighs]
[line ringing]
Come on, TJ. Don't ignore me.
[bird caws]
[phone buzzing]
[boy] Do you know '1984'
was supposed to be,
you know, like,
a cautionary tale
for us average Joes?
Not a...not a goddamn
instruction manual
for the rich... [stutters]
..b-bitches that run the show.
You know, I mean,
they read the book and go,
"Hey, th-th-these
are some great ideas.
"Let's...let's do this."
Mind control for dummies.
I mean, c-c-can you
b-b-believe that shit?
And cell phones. Cell phones.
That's real b-big brother
except they don't need
to brainwash us to use them.
We pay for the privilege.
I mean, cops, politicians,
they don't protect and serve us.
They protect and serve
the hard-cash overlords from us.
They sell us the idea of freedom
while making sure
we never get it.
It's...it's all psychopaths
who say, "2 plus 2 equals 5,"
who say the best we're gonna get
is...is a boot in the face.
Bro! Could you just
shut the fuck up?
No, no, because if you ask me...
Shut... Hey, give me
the fuckin' book!
No more Book Club, Oprah.
-Alright? Goddamn!
-Fine, fine! OK!
[sighs]
Let's do this, man.
[tense music]
OK.
We got this.
-Alright.
-No, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing, Book Club?
You're the driver.
You're stayin' here.
I... Yeah, no, I know. I, um...
You know, I hate to be
the one to tell you this.
I don't have a licence.
You don't have
a driver's licence?
-Yeah.
-Oh, holy fuck.
What are we gonna do about you
not having
a driver's licence right now?
I...I...I don't know.
-[sighs]
-I don't know.
Dude, guess I'm just gonna
have to fuckin' kill you.
Whoa, whoa! OK, wait.
You said no-one was gonna...
-[fires BB]
-Fuck!
-[laughs]
-Fuck you!
Fuck!
Dude, I could have poked
my fucking eye out!
What do you think, I got
a real gun or something?
No, I don't know, I don't know!
[sighs] OK.
-Right pedal's gas.
-I know, I know.
Left pedal's...
Oh, you know so fucking much?
But you don't have
a driver's licence.
Yes, I know, I know. I just...
Look, I'm just... Look,
I'm still getting my cut, right?
TJ, I'm only doing this
so you get your fucking cut.
-You know that, right?
-Yes, I do.
That's the only reason I'm here.
I know.
Thanks.
Seriously, we...we, you know...
..be...we'd be dead
without you, so...
-I got you.
-Yeah.
You just...keep it runnin'.
I know.
-Just be careful, OK?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
-[TJ] Alright?
-Alright.
Right pedal, gas.
Left pedal, brake.
Brake. Yeah, I know.
Less than a minute, alright?
Yeah, just hurry, OK?
[tense music rises]
[exhales]
[TJ] Alright.
Alright.
Right pedal... Right.
[gunshot]
-Oh! Shit!
-[alarm blaring]
-Let's go!
-[ignition churning]
Start the car! [groans]
[man] Hey, you punk!
-Go!
-[engine sputters]
-Come on!
-Just start the car!
-Start the fucking car!
-Get out of here!
[tyres squealing]
[dramatic music]
[knock at door]
[knocking continues]
Hello?
Chloe, it's me.
-Can you let me in?
-Oh.
TJ. Hi... Whoa.
-[TJ] Fuck! Ow!
-[Chloe] Hold still, hold still.
-[TJ] Shit, Chloe! God.
-Yeah, shit is right.
What the hell were you thinking?
[stutters] No...no-one
was supposed to get hurt.
OK? Ross said that it...
Wait... Ross?
TJ, you...you pulled
this shit with Ross?
I couldn't do it alone.
I've told you to stay away
from him so many times. [sighs]
You dated him for three years.
You know he's not a bad guy.
[Chloe] He's bad news, TJ.
[TJ groans]
-Fuck!
-It's out.
Chloe!
He's not a bad guy, OK?
He just...
Things got away from him.
Things didn't get away from him.
He pushed them away.
We can't be like him, TJ.
-You cannot be like him.
-He's dead.
I think. I don't...
I don't know.
It's not easy...
..for me, Chloe, OK?
You know, you handle all...
You think that this
is easy for me?
No. No, I did this for you, OK?
-What?
-OK, I...
I know you're having
trou-trouble with tuition.
And...
..now they're gonna
take the house.
And I...I just
wanted to help, OK?
I know how this is
gonna affect you.
I just...I just want to help.
I couldn't just st-stand by...
..and let you go
through this, you know?
[Chloe mutters]
No, I know.
I know, OK? I fucked up.
I fucked up.
[indistinct chatter
over police radio]
Another one bites the dust.
Yeah, get the coroner
and his meat wagon here ASAP.
I don't want the locals
looking at this dead hoodlum
bleeding in the street.
[siren wailing]
You get a plate
on our wheel man?
-[deputy] No plate, Sheriff.
-[sheriff] Description?
-[deputy] Ski masks.
-[officer on radio] Sheriff.
We've got a flaming car
out on Mission Road.
Sounds like a match
for your getaway vehicle.
Huh.
Well, ain't that a thing?
Looks like our wheel man's
the brains
of this cluster fuck.
[Chloe] OK, I'm going to
ask you some questions, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
-TJ?
-Yeah, yeah.
I need you to be
100% honest with me, OK?
OK, did anybody see you?
[TJ] No. We...we wore
masks and gloves.
OK, good. Uh, did you tell
anybody about this?
No, no, I swear.
And the car? What about the car?
I ditched it.
I...I set it on fire.
Fire? That's smart.
OK, um... Whose car was it?
Stolen.
OK, then, you're fine.
You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna...
you're gonna stay here with me.
Right? You're gonna...
you're gonna keep a low profile.
They have absolutely no reason
to think that you would...
[TJ murmurs]
-[Chloe] What?
-[mouths]
What?
Ross's phone.
What about Ross's cell phone?
I...I...
It's on...it's on him.
It's on him and I forgot.
I just...
It's...it's...
You planned a robbery
on a fucking iPhone?
-Are they gonna go easy on me?
-Are they gonna go easy on you?
TJ, it is an armed robbery
where somebody ends up dead.
TJ, that is 25 to life.
But, you know,
I...I was only the driver.
You were only the driver?
You think that matters to them?
That doesn't matter to them.
And you going to jail,
that breaks my promise to Mom.
What are we gonna do?
We have to get the phone.
[TJ] How?
Just give me five minutes.
[Chloe] Out here,
regional budgets have been cut
and so the morgue
is pretty much a one-man shop.
And the sheriff's department,
it's overworked, understaffed.
The chief has been cracking down
on local meth-heads.
According to the news,
about an hour
before they
brought Ross's body in,
a girl was killed
when her car hit a tree.
So we know there are at least
2 bodies in there, 1 coroner.
Buys us some time to get inside
and find Ross's phone.
[TJ] Won't...won't his phone
be with the cops?
[Chloe] Not out here.
Ross and all he had on him
will be processed
at the morgue first.
His clothes, his phone,
everything will be
bagged and tagged
and locked in the evidence room
for the sheriff
to claim in the morning,
along with the coroner's
autopsy report.
Walk the perimeter,
look for access.
Yeah, and I'm sure they have
a back door for graverobbers.
[alarm buzzes]
[Chloe on intercom] Hello?
I...I'm a friend
of the girl who was in the...
..the car accident tonight.
I was hoping that
I could see her
for one last goodbye.
-[dog barking]
-Oh, fuck!
-[barking and snarling]
-Oh, fucking hell!
[TJ] Cujo's out back
and there's cameras everywhere.
-[dog barking]
-Fucking Fort Knox.
[barking]
Hello?
[TJ] This whole place
is locked down.
The only way
we're getting in
is through a fucking
body bag, you know?
-What if that can be arranged?
-Huh? What?
Do you still score Adderall
off that vet tech?
Yeah, yeah, you know,
it helps me focus.
I need you to call her.
Hey.
Whoa. Who is this?
Oh, this is my...my sister.
She...she's cool, so...
Hey.
Uh-huh.
-It's 50 for the Addy.
-And the propofol?
Listen, I got it.
But I need you to understand
that this shit is...
A sterile,
nonpyrogenic emulsion,
full name diisopropylphenyl.
It's used in the induction
and maintenance
of sedation anaesthesia,
and it works
by dramatically slowing down
the recipient's brain
and nervous system.
I study criminology
and forensic medicine.
150.
Come on. No deals today?
[TJ] Shh. Here.
So I hope y'all know
what y'all doin'.
That shit killed
the King of Pop.
Yeah.
[TJ] OK. Now what?
Now it's time to die.
[TJ] How does this,
uh, work exactly?
I inject it.
A few seconds later,
I'll be unconscious.
The propofol slows
my heart rate
and brain activity
to almost nothing.
I'll still be alive.
[TJ] I just have a bad feeling
about this, you know?
[Chloe] TJ,
it is after nine o'clock, OK?
By the morning, the sheriff is
going to be in that morgue,
hearing the results
of Ross's autopsy
and collecting his belongings.
How long after that do you think
it is going to take
until you are in custody?
Once I'm unconscious, you're
just gonna wait 30 minutes, OK?
What? Why?
Because I have to be cold
when they find me.
Otherwise, they'll...
they'll try to resuscitate.
Look, TJ, you are going
to wait 30 minutes.
You are then going to call 911
and you are going to say
that you saw a girl
OD in the underpass
and that you think
she might be dead,
but you aren't gonna give
a name or anything.
You understand that?
Yes, but as-assuming
this works,
how are you gonna get out?
Let's just worry about
getting me in first, yeah?
Look, I, um...
I should do this.
OK? Look, this was...
this was...
No, no, this was my mess-up.
Alright? Let me fix it.
[Chloe] You have any run-ins
with the local sheriff lately?
They won't remember me.
-Hey.
-[sighs]
Hey.
You know I love you.
Don't. Don't do that.
[dark music]
[Chloe exhales]
OK.
Hey, you alright?
OK, you gotta go.
You gotta get out of here.
OK.
Love you.
It's alright.
[dark music rises]
[heartbeat thudding and echoing]
[music intensifies]
[sheet ruffles loudly]
[metallic screeching]
[groans softly]
[grunts]
[shivers]
Oh!
[Chloe exclaims softly]
OK.
[door handle rattles]
[keys jingling]
Oh...
Oh, shit! Sorry.
[tense music]
[trolley clatters]
Oh!
[lock rattling]
[lock clicks]
[switch clicks, lock buzzes]
[papers rustling]
[slow footsteps]
[pen scratching]
[trolley rattles]
[metal clanging]
[man grunts]
-[intense music]
-[metal clangs]
[door clicks]
[breathes shakily]
[metal clangs]
[breathes heavily]
[door shuts]
[trolley clattering]
[keys jangling]
[breathes shakily]
[door creaks]
[squelching]
Oh, God! [gasps]
[switch clicks, light buzzes]
[dark music]
OK.
[gasps]
[inhales sharply]
[door clicks and squeaks]
[lock clicks]
Shit, shit, shit...
OK.
[switch clicks]
[frantic music]
[alarm buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[buzzing]
[man on intercom] Hey, you gonna
have Mannix waiting all day?
Come on already.
[gate rattling]
[lock buzzes]
[tapping on door]
[man] Yo, I'm here
for the seance.
No? No funnies today?
Man, this is no way
to spend your day.
You got a family,
dinner waiting for you at home?
Or are you too busy breakin'
bread with the dead, huh?
[chuckles] Come on, man!
What do you do for
a good time around here?
You got a girl back there
or something?
You know, every time
you hand me one of these,
I feel like we're
going to the beach.
Don't you wish there was
a sixpack in here, huh,
some Kool-Aid,
some chicken salad sandwiches?
Ooh, there she is.
Hey! Take it easy.
I'm just checking out
the merchandise.
[latch clicks]
Sheesh!
Oh, shit, I almost forgot.
About that guy in L.A.
looking for the liver?
Thank God for alcoholic
movie producers, huh?
[chuckles and wheezes]
Alright, well, let me know
if that works out
and you might see me
again tonight.
Lucky fuckin' me.
[dog barking outside]
[sorrowful music]
[gasps]
[softly] Oh, God.
You stupid asshole.
[exhales sharply]
[low uneasy music]
[gasps, breathes shakily]
-[Chloe shrieks]
-[Ross inhales sharply]
[coughing]
Ross!
Hey, hey, hey.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
Shh, shh! Hey. Shh, shh, shh!
Shh, shh!
It's Chloe. It's OK.
-[Ross coughing]
-What the...?
[Ross grunts]
Why the hell
are you not in a hospital?
I am. [coughing]
Who did this to you?
Was it the...
the guy with the keys?
Was it him? Yeah?
OK, was there anybody else?
Ross, have you seen
anybody else?
[coughs]
What the fuck is going on?
Chloe... [coughs]
-Shh, shh!
-What are you doing here?
[chuckles softly]
You dipshits planned
a robbery on an iPhone.
I know.
If I don't get it,
then TJ's going to jail.
[Ross murmurs]
It's not safe here.
What?
[Ross coughing]
OK.
TJ's going to freak out,
he finds out you're alive.
I'm going to get
to the evidence room
and then I'm gonna get you
the hell out of here.
-OK.
-OK, good.
You know where the keys are?
Yeah, I know where they are.
I'll be back.
[quiet eerie music]
[Chloe gasps]
[saw whirring in distance]
[crunching]
[ripping and squelching]
[saw continues whirring]
[saw powers down]
[switch clicks, saw whirring]
[whirring stops]
[squelching]
[grunts]
[creaking]
[saw whirring]
[crunching and cracking]
[tense music rises]
[whirring continues]
[whirring stops]
[phone buzzing]
[phone clicks]
[distorted voice on phone]
The order came through
for our man in L.A.
Mannix will be by in an hour.
[dramatic music]
Ross? OK. Hey!
I need you to get up, OK?
Ross? Ross!
OK. Hurry.
I know. Look.
I need you to come with me. OK?
Shit, I'm sorry.
-[Ross groans]
-I'm sorry! Shh, shh!
[panting]
OK.
I have the keys.
You need to get up
with me right now, OK?
-Come on.
-[Ross straining]
-I know it hurts. Shh! Shh!
-[grunts]
[shushing]
OK. I got you.
Good job. Ready? Almost there.
Just lean onto me.
-[Ross groaning]
-I know. Shh, shh!
-I got you...
-[metallic clanking]
-OK, you alright?
-Yeah.
-[groaning]
-Shh!
-OK?
-Alright.
[Chloe] We need to go.
We need to go, OK?
-[Ross groans]
-I know it hurts.
They cut you.
-[Ross exclaims]
-Hey, hey.
[panting heavily]
-Ross.
-Oh!
Ross, would you look at me?
We have to go.
-Now.
-OK.
-OK? Come on. I got you.
-Fuck!
[dark music]
[Chloe] OK.
You see the door?
We're going to get
through it, OK?
-OK, go. Right there.
-Oh! OK, OK, OK.
[Chloe shushing] OK.
[Ross groaning]
OK.
[key rattling]
-[keys jangle]
-Oh, God.
Fuck. [panting]
[unsettling music]
[keys jangling]
Chloe, what did they do to me?
They took your kidney, Ross.
[Ross] They what?
That's OK, though,
because you have another one.
Son of a bitch.
-[lock buzzes]
-Got it. Come on. Right now.
-OK.
-OK. Shh, shh, shh, shh!
[exhales] OK.
-[Ross groaning] Fuck!
-Shh, shh!
Alright.
[door handle rattles]
[Ross panting]
I'll slow you down.
You know you...you just
gotta go, right?
-I'm not leaving.
-What?
When I open this door,
you are going to run.
I still need to get
into the evidence room.
-OK.
-[lock buzzes]
OK. Almost there.
-[whirring]
-[Ross] Oh, shit. [groans]
[Ross] He sees us.
-Chloe...
-Shh!
[Ross] Shit.
He knows we're in here.
-OK.
-Fuck.
[tense music builds]
OK.
He's coming. He's coming.
Hey, hey, Chloe?
I'm...I'm sorry.
I fucked up.
I'm sorry for all of it.
I will stop him, OK?
You just fuckin' go.
Hey.
You cut the macho shit
right now, OK?
You left me once. You're not
fuckin' doing it again.
OK...
I shouldn't...
I shouldn't have ever left.
[Chloe] Where is it?
Last key, Ross.
Here we go.
We're on the last one.
-[lock buzzes]
-I got it!
Ross!
No. Ross.
Hey, I got the door, OK?
I need you to get up.
Come on, come on.
I need you to move.
[speaks indistinctly]
OK, I need you to come.
[straining] Come on.
[grunts] OK.
Come on, Ross.
[speaks indistinctly]
[both gasp]
[gas hissing]
[Chloe wheezes and coughs]
[Chloe coughs]
[gasps]
[softly] Ross...
Ross, Ross...
[grunting]
[coroner] I doubt
he can hear you.
[liquid squelching]
OK...please,
please, just let us go.
I won't say anything
to anybody, please.
[coroner]
And where would you go?
Back to your
rat-infested apartment?
To your tent city?
To your life of crime?
What? No.
No, that's...that's not me.
Then what are you doing here?
Attempting to claim that
which does not belong to you?
Do you think you're
deserving of it in some way,
that you've earned it?
Compensation for the toils
and petty grievances
that you've accrued
during your time on this Earth?
-[rubber gloves squeaking]
-[Chloe clears throat]
Maybe you feel like you got
dealt a bad hand
and you should be allowed
to slip a few extra aces
up your sleeve.
You ever considered
getting a job
or is...that completely
out of the question?
This country's filled
with people like you,
people who take, take, take.
They don't earn. You cheat.
You don't strive.
You cut corners.
You take shortcuts.
No, that's not me, though.
Fortunately for me,
you are all defined
by one undeniable truth.
All that you are...
..all that you've done,
all of your thoughts,
your feelings, your beliefs...
..your entire being
is worth considerably less...
..than the sum of your parts.
No.
No, no, no, no. Please, please.
Please. OK? You're wrong.
I...I am a student
and I know the opportunity
I have been given.
-I wanna make something out...
-What are you studying?
I study...I study...
forensic medicine.
That's an
underappreciated field.
Yeah.
Then you already know
that there are
over a million dollars' worth
of assets inside of you.
Kidney, heart,
liver, lungs, eyes.
That's before we get
into your plasma,
your bone marrow.
Even your skin bears a price.
You should have
valued yourself higher
before you broke
into this sacred place.
-I didn't have a choice.
-Of course you had a choice.
Just like he had a choice.
You obviously know
this young man.
Caught earlier this morning...
..cutting another corner,
taking another shortcut.
Look, I know
what he did was wrong.
I get that. I'm pissed.
But he...
he does not deserve...
Of course he deserves it.
Who wouldn't vote
to end this wretch's life
if it meant saving
a more worthy person,
a person of value?
You think life
is essentially fair?
Well, unfortunately,
life is not fair.
I know that life isn't fair.
Hey, I know that!
I know that...
-[gasps] OK.
-And what is your excuse?
My excuse?
My excuse is that
the medical examiner,
he determined my dad's
cause of death as suicide.
But it wasn't suicide.
I know that it wasn't suicide.
He suffered from PTSD,
psychotic episodes
and he was heavily medicated.
And then the insurance,
they cut off his medication...
Ah, suicide cancelled
the insurance policy
and you and Mommy
didn't get any money.
Sad tale.
A common one.
-A victim's excuse.
-No.
No, I am not
who you think I am, OK?
I got into forensics
because I want to help people
find the truth, like...
The truth is what I say
the truth is.
Your father was a pathetic loser
that did the world a favour
by ending his life.
And you, when you broke in here,
ended your life.
You are a sick man.
I'm not sick.
I'm the cure.
[monitor beeping]
[screams] No! No! No!
Please stop!
[Chloe sobbing]
[monitor beeping]
Please, please, please!
[Chloe sobbing]
-Oh!
-[monitor beeping slowly]
[coroner grunts]
[beeping slows]
It's OK, it's OK...
[squelching]
[beeping increases]
[grunting]
-[monitor beeping rapidly]
-[Chloe] No, no!
[sobs] No!
[beeping quickens and flatlines]
[Chloe gasping and weeping]
Ross...
[coroner] You know
this used to be
the largest hospital
in the county?
[water running]
Now it's just me down here.
And I do not like
uninvited guests.
[latch clicking]
[gas spurting]
[gas hissing]
[metallic clatter]
[exhales heavily]
[phone buzzing]
No...
Please!
No, please.
Please, I'm sorry!
Please!
[coroner] Shh-shh-shh-shh!
[Chloe whimpering]
Shh, shh. It's OK, it's OK.
Listen, listen, listen.
Not one word.
-Hi, sweetie.
-Hey, Dad.
Mom wants to know
if you're coming home tonight.
Oh, no, honey, I can't make it.
Daddy's working.
Oh. We miss you.
I miss you too.
I'll see you
for breakfast tomorrow.
Don't forget to call Brad
before school.
I won't.
Love you.
Love you too.
[gagging and coughing]
[sobbing]
I don't know what you want.
I'm sorry. I'm... [stammers]
Thank you for that.
Know that his death and yours
will bring renewed life
to someone who's willing
to sacrifice everything
for their beliefs
and now, thanks to me,
your trivial existence
will have meaning.
I'm going to give your
life worth,
piece by piece...
..by piece.
[Chloe] No...
[metallic clang]
[breathes heavily]
[straining]
[pants]
[dark tense music]
[gasps]
OK, OK, OK.
[groans] OK. OK.
I'm sorry, sorry.
[grunting]
I'm sorry.
OK. Alright.
Yes.
[panting] OK.
OK.
[strains]
Come on. Please.
[tense music builds]
Come on.
-[blade flicks]
-[winces]
[clanging]
[tense music continues]
[metallic clanging]
[inhales sharply]
[saw buzzing]
[motor rattling,
pipes whining]
[buzzing]
[motor whirring]
[saw buzzing]
Ahh!
[distant clatter]
[motor stops]
[footsteps approaching]
[soft uneasy music]
-[rattling]
-[Chloe gasps]
[trembling]
[blade clatters]
[whimpering]
[metal clangs, motor whirring]
[gasps]
[sad, tender music]
[music darkens]
[hissing]
[door creaks]
Eight...
[breathes rapidly]
[door opens]
[tense music]
[gun clicks]
Give it to me.
This is what this is all about?
Some dead loser's cell phone?
Just give me the fucking phone.
You know, for someone who's
a scholar of forensic science,
you should know a little more
about protocol procedure.
We would never leave
a live firearm unattended...
..which means that gun
is either unloaded...
..or it's fake.
-[gasps]
-[groaning]
-Give it to me!
-[grunting]
Oh!
[coroner groaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
No... No!
Damn!
[sighs]
[phone blips]
[quiet unsettling music]
[gagging]
-[man groans]
-[gasps]
[monitor beeping]
[stammers]
[monitor beeping steadily]
[gasps]
-[man grunting]
-Sorry...
Help me.
Please.
[whimpers] I'm sorry.
-Oh! Ah!
-[loud clanging]
[Chloe hyperventilating]
[people moaning]
-[moaning and wailing]
-Shh, shh, shh!
[gasping]
Oh, my God.
[coroner on intercom] Chloe.
Can you hear me?
Up here.
I assume TJ is your brother.
Naughty little boy, isn't he?
In literature,
they refer to him
as an irredeemable character,
loathsome.
I'm sure you disagree.
I can tell
he's had his problems.
Probably renders him
sympathetic in your view.
But to me,
he's just a pile of dog shit
on a pristine carpet
and tarnishing the environment
for those of us
that are hard-working,
those of us
that are law-abiding
and those of us
that contribute.
[microphone clatters]
Luckily, the cell phone
you've risked so much for
holds the key
that will imprison
your feeble-minded brother
for what's left
of his worthless life.
You know what they call
someone like TJ in prison,
Chloe?
They call them "June bugs".
Do you know why
they call them June bugs?
Because they only live
for six months.
[gasping]
But I believe you sought
to better your life.
But your delinquent brother
pulled you back into this world
and now you are one step away
from Ross's fate.
Turn yourself in to me
now, Chloe.
[grunting]
[switch clicks]
[dog panting]
[softly] Here she is.
Yes. Go find her.
[dog barking]
[keypad clicking]
[line ringing]
[phone buzzes]
[phone click]
Hello?
TJ?
Oh, Chloe, where are you?
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
I'm...I'm still inside.
Are you alright?
TJ...
Look, they, uh...
..they hurt people here.
OK, wh-what do you mean?
I don't know. It's really
hard to explain right now.
-Chloe...
-TJ, I...
I think I failed you.
I'm so sorry.
I can't get your phone.
I tried really hard.
I promise.
-Are you in danger?
-No, you don't worry about me.
I need you to get
the hell out of this state.
Chloe, I'm not
leaving the state.
I am not asking you
right now, OK? I...
Look, I couldn't save Mom.
I couldn't help Dad,
and I am not being the one
to lose you too,
so I need you to listen to me.
I'm not leaving you.
Chloe, just stay where you are.
TJ, now, you listen to me
right now.
[static, line beeps]
TJ?
Hello?
[footsteps approach]
[coroner] I had to cut the line.
Can't have you making
outgoing calls.
-[dog snarls]
-Don't worry about him.
He's a good boy.
He's trained to maim
and detain, not kill.
[blows whistle]
[dog snarling and barking]
-[grunts]
-[dog yelps]
[dog barking]
[barking]
Hi.
Yeah, um, I'd like to speak
to the sheriff.
[blows whistle]
[grunts]
[indistinct chatter
on police radio]
Sheriff.
Well, if it ain't TJ Albright.
What can I do for you
this fine evening?
I'll, uh...I'll...
..I'll confess.
I just, um... I need you
to do something for me first.
What's that?
I need you to save my sister.
[dog barking in distance]
[panting] Oh, shit.
[dog panting and growling]
[dog sniffing]
[growling]
[barking]
-[barking]
-[Chloe whimpers]
[dog continues barking]
-[grunts]
-[dog whimpers]
[dog growling]
Alright.
You want it? You like this?
-OK, OK.
-[barking and snarling]
OK, OK!
[dog snarling]
[gate rattling]
[panting]
TJ.
[locks buzz]
Slow down there, tiger.
Oh, God! Oh! Sheriff!
We need to...we need
to go outside right now.
-Miss Chloe Albright.
-Don't...
TJ here was bullshitting me.
Ooh... It's OK, TJ.
What in Christ's name
is going on?
OK, um...
OK, look, the coroner,
OK, he...he's...he's keeping
people alive, OK?
He is selling...
he is selling their organs
and bits and parts of them
and I think he has killed
a lot of people.
That's quite an accusation
this late on a Friday.
You need to get in there, OK?
I saw him. I saw him.
[sheriff] It's OK.
Sheriff, he murdered somebody
right in front of me.
[sighs] Come on.
I never liked this coroner.
Old-timer before him,
he was easy.
This guy's
a pretentious nightmare.
Yeah, yeah.
[sheriff] If he's the psycho
you say he is,
I'm looking forward to being
the swift boot of justice
up his ass.
Tell you what.
You two stay put
while I go see what's what.
[Chloe] OK, OK.
But, Sheriff,
you need to be careful.
I'm telling you,
he's dangerous.
OK.
Thank you. TJ...
Oh!
[gasps]
What the fuck?!
TJ, TJ, just run! TJ!
Dangerous, huh? Well, so am I.
Get...
[grunting]
[Chloe] No!
-Mm-mm, no.
-No, no, no!
-[crack]
-Oh!
Oh! TJ!
[Chloe hyperventilates]
[stammering]
Sh-sh-sh-sh-sh...
..shut the fuck up!
-Whoa...
-Let's go.
-OK...
-Get the fuck away from him!
Hey, now.
Let's not be hasty.
Is that Ross's gun?
Put the gun on the ground,
Miss Albright.
TJ, TJ, get behind me right now.
Chloe, we should just
do what he says.
No.
No, we are walking out of here.
Don't make me kill you.
You wouldn't...
..because we're more
valuable to you alive.
Right?
[sheriff] Yeah.
I wouldn't be too sure
about that.
[coroner on intercom]
The gun is fake.
Shit.
Now...
..this one is real.
Changes your odds of survival
a little bit, now, don't it?
[Chloe] Oh, TJ...
[coroner] I want them alive.
Oh, come on, man! You serious?
-I just...
-Hyah!
-Oh!
-Move! Run, TJ!
[Chloe] Go!
[gate rattling]
[Chloe] TJ, the gate! TJ!
-We're trapped...
-No, no, no, that's not good.
That's not good.
[dog snuffling and grunting]
Bad...dog.
[whimpers]
-[TJ] Come on.
-OK.
[Chloe] Shit! Go!
[blows whistle]
[dog barking and snarling]
That-a-boy, Mac.
Burn 'em down.
[dramatic music]
[dog snarling]
Go!
[Chloe grunting]
Let's go. Go.
Just go. Go! Go, go!
[dog snarling]
Fuck.
[barking]
[gasping]
TJ?
TJ?!
TJ!
[dog barking]
-[snarling]
-Shit! No! Chloe!
[snarling]
Chloe! Fuck!
[TJ yelling on monitor]
Chloe! [whimpering]
TJ!
[TJ] Let me go!
[screams] Chloe!
-[gasps]
-[TJ groans and sobs]
[laughs]
[gasping]
-[snarling]
-Chloe!
-Get off!
Get off me! Get off me!
[both shouting]
-Get off of him! Get off of him!
-[TJ sobbing]
Get off of him! Get off!
-[both yelling]
-[dog snarling]
[TJ] Come on, get him off!
Get him off!
[sobbing]
Get him off! Get him off!
-[sparks zapping]
-[Chloe shrieking]
[dog snarling]
[yelling]
[dog yelps]
[Chloe gasping]
[TJ moaning]
[continues laughing]
[panting]
TJ? TJ?
[TJ murmuring]
-You have to get up.
-No, I need a minute, OK? No.
[grunts]
Come on. You've got to get up.
You've got to get up.
[both grunting]
[dog snarling]
[TJ] Slow down, down.
Fuck. Alright.
[sighs] OK, we're trapped.
[barking]
OK.
OK, it's locked.
We got to break in.
Look on the ground, OK?
[tense music]
-This will work.
-Yeah.
OK, OK.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
-I need you to twist it.
-I know.
[dog growling]
-[Chloe] One, two...
-Come on.
[grunting]
-OK, that's it.
-Yep, go.
-[dog snarling]
-OK, OK.
[snarls]
[barking]
[panting]
[Chloe gasping]
You OK, bud?
They rattle your brain?
Where are they?
[sheriff] They went down there.
Keep 'em there
till we can drive them to us.
-How?
-Smoke 'em out.
Tear gas in my car.
[horn honking]
What the fuck is that?
Mannix.
Shit!
No-one's supposed to know
about me, remember?
[Chloe panting]
TJ.
Come here. Come here.
-OK? It's OK.
-I'm so sorry, Chloe.
-[Chloe] No.
-I'm sorry.
It's OK. It's OK.
-You're OK.
-I'm sorry, Chloe.
Hey.
It is going to be OK.
-Shh!
-No, it's not.
-No, we're trapped.
-Look at me.
There is going to be
a way out of here.
You need to trust me.
-Yeah, OK.
-OK.
-We're a team.
-Yeah, I know.
Come on.
[upbeat funk music playing]
[sarcastically]
"Wow, look at me.
"I'm the coroner. I got keys."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, open up the door.
[gate rattling]
What's the deal?
You're not gonna
let me in this time?
There's been a situation
with the liver.
-I lost it.
-What?
What the fuck, man?
That puts us down 100 grand.
I'm in the process
of replacing it.
I need you to come back
in an hour.
What the fuck
is up with your eye?
Why did you change
this shit up on me?
You know Mannix is
a creature of habit.
You're making me nervous.
I'm starting to sweat in places
you don't wanna hear about.
What the fuck?
Is that a cop car?
What if he sees me?
[laughs]
Oh, shit!
You sly motherfucker, you.
You got a pig
working for you, don't you?
That's how you get
the live ones.
Me and Chase,
the pick-up guy in Lancaster,
we was wondering about that.
Fuck, now I owe him 50 bucks.
I knew I smelled bacon.
So where is he?
Can I meet him?
Or her. I'm down
with either one.
We're all part of the
same team, right?
It's... What?
Ugh!
[gasps] Gunshot.
Oh, God. Who's shooting who?
It doesn't matter. OK.
Come on.
[Mannix] Motherfucker!
[wheezing]
What?
You just cost us $100,000.
[sheriff] He had a big mouth.
Shame we can't sell that.
We would have raised
a pretty penny.
[Mannix groaning]
Ow! [gasping]
[panting]
-TJ.
-[TJ] What?
[Chloe] Over here.
-Move this?
-Yeah.
Shh!
Shh! Shh!
[shelf clattering]
OK.
-Can we get through?
-[TJ] Yeah, yeah, we can.
[Chloe] Shh! Shh!
OK.
-[thudding]
-[Chloe groans]
-[TJ] You OK?
-Yeah, there's just some pipe.
-Watch it.
-OK.
[Mannix groaning in distance]
[Chloe] Shh, shh, shh.
[Mannix groaning]
[grunts]
[Mannix cusses in Spanish]
[coroner] You shot our contact.
You, Sheriff, have fucked us.
[sheriff] Not the way
I see it, partner.
This guy was shot
by some intruder.
The same punks
locked in the basement.
They killed him, not us.
Can't we just hand over
his liver?
[screaming]
I don't think they'll accept
a liver with buckshot, do you?
OK. How about the ones
you keep in reserve downstairs?
Spare parts
from drunks, junkies.
Kidneys are OK, eyes are good,
but livers are rotten.
How about yours?
Don't even joke.
You so much as raise
an eyebrow at me
and I will shoot you
in the fuckin' face.
And what story will you tell?
Any one I want.
I'll be a goddamn hero,
stopping the Calexico Butcher.
Might even get a parade.
Squirrelly SOB, ain't he?
[Mannix groaning]
[moaning]
I'll make the call.
I'll tell them there's
been a slight hiccup...
..but there's
a solution in play.
What about him?
Get the tear gas.
We need a liver.
[Mannix wheezing]
I have the item
you requested on hand.
But you'll need a new courier.
[distorted voice]
Drive it yourself.
Transfer me an extra 50.
Your rush is not my problem.
[murmuring in Spanish]
I'm sorry, TJ.
[TJ] No, no. He's gone.
[murmuring]
Your man getting blindsided
is not my fault.
Misfortune is remedied
by ingenuity.
And money.
[distorted voice]
Deliver in two hours.
You'll have your extra.
Don't be late.
Rats in the walls.
[intense music playing]
[Mannix groaning]
[TJ] Grab his legs.
Grab his legs.
[monitors beeping distantly]
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on.
-[Chloe] Shh, shh, shh!
[TJ] He's...he's bleeding
all over the place.
[Mannix] Who the hell
are you guys?
No-one. OK, OK, good.
Well, you just
saved my ass back there,
so that's got
to make you somebody.
[Chloe] OK,
this is gonna hurt.
-[cusses]
-Sorry! Shh, shh, shh!
I'm sorry.
Get me the hell out of here, I
got 10 G's with your name on it.
-Make it 25.
-TJ.
Our enemy's enemy has money.
We need it, he needs us. Right?
I don't know. I can't think.
Done. But Mannix can't be dead.
The fuck?
Tear gas.
OK, uh, TJ?
I need you to focus, OK?
Focus. Get back...
-[TJ stammering]
-[Chloe coughing]
OK, look at me.
OK, you need to put this on.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
-Breathe. Breathe.
They're going to come
after me, OK?
You take him,
you go where it's safe
and then you wait and then
you get the fuckin' money.
-No, no. Wait, wait...
-Listen to him, OK?
I'm gonna be fine.
You go. Go, go, go, go.
OK, OK.
[Chloe] Go, go. There, under.
You follow him, OK?
[coughing]
Oh, fuck!
[dramatic music]
[music fades]
[monitors beeping]
[gagging]
-[sheriff] Dammit!
-[Chloe coughing]
God!
Alright.
OK.
[sinister music]
[stun gun sparking]
[TJ groaning]
-[coroner] OK.
-[Chloe coughing]
[coroner] Shh! Shh! Shh!
Go, go.
-[sheriff] Thanks.
-You're welcome.
[Chloe wheezing, coughing]
[coughing and gasping]
[TJ grunting]
[gagging]
[gasping]
[Chloe straining]
[canister clangs]
[sheriff] I got her!
Nowhere to run, baby.
Drop the hammer.
Ugh!
[coughing and gagging]
[monitors continue beeping]
[monitor flatlining]
Shit.
[coroner]
Your sister owes me a liver.
Yours will do.
[TJ whimpering]
[coroner] Chloe?
You have completely
ruined my life.
I can explain a lot of things,
but a dead sheriff
is not one of them.
Looks like I'll have to move on.
But before I do,
you should know
that this pathetic life
of your brother's...
..will bring renewed life
to three, maybe even four
more worthy people.
And once he's donated
to the deserving...
[gasps]
[coroner whispers]
..it will be your turn.
TJ?
TJ. Hey.
Hi. Hi.
It's gonna be OK, OK?
I got you.
-[weakly] Behind you...
-What? What?
Behind you.
Hi.
[Chloe shrieking]
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
An eye...
..for an eye.
[whimpers] No...
[Chloe screaming]
[continues screaming]
[Chloe gasping]
[coroner groaning]
Oh, holy shit.
[gasping]
[both grunting]
[shattering]
[panting]
[dark intense music]
[laughing]
It's my turn now.
[blade ringing]
[both grunting]
[Chloe panting]
Huh!
Arggh! Arggh!
[Mannix] Take it!
-[Chloe grunts]
-[squelch]
[grunting and groaning]
[Chloe panting]
You are the sickness.
I'm the cure.
[blade clatters]
[coroner grunting]
[laughing]
[music fades]
[sighing]
[laughing]
[groans]
[momentous music builds]
I'm OK.
OK, w-w-we saved you, so...
..you know, you...
..you gotta pay.
I saved you back, so...
..seems like we're even.
That's bullshit.
I still need something.
You get it for me...
..I pay you in full.
[dog whimpering]
God, I hate that damn dog.
Dr Death killed his reserves.
No loose ends, I guess.
Not that it matters now,
you arrogant fuck.
Mannix is a bad dude,
but that motherfucker,
he's gonna be the devil's bitch
for sure. [chuckles]
[TJ] OK.
OK, she's done.
Pay up.
[Mannix]
A deal's a deal, my man.
[birds singing]
[soft music]
[blows whistle]
[dog barking]
[Mannix grunts]
[TJ] Nice shirt, man.
Huh!
Hey, you good?
Yeah, I'm better than ever.
You need a ride?
You need a doctor.
There's one where I'm going.
Close enough.
So can I drop
you two off or what?
Yeah.
-[Mannix] Alright.
-You can drop us off.
-Oh, hey, uh...
-[engine starts]
I almost forgot
to give this to you.
-Ready to get outta here?
-Fuck, yeah.
[engine revs]
[intense electronic music rises]
[snuffling and grunting]
[intense electronic music]