[intriguing music playing]
[reporter 1] It's a race against time
in Thailand
to save the young members
of a missing soccer team.
The boys, ranging in age 11 to 16,
have been feared dead
after they went missing
with their 24-year-old soccer coach.
[music continues]
[interviewer] There's no pressure. Okay?
[reporter 3] The fate
of a dozen youth soccer players
and their coach in Thailand
has captivated people around the world.
[interviewer] You don't have to
answer any questions you don't want to.
There are no right or wrong answers.
[reporter 4] This is
the biggest international rescue attempt
that's ever been staged.
There's help here from all over the world.
[water trickling]
[interviewer] It's important to us
that you feel comfortable.
-We can stop at any time.
-Okay.
[interviewer] Okay.
[reporter 5] It was a drama
the whole world watched unfold.
Stuck inside a flooded Thai cave
for 17 days.
[music continues]
[man] The outside world has no idea.
They probably have no idea at all
what it was actually like inside the cave.
The truth might be different
from what they think.
[intense music playing]
[birds chirping]
[boy 1] Stay close, Titan.
That day, we had soccer practice.
[dogs barking]
-[Titan in Thai] Help! There are dogs!
-[boy] Come on! Let's go!
[yelps]
[boy 3 laughing] Dummy.
[boy 1] There's a group of dogs. My bike!
[man] Let's go! [clapping]
[in English]
I'm Eakapol Jantawong, or Eak.
[Eak] One foot in!
A coach is a leader.
[in Thai] Shuffle, Tao.
[in English] You need discipline.
[in Thai] Look at your teammates.
[in English] You must love this job.
Two passes only. Three touches max.
[whistle blows]
All right. Forward! Dom, come in.
-Tao, can you go forward?
-[boys laughing]
[boy] Let's go.
[Eak in English] Most kids
who go to school in this area
usually become thugs, drinkers or smokers.
We have the soccer team
to keep them away from drugs.
[in Thai] Go! Go!
[in English] In terms
of family background,
they mostly come from poor families.
[in Thai] Get in! Get in there.
[in English] I want to play
for the national team.
[Eak in Thai] Hey, defense.
Watch out for your opponents.
[in English] I like Man U.
Manchester United.
Man U.
[Eak in Thai] Finish it.
[in English] Coach Eak likes every play
to be practiced, so we work hard.
[Eak in Thai] Pass it, Mix!
[in English] I try to support these kids
so they can get a scholarship
at a high-level academy.
[in Thai] Let Tao finish it.
[all cheering]
[blowing whistle]
Break time.
[in English] At that time
I was 24 years old.
Off the field,
I was just their older brother.
[in Thai] Come on.
[in English] We're not related
but we're brothers.
We spend time together like a family.
Top North team versus Top South.
The Score is 2-0.
We were planning
to go to the cave after practice.
[adventurous music playing]
City kids go to the mall
in their free time,
but country kids only have the mountains
and the forests.
Tham Luang Cave
was the most exciting place.
I'd been many times.
After practice, we ate.
I remember I only had about ten sticks
of grilled pork and a kilo of rice.
[man in Thai] That's what they said.
[in English] I threw my leftovers away.
[boy 1 in Thai] Eat the sticky rice.
[boy 2] What is it?
[boy 1] It's sticky rice.
[clucking]
[Eak] Hurry and get ready.
-[boy 3] Let's go.
-[boys] Come on, let's go.
[in English] After eating,
we rode our bikes to Tham Luang Cave.
[Eak in Thai] Hurry up.
-[boy 3] Wait for me.
-[boy 5] I'm coming.
-[hip-hop music playing]
-[boy 6] Me too.
[boy 7] What?
[Eak] Follow me. Come on.
Let's go.
[boy 6] Don't do that, Tle.
[Eak in English] There was no rain.
It was hot and sunny.
[music continues]
[boys] Whoo-hoo!
-[boy 6 in Thai] Let's go, let's go!
-[boy 8] It's not that. It's…
[in English] Some were excited
for their first cave experience.
-[in Thai] Come on, let's go!
-Let's do this!
[Eak in English] We raced each other
as hard as we could.
[indistinct chatter]
[in English] I was always left behind.
I'm so tired.
Titan was the youngest in the group,
and everyone wanted to tease him.
There wasn't a single day
I didn't get teased.
Titan's strengths?
I can't think of any. [laughs]
[hip-hop music continues]
Titan and I are close.
We're like brothers.
[music continues]
We rode past orange groves.
[turns off music]
[Eak] Let's pray to Jao Mae.
[boy 1] Look over there.
[boy 2] Hurry.
[Eak] Let's go.
We saw the sign and we all said,
"We can't go inside."
I think the sign said, "There are
flash floods from July to November."
We went in the cave on June 23rd.
It wasn't even the rainy season yet.
Let's pray to Jao Mae Nangnon.
Jao Mae is the guardian of this place.
If we do something
without asking for her permission first,
something bad can happen.
[boy] There's a legend
about Jao Mae Nangnon.
She was a princess.
There was a horseman
who fell in love with the princess.
They ran away together.
[horses galloping]
-Soldiers chased them.
-[horse neighing]
The horseman went to look for food.
[man shouting]
[boy] The soldiers killed him.
The princess waited,
but he never came back,
so she used her hairpin to kill herself.
The mountains look like the princess.
[somber music playing]
-[Eak in Thai] Let's get the bikes.
-[boy 1] Let's go into the cave.
[boy 2] Come on.
-[boy 3] Wow.
-[boy 4] I see.
[Eak in English] When we arrived
at the cave entrance,
the kids were excited and they were like,
"Wow! It's this big?"
[in Thai] Hurry up.
[in English] Guys,
pray before you enter the cave.
We'd usually leave everything behind.
[Eak in Thai] Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[pensive music playing]
[in English] We didn't bring food.
We only had flashlights when we entered.
[music continues]
[Eak] I had Tee lead the way
and I was the last one inside.
Tee was like my special assistant.
I felt more at ease
when I had Tee with me.
Because at the very least, with Tee there,
he could help take care
of the rest of the kids.
[indistinct chatter]
[in Thai] Let's go.
[Tee in English] I had been inside before.
So I was confident.
I wanted to take the boys there.
[music continues]
We were only supposed to stay for an hour.
I had a tutoring session.
[indistinct chatter]
[all cheering]
[boys howling]
[indistinct chatter]
[boy in Thai] Wow, look at that!
We were messing around.
[all cheering]
[boy] We were teasing Tee
because he had a girlfriend,
joking that they take pictures together
and hold hands.
[all cheering]
[boy] Let's go, let's go.
[Eak] They were joking around
the whole way.
When I saw that. I was happy.
[boy 1 in Thai] There are more places
to hide ahead?
[boy 2] Yes, there are.
[boy 3] You know you can't go in there.
[intense music playing]
[Eak in English]
When we arrived at the T-junction,
we couldn't go
further than a few meters to the right.
We had to take a left to go further.
[music continues]
[boy] I think I was scared
when we got to the T-junction.
There was a stream of water.
I was afraid it would flood
and we couldn't get out.
No matter what season it is,
there's always water there.
It's never dry.
[Mix] I said,
"A lot of water is pouring in.
Should we go back? We're far enough."
They said, "Go back by yourself
if you want to. What, are you scared?"
[indistinct chatter]
I let everyone decide for themselves.
If they chose not to keep going,
we'd all go back.
We voted. It's more beautiful further in.
-[boy 1] Let's go. Let's go now.
-[boy 2] Let's go.
[Mix] They said, "Let's keep going."
But I was thinking how I wanted to leave.
[Eak in Thai] Follow me, follow me.
[boy] Let's go inside.
[Mix in English]
We left our bags and shoes.
We were afraid they'd get wet.
We kept going with only our flashlights.
[indistinct chatter]
[Tee in Thai] Hey, wait for me.
[thunder rumbling]
[man in English] I've been working
at Tham Luang-Khun Nam Nang Non
for about two years.
In the evening,
I have to check if anyone is still inside.
[thunder rumbling]
It usually starts raining in July.
It was June.
How can it start raining in June?
From the entrance,
the length of Tham Luang Cave
is 10 kilometers and 316 meters.
When the rainy season starts,
the water flows from the peak.
The water flows down from every direction.
It's full of holes inside.
I counted eleven bikes.
At first, I thought they were adults.
If you enter without the staff knowing,
you could be stuck all night.
I mean, who'd know?
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
[Tee] As we went further,
it got more beautiful, so we kept going.
[Eak] There was like an aura drawing us.
I wanted them to see something beautiful.
[gentle music playing]
I thought I could take them
to learn something new.
[boy] It was very beautiful.
It was like diamond dust, just amazing.
There was a big chamber.
[music continues]
Titan had to leave
before five o'clock for his class.
I said, "Guys, let's go back.
Time's up. We'll come again."
Let's go.
-[water trickling]
-[boy laughing]
[Eak] So we started to wade back.
While we headed back,
we were just chatting like normal.
Until the T-junction.
At the T-junction, I thought…
It was one way in and out.
"Is this right?" Eak said yes.
[Eak] The water flooded the T-junction.
It was covered entirely,
and we couldn't go forward.
At that moment, I suddenly thought,
"Oh no. "We're in a big mess."
We were in shock.
So I said,
"Let's find a way to get out of here."
I was going to check another way.
I decided to dive.
[tense music playing]
I felt anxious.
I didn't know if Eak would find a way out.
[tense music continues]
[Eak] I opened my eyes,
but I couldn't see anything.
I tried to dig.
[digging]
I couldn't make it through.
I was about to run out of breath.
[water sloshing]
I thought I was dying.
At that moment, I shook the rope.
[boys in Thai] One, two…
[Eak in English] The boys pulled it.
[boy in Thai] One more time.
[in English]
I had completely run out of air.
[boys in Thai] Two. Again.
One, two. One, two.
[indistinct chatter]
[in English] I told the kids
it's a dead end.
When Eak said that, I got quiet.
I didn't know what to do.
[Phet calling]
Anybody here?
It was around five or six o'clock,
and they were still inside.
My boss sent out two more staff
to help the search.
[ranger 1] Where are you?
[ranger 2] Anybody there?
[rangers calling]
[Phet] We walked from the first chamber
to the second chamber.
We yelled out, but we couldn't find them.
[rangers calling]
There was already a lot of water.
[ranger 2 in Thai] Anyone there?
[Phet in English] They weren't in
the third chamber either.
I hoped we'd find them at the T-Junction.
[ranger 2] Is anybody here?
[Phet] When I got there,
I found their bags and shoes.
I looked around
until I found their phones.
At that moment, my heart sank.
They're kids.
[ranger 1 calling]
[in Thai] Anyone hear me?
[calling] Can anyone hear us?
[Phet in English]
The cave was full of water.
At that point I thought,
"Man, what do I do?"
"How can I get these kids out?"
Hello!
I said: "Let's get out and call for help."
[tense music playing]
[water sloshing]
[Eak] When I saw the water level rising,
I had to do whatever I could
to keep the kids calm.
So I tried to act as normal as possible.
I told them, "Maybe it's just the tides."
I thought the water level would drop.
So I said,
"Let's go find somewhere to sleep."
"We'll come back and check tomorrow.
When it drops, we'll get out."
[in Thai] Two, three, yeah.
[Titan in English]
We tried to stay positive.
[indistinct chatter]
I had missed my session. So I thought,
"Perfect. I don't have to go to my tutor."
[chuckles]
[Eak] No one was panicking
because it was like we were
just going to sleep in a new place.
We're having an adventure,
something like that.
[indistinct chatter]
That night, I was only afraid
of my parents scolding me.
Some of us hadn't even told our parents
where we were going.
I thought my parents
would probably look for me
and try to find out where I went.
[crickets chirping]
[woman] I worry about Tee when he goes out
or goes somewhere with friends.
I kept waiting, but he never came back.
I was concerned
Tee had gotten into a fight with someone.
A kid from his school came and told me,
"Tee is stuck in the cave."
[contemplative music playing]
The first time my husband took me there,
I was scared.
When I went inside the cave
and I saw people…
-[man 1 in Thai] Go down to the ridge.
-[whistle blows]
[man 2] Let me help.
[woman 2 in English]
Shoes were left at the front.
No one had moved anything.
His bicycle was there,
his bag and belongings.
I was so shocked.
[indistinct chatter]
[man] The atmosphere
at the entrance was eerie.
I felt terrible after, I was breathless.
I didn't know what to do but pray
to our sacred beings to protect my son.
I had no idea he was going to the cave.
In the morning he only said that
he was going to play in a soccer match.
He said nothing about going to the cave.
People came to ask me questions,
but I kept crying.
I couldn't answer them
because I was so sad.
[sniffling]
[shivering]
[boy] The first night
I slept with the flashlight on.
If it got completely dark,
everyone would get scared.
[shivering]
[Titan] We slept next to each other,
and held one another.
[Tee] It felt as cold as ice,
we could feel the frostbite.
[exhaling]
I could only hear the sound of our breath
and my own heart beating.
It went…
[imitates heart beating]
…in rhythm.
[heart beating]
[water dripping]
[Eak] The first night,
what I was worried about
was whether or not
we would be able to get out.
I had to take care of these 12 lives
without knowing what would happen next.
[heart beating]
[newscaster] Our first story is
an incident that happened last night.
A Thai cave is flooded and 13 are trapped.
DUO NEWS
Right. Even rescue workers
haven't been able to get to them.
Okay, count off.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
-Five.
-Six.
As of now, we have sent eight teams.
In terms of headcount,
that's almost 50 officers.
They're carrying diving gear and food.
[suspenseful music playing]
At the time, there were very few of us
who knew their way around Tham Luang Cave,
especially those of us
known as cave explorers.
THAM LUANG MAP THAM LUANG
KHUN NAM NANG NON LEGEND
I happened to have
prior knowledge of the cave.
The first time I went to help,
I saw all the water at the T-junction.
We started our rescue mission
with equipment.
Water pumps, ropes,
things we could find around the area.
[motor whirring]
Now it's up to the water pumps
to clear out the path.
We were fighting massive amounts of water
with limited equipment.
The technology we had wasn't enough
to pump the water out.
[motor whirring]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
Once it starts raining, it won't let up.
I thought, "If it rains heavily, the water
will flood in and fill up everything."
"We probably won't find them
by that point."
If we don't get any more rain,
and the water level drops,
we might be able to pump more out.
That would be good news.
I was glad the governor was there.
He said he would keep us informed.
Every one or two hours,
he'd give us an update
My only hope is that they're doing well
and there will be no more rain.
We were against time and nature.
[officer 1]
Oh, the water is rising, see that?
[officer 2] I see.
[officer 1] Yesterday,
the water wasn't this high.
It's rising quickly
-[officer 2] It's getting higher.
-[officer 1] Yeah.
[Kamon] We had to work faster
because more water
was coming in from the back.
It was also very difficult
because the water was coming
from two channels that would meet
and surge towards the cave entrance.
That's what was troubling.
[tense music playing]
[Titan] When we woke up, there was water.
When I turned back around,
the water almost got to me
It was quick.
It kept coming. It kept following us.
[Eak] We had to solve the problem.
So we gathered
and discussed what to do next.
"Do we go forward?"
I told the boys
to use the flashlights sparingly.
[suspenseful music playing]
"Don't give up, no matter what."
[music continues]
Some of the kids started complaining,
"What are the rescue workers even doing?
Why haven't they come looking for us?"
[indistinct chatter]
We need more people.
[man in Thai] Seventeen.
[reporter in English]
How long before they're really in danger?
Uh, I… I cannot expect how long,
but every minute is important.
[tense music playing]
[woman 1 in Thai] Slowly. Be careful.
[Ei Khan in English] Titan, sweetie,
I'm waiting here to take you home.
[Biw's mom] Let's go home, son.
Come on, let's go home, Biw!
At that moment,
I felt like I had to call out to Titan.
I thought if he could hear me,
he would at least know
that I was waiting there.
[sniffling]
I would go to work
and get off around 8:00 or 9:00 p.m.
So during that time,
he was really close with Eak.
[indistinct chatter]
At the time, I could only think about
how much Titan looked up to Eak.
I said to myself,
"You must get Titan out, Eak.
I know you can do it."
Jao Mae,
please give our boys the strength.
Frantic search for 12 boys
and their football coach.
And desperate families
are waiting nervously for news.
[man] It was still
quite a local story at that time.
I didn't think
it would turn into anything.
And I honestly thought at that stage,
"Well, that's... that's 13 dead people."
But I remember
our news director was very, very keen.
He said,
"This is going to be a huge story.
Different units
have been coming here frequently
to provide us with important support.
There were all sorts of people
who came to help.
From doctors and nurses, to soldiers.
It was like the forces
of the whole country were there.
That was what I was most impressed with.
[Narongsak]
We have a patrol unit searching
for any other possible exit routes.
The Border Patrol will fly a helicopter
to check and see if there are
any other entrances to the cave.
Different local forestry forces
along with part of the military forces,
will patrol the area to find entry points
where water can flood in,
in order to block them.
The SEALs will fly in directly
from Sattahip at midnight.
I was the commander
of the Naval Special Warfare Command,
for the Royal Thai Fleet.
We were racing against time
and rising water levels.
[SEAL] Watch your feet.
[officer] A bit more, one, two.
We had to pump the water out
so the SEALs could find the kids
as quickly as possible.
[indistinct chatter]
[Apakorn] The SEALs are skilled divers.
When they first arrived,
they tried to dive through
and away from the T-junction.
As the water got higher,
we couldn't go further.
[water dripping]
[alarm beeping]
[Eak] Tee's alarm rang at 6:00
every morning.
We would have been more stressed out
if we didn't know the time.
We would have lived each day
without having any plan at all.
I organized the day as I would
under normal circumstances.
From morning until evening,
we would look for a way out.
Coach Eak told us,
"There's definitely a way out."
And we tried to find one every single day.
[gentle music playing]
I was trying to fight off
mental weakness in myself.
[indistinct chatter]
[Titan] We walked until we got tired.
It was around evening.
The only thing I could think about
was that I was hungry.
[boy in Thai] You want to give up?
[in English] I was so hungry,
and everyone kept talking about food.
That was aggravating.
It was freaking torture.
I imagined food in my head
and I wanted to eat everything.
"I want to order KFC.
Will they deliver to us here?"
[inhales] We couldn't stop thinking
about food.
[chuckles] One guy dreamed about
drinking his favorite brand of milk.
He was drinking the milk in his dream.
When he woke up, he found himself
with Adul's toe in his mouth.
[male voice in Thai] Pork skewers.
[Titan in English] I thought about when we
were eating at the soccer field at noon.
That was my biggest regret.
I ate very little.
I should have eaten a lot.
[indistinct chatter]
[solemn music playing]
I dreamed about a meal with my family.
[music continues]
I hoped that I would get to eat
my mother's cooking again.
We didn't have a lot of money.
My mother mostly cooked simple dishes.
[solemn music continues]
I missed my mom's cabbage curry.
I really wanted her cooking.
[water trickling]
[Eak] The only thing I could
tell them was, "Keep drinking water."
We had to do whatever we could to survive.
[Tee] Drinking water helped a little.
But we were still hungry.
Then I was starting to get very tired.
I had no energy.
I felt dizzy.
I immediately fell when I got up.
I had to protect these guys.
I couldn't let anything happen to them.
My parents passed when I was young.
In order to lighten the burden
on my relatives,
I had to be ordained into monkhood.
I was ordained for over ten years.
Being ordained as a novice monk
has made me a stronger person
mentally and physically.
If your mind is weak,
your body will be weak.
If your mind is strong,
your body will be strong.
Before we went to sleep, we would pray
and ask holy spirits for blessings.
We just asked Jao Mae Nangnon
to help us with a miracle.
We meditated to calm down.
To be with ourselves,
and not lose our focus.
We thought, even if no one is coming
to save us, don't panic, just stay calm.
[breathing deeply]
I took a breath
and prayed that we would make it.
[water dripping]
[breathing deeply]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
It's raining heavily.
THAIRATH MORNING NEWS
The entire ground of the national park
has turned into mud.
RESCUE MISSION FOR 13 LIVES, DAY 4
It's currently quite difficult for
our rescue teams to carry out their work.
[reporter]
How survivable is it inside there?
Depends where they are.
[reporter] Right. And what do you know
of these types of caves?
This system,
if they're… if they're in the right place,
they could survive for five, six days.
But the water now, the… the, uh...
the flood water
is… is getting higher and higher.
[water gushing]
I do have hope.
I want all 13 of them
to make it out safely.
[all chanting]
They told us to go to various places
to pray for the rain to stop.
Pray to the guardian spirits
at Tham Luang Cave
so that they could get the kids out.
[gentle music playing]
Mark is a small boy.
He's afraid of the dark.
The two of us have struggled
since he was little
because Mark's father and I divorced
when Mark was about a year old.
I didn't know
if my child was going to survive.
[sobbing]
It was too much for me,
so I fainted.
I couldn't control myself.
[in Thai] Are you feeling better?
Here, this is ammonia.
-Massage her.
-She has regained consciousness.
[water trickling]
[tense music playing]
[in English]
The water kept getting higher,
so we went further in
to try to find a way out.
[Tee] We reached
the farthest point we could go.
[Mix] We just couldn't find a way out.
There was only darkness.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I wanted to see the light.
[Tee] One of the boys shouted out,
"I can't take it anymore.
I'm tired. I want to go home.
[Tee in Thai]
Hey, we're going to make it. Trust me.
[Eak in English]
With all the stress piling on
and hunger on top of that,
it was getting harder to cope.
[indistinct chatter]
Everyone blamed themselves.
We all thought, "We shouldn't have come."
Eak said,
"If anyone wants to cry, let it all out."
I wanted to see my parents. I was hungry.
We told each other
that we loved each other.
At that time I was so stressed out.
I didn't think we'd make it.
I would tell them, "No matter
what happens, we must never fight."
"We must always help each other out."
I think it got quiet for five minutes.
Then I started hearing
the sound of a helicopter.
Like it was flying over.
[imitating helicopter hovering]
-[boy 1] Hurry!
-[boy 2] Help us!
I heard what sounded like someone
drilling, or digging into something.
We're going to make it.
[Eak] Stop. Stop.
Everyone was excited.
We were hopeful again.
We had lost hope earlier
and we got it back.
[in Thai] Hello! Please help us!
[in English]
Is someone coming to rescue us?
Please help us!
We tried to find where it was coming from,
see if it was a person.
[water gushing]
Suddenly, I heard what sounded like water.
I heard the water gushing in.
So I tried to look.
Then I saw this black thing, like a wave.
[water gushing]
[man yelling]
It was like a flash flood.
When I saw that,
I told everyone to get to a higher place.
[all clamoring]
Everyone ran up, pushing each other.
[all shouting]
If Eak hadn't jumped,
he would've been swept away by the water.
[all shouting]
It was so loud.
Then it got quiet.
The water got still.
[water flowing]
We were at the highest point in the cave.
We couldn't find a way out.
The entrance was completely flooded.
[somber music playing]
[water sloshing]
[Apakorn] The water was flooding the cave.
It was crashing into the walls.
[imitating water crashing]
The water was surging towards us.
I had never seen it before.
We had to retreat.
We had to go back
and start from square one.
It was depressing.
[Eak] We were trapped on both sides.
[Adul] We had no options left.
That meant we had to stay.
We couldn't go anywhere else.
We just hoped
that the water would stop there.
Hmm.
[water gushing]
[Tle] I thought about how we would die.
We would probably die drowning.
That's what I thought.
I worried about my mother.
She'd already lost one child.
I didn't want her to lose another one.
[Saksipong] Tle is a sensitive child.
As an only child,
he was the center of attention.
I have to hold him when he sleeps.
We sleep in the same bed, the three of us.
I blamed it on my luck.
I must have bad karma
because I didn't get to
raise my first child either.
If I lose this one too, I couldn't live.
[water dripping]
I did blame myself.
I was the one who brought them there.
I had to take responsibility.
I wouldn't want anyone to experience loss.
Experiencing loss
was something very painful for me.
When I was six years old,
my younger brother died.
Then, my mother,
who couldn't cope with the loss,
also passed away.
And not long after,
my father started falling ill
and he died too.
If one of them,
if any of them didn't make it out alive,
I wouldn't be able to face…
to look their families in the eye.
I wouldn't be able to confront them
and tell them how...
I brought their boys into the cave to die.
[somber music playing]
[water dripping]
[tense music playing]
We had nowhere else to go.
The only way to go was up,
and dig our way out.
[tense music continues]
We had no idea how thick it was.
"Help each other dig.
We'll get through." I told them.
We would take turns digging.
Without giving them something to do,
I thought that they would just sit around
talking or start thinking too much.
Then they would start
getting on each other's nerves.
We had to help each other.
-Let's help each other.
-[boy] Come on. Move that. [grunts]
Come help me.
We had to work together.
It was teamwork
just like when we played soccer together.
We can't play soccer alone, can we?
All of us have to play together.
[grunting]
We win and lose together.
-[Eak in Thai] Hey, slow down.
-[boy] Go forward.
[in English] The kids asked me,
"How far do you think it is?"
I said, "Five meters."
Everyone believed that.
[Eak] We imagined
that we'd turn up in the orange groves.
-[ethereal music playing]
-[birds chirping]
[indistinct chatter and laughter]
[Tle] If we made it out
we would eat other people's oranges.
Would they yell at us?
Would the owners kick us out?
We came up with a whole plan.
We just used our imagination.
Once we got out,
we would go down from the orange groves.
There would be a small shop
where we would buy something to eat.
Then, we would go to the cave entrance
and get our bikes and head home.
-[ethereal music playing]
-[laughing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[boy in Thai]
We have to make it outta here.
[Eak in English] So we kept on digging.
Some started wishing
for an asteroid to hit Earth.
-[explosion]
-[Eak imitates explosion]
After the hit, we could get out.
[panting]
The boys played around, teased each other,
made jokes, that helped them quite a bit.
[Tee] We joked about "If a naked woman
walked in here, what would you do?"
Adul said, "That's good.
I'm tired. We'll make her dig." [chuckles]
Everyone burst out laughing.
No one was expecting that.
Many funny things happened back then,
but we weren't in the mood to laugh.
We were tense.
[grunting]
[Titan] It was like our last hope.
It was the only way.
[thunder rumbling]
[James] I could just
really feel the interest
in what was happening
day after day after day.
In time, it became like a mini village
in the middle of the jungle
where there were
hundreds and hundreds of people.
It became a huge global phenomenon.
The fate of a dozen youth soccer players
and their coach in Thailand
has captivated people around the world.
Twelve youth soccer players
and their coach
have been reported missing in a cave.
Has anyone said
how long this group can survive?
They just don't know.
Rescuers have been
working around the clock
pumping thousands of gallons of water
out of that cave
so they can get better access
and find the group inside.
I remember, we got there.
I think most people just thought
they'd be gone.
I think that was really what it was.
Like, surely, they can't be alive.
But what was happening in those early days
was that they were trying
to pump the water out.
And then they'd send in the Navy SEALs.
But, basically, the current
was so strong, they just couldn't get in.
And that's when
they asked for international help.
Yesterday, we said every minute counts.
Today, every half a minute,
every ten seconds
all count to save the boys' lives.
But we are still unable
to fight against the water.
Today we have experts on site
who have years of experience
cave diving around the world.
[Apakorn] There were many moving parts
for this mission.
I think there were around 8,000 people.
There were divers
from the US, Australia, and China.
[man] So, there's this group
of volunteer cave divers.
A very… kind of desperate bunch
of oddballs from all around the world.
So, very early on, I just said,
"Look, if there's anything
we can do from Australia
with manpower
or… or phone advice or anything,
uh, just let us know,
and I can help facilitate that."
But we asked and nothing happened…
[Richard] Rick Stanton and John Volanthen
are two very well-known cave divers
at the elite level in this sport.
My dialogue with Rick had started
a few days before we actually left
to go over to Thailand.
The description of the cave from Rick
and John was that it was fully in flood.
The cave was essentially impenetrable
by the divers.
[thrilling music playing]
The Thai Navy SEALs and Ben Reymenants
and one of Ben's dive buddies
were involved
in laying some lines early on in the cave.
But the information we were receiving
from a few people like Ben on the ground
was that the conditions were really dire.
[Ben] Make no mistake.
In a normal situation,
I would have never jumped in there.
Out of the question.
[water sloshing]
Strong currents and zero visibility.
I was really not very hopeful.
[Apakorn] The cave was complex.
It was dark.
We had to lay the line.
The first team went in.
They laid the ropes as they went.
They came back when they reached the end.
And the next team would go in,
and continue laying the lines.
Rotating around the clock,
the British divers, they were laying rope.
Then the Navy SEALs, then us,
and rotating, literally, around the clock.
We had to get in there.
We needed to find the kids.
We had to rescue the boys.
[water flowing]
[Eak] The fifth, sixth,
and seventh day were all the same.
[curious music playing]
[boy] What's up with the light?
[Titan] Our flashlights were about to die.
We were worried we wouldn't be able
to do anything without them.
[Tle] We kept digging.
All we did was dig, sit,
and drink water, that's it.
If we stayed still, we would lose hope.
If we kept digging,
we might have a chance.
[indistinct chatter]
[kids chatter in distance]
As we were digging, we all heard sounds.
I heard kids playing and crying.
-[kids chattering]
-[rooster crowing]
I heard a rooster crow.
And some of the boys heard dogs.
[dog barking]
We had no idea where they came from,
but we heard them.
Our brains were foggy.
[in Thai] You okay?
Hey. Come on.
[Eak in English]
If anyone was feeling down,
they would help cheer each other up.
[emotional music playing]
I'd tell them, "Someone is coming
to rescue us. We are going to survive."
"We're not going to die here."
Tee consoled us, gave us hope.
I had to make sure they would survive.
I brought them in here,
so I had to get them out.
[water dripping, flowing]
I missed my mother and family.
They slept in my arms,
next to me on both sides.
[emotional music continues]
We held each other as we slept.
It was like hugging my family.
It felt good.
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
I couldn't sleep.
So I asked my husband,
"What are we going to do if he dies?"
I wasn't able to eat for about five days.
I'm worried about my son.
I wonder what he's doing in there.
-[reporter] How have you been doing?
-I've been so stressed out.
[reporter]
What do you want to tell your son?
I want to see him.
I didn't want to sleep.
They wanted me to,
so they tried to give me sleeping pills.
I didn't take them.
I was afraid that if my son came out,
I would miss it.
-[reporter] Are you still hopeful?
-It's fifty-fifty.
I felt so disheartened
whenever someone asked,
"If something happens to your son,
where will you find the money
for the funeral?"
I was so devastated.
I pray that we find the boys
no matter what happens to them.
Let us find their bodies at least.
[thunder rumbling]
It can be said that as of now,
the mission hasn't been successful.
People are anxious.
Today, Phra Khuva Boonchum,
who is Chiang Rai's most respectable monk,
has been invited here.
He has come to perform the rituals
to beg for forgiveness
and to open the cave entrance.
[cameras clicking]
Phra Khuva Boonchum came to free
the spirits and say a prayer for them.
Legend has it that Khuva Boonchum
was Jao Mae's loved one in a past life.
Before Khuva Boonchum came,
it rained all day.
It rained heavily.
But as soon as he came, the rain stopped.
[all chanting]
[Patchanee] When Phra Khuva Boonchum
arrived, he meditated.
He said the kids were fine.
They were together.
They were alive, they weren't dead.
I stopped crying
because I was told my son was all right.
I was happy.
-[man 1] Let's go. All set.
-[man 2] Exit on the right.
[man 1] Go right.
[bell tolling]
Let's pray for the children
who have been missing for the past week.
They were praying all around the world.
[kids praying]
It was a huge amount of good karma.
It came from everywhere.
[singing devotional song]
[prayer call]
[chanting]
[water dripping]
[foreboding music playing]
[Eak] By the ninth day,
we almost had no energy left.
[tense music playing]
We were on the edge of life and death.
[Mix] Eak worked harder than anyone
to try to get us out.
[grunting]
[Titan] His hands were shredded.
[Eak] I was a mess on the inside.
It got to be too much while I was digging,
so I would cry secretly.
[grunts]
I didn't want them to feel my weakness.
[sobbing]
I was afraid people would forget me.
That they might have thought,
"These 13 kids weren't going to make it."
And they would forget about us.
[Tle] We were all in really bad shape.
Everyone was sitting around
hugging each other, ready to give up.
We thought, "At this point,
we don't care if we die."
[solemn music playing]
Some of them said,
"Whoever dies first will be eaten."
If anyone died, that person would
become food for their friends
so that their friends would survive.
That night, I went to sleep
and I started saying,
"Tomorrow, if we still
can't get through, that's it."
[tense music playing]
[breathing weakly]
[Mark] My body couldn't take it anymore.
I was lying in one position.
Curled up and hugging myself.
[ominous music playing]
I couldn't think.
Everyone was thinking,
"This is probably our last day."
It was like I was dying.
[shivering]
[Mark] Around that time,
our batteries were about to run out.
So Eak told us to turn off the flashlights
and just be with each other.
[flashlight clicks]
-[water flowing]
-[breathing weakly]
[breathing shakily]
[Eak] Then, I heard something.
[water bubbling]
It sounded like… air bubbles.
[bubbling]
Then I heard what sounded like, "Hello."
It was like a force had woken me.
[suspenseful music playing]
The hunger and exhaustion were gone.
[music continues]
[Tee] Everyone was shocked.
We rushed down.
I said, "Hurry, before they leave!"
[music continues]
[Titan] I almost fell into the water
when I jumped down.
I cried. I cried.
[John] Here, put your hand.
-Thank you.
-Hello. Thank you.
[John] How… How many of you?
-[Adul] Thirteen.
-[John] Thirteen?
-[Adul] Yes, thirteen.
-[John] Brilliant.
[Adul] Yeah, yeah.
[boy 1] Hey, somebody ask him for food.
We were so happy.
Someone came to rescue us.
[chuckles] I didn't know what to say.
I was so grateful
someone finally came for us.
[John] You have been here 10 days.
You're very strong.
-[Adul] Strong.
-[John] Very strong.
-[boy 2] Who can speak English?
-[Adul] We hungry!
[John] I know. I understand. We'll come.
[boy 3 in Thai] He knows.
He'll come back again.
[John in English] Okay? We'll come.
[boy 3] He's going to take a picture.
[boy 4] Come here. Let's move back.
[boy 1] Tell him we're hungry.
[Adul] I already did.
He said he understood.
He brought some chocolate.
"Should we ask him? Should we ask?"
But nobody dared to ask him.
It was freaking hilarious. [chuckles]
-I am very happy.
-[John] We… We are happy too.
[Adul] Yes. Thank you so much.
-Thank you so much.
-[John] Okay.
[Eak] I was proud.
I was so proud of the boys
If the boys hadn't been strong enough
mentally as well as physically,
they probably wouldn't have survived
to be rescued.
[John] Tomorrow, many of us come.
[Adul] Okay, thank you.
[in Thai] They said we should wait here.
[in English] The diver said to wait here.
That Thai divers were coming.
[Adul] Hurry.
When I heard that, I was confused.
I thought the foreign diver
was getting us out,
but he already dove away.
[pensive music playing]
-[cop 1] Please let us through.
-[cop 2] Police.
-[cop 1] Stand aside please.
-[man] Be careful.
I saw people cheering.
So I told her, "Let's go check."
[all cheering]
BIGKREN
I was so happy.
[all cheering]
[In] We were hugging and cheering.
He's coming home.
We felt alive again.
It was like the sky had opened.
[all cheering]
[people cheering]
I felt relieved.
It was like a flower had bloomed.
It was such a relief.
I was happier than I'd ever been before.
I was overjoyed.
[all clamoring]
Press conference is starting.
All 13 boys are safe.
[crowd cheering]
MISSING THAI BOYS MIRACULOUSLY FOUND ALIVE
After ten days missing,
they have been found alive.
Rescue workers have found
12 boys and their soccer coach alive.
We just got the news that the boys
have been found. It's incredible news.
[all cheering]
[uplifting music playing]
[Eak] That night, we all celebrated.
[Mix] We hugged each other. We sang songs.
We weren't stressed or scared anymore.
[Eak] Getting to that point
after such a stressful time
felt like a weight
had been lifted off my shoulders.
We made it.
Everything we had done was worth it.
I only thought about
what was waiting for us.
[birds chirping]
-[reporter] Are they all okay?
-They are.
[reporter] Will you send in
a mental health counselor?
For their safety,
we're first sending in a SEAL team.
[man] Let's help move the tanks.
I could hear the rescue workers.
They said, "You know,
you're famous around the world."
We all thought, "Really?"
We were just country kids.
I couldn't believe it.
[man] You still don't believe me?
[Tle] We were getting food.
The only thing I thought about was,
"Food is coming." [chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[Titan] That day,
we got to eat these pouches.
[Mark] Everyone was a little disappointed.
The food wasn't very good.
We just ate to survive.
Is everybody okay?
[Titan] When they came,
I asked, "How are we gonna get out?
"The water level hasn't dropped."
They weren't sure yet.
They would let us know what to do.
[in Thai] What's your name?
[Eak in English]
A group of four rescue workers
stayed behind with the kids.
[indistinct chatter]
Who's that in the dark blue T-shirt?
Who is that?
-Ae's kid.
-It's Titan.
[man] Look at Titan sleeping.
I cried when I saw how thin my son was.
-I almost didn't recognize him.
At least he was safe.
[tense music playing]
[Apakorn] We couldn't stay happy for long,
there were still challenges ahead.
The next thing we needed to figure out
was creating a strategy
to get the kids out safely.
[Craig] For the Thai government,
they didn't know what to do.
And that's certainly
not a criticism of the Thais,
because any country in the world
wouldn't have had a… a plan for this.
It was a situation
that hadn't been experienced before.
-[cameras clicking]
-[indistinct chatter]
[Richard] There are a lot
of very experienced cave divers worldwide
who would have been
up to the task of getting to the point
where they could assist
with rescuing the kids.
But the one thing that set us apart
from many others
was the… the medical skills
we could also bring, uh, to this rescue,
and obviously, as an anesthetist
and as a vet with anesthesia experience,
you know, that, uh, was
a very important asset for us to have.
[gentle music playing]
The risk of diving out
conscious boys was immense.
The likelihood
was that those boys would panic.
And panic is death, basically.
[in Thai] Three hundred is still…
[Apakorn in English]
We thought of different methods.
I even thought that maybe we would
have to wait for the water to drop,
which would have taken four months.
In the meantime,
we would send in food and water.
[indistinct chatter]
[Adul] I was shocked when I heard
about the plan for us to stay there
until the water level dropped
or until the end of the season.
I thought, "What?
Why do we have to wait that long?"
[indistinct chatter]
I felt discouraged.
[pensive music playing]
[Craig] As it was thought about more,
obviously the conditions
weren't all that sanitary in there,
and that became a lot worse
once the boys were eating
because that has inevitable products.
So they were likely to be
getting sick, getting infections with,
you know,
beyond the reach of…of medical help.
It was going to be
a fairly slow and very unpleasant death.
[Richard] So, you know, when all these
other plans and ideas fell away,
only one solution was left.
And that… that was
sedating the children and diving them out.
You don't even need to be
a cave diver or an anesthetist
to realize that the concept
of rendering a child unconscious,
pushing their head underwater,
and then three hours later,
expecting that when
you reemerge from the water,
that those children
are still gonna be alive,
it's just a preposterous idea.
[Craig] There were three things
that I could see
would inevitably happen to these children.
The masks would fill with water,
and they'd drown.
Their airway would obstruct,
and they'd suffocate.
And the final thing I was worried about,
if those two things
didn't take the lives of the kids,
with the 23-degree temperature
of the water and the air in the cave,
over the course
of three hours, under anesthesia,
their core temperature would
steadily but surely head down south,
and they'd slowly freeze
to death in the cave.
I think, in the end,
I justified it to myself by saying,
"If I do this anesthetic,
they're probably going to die."
"But at least
they'll be asleep when they die."
[indistinct chatter]
[Apakorn] We had to
inform the parents of our plan
and they had to accept the risks.
There was a possibility
that some of these kids might not survive.
It was risky either way,
and they told me
I had to sign a consent form.
If I didn't,
the SEAL team couldn't get them out.
[rain pattering]
If we waited for the rainy season to end,
it would be three or four months.
The chance would be zero.
If we took a risk to get them out,
it was at least fifty-fifty.
We had to make a decision.
It was a tough call.
[Ei Khan] I decided to sign it.
It was a very difficult decision.
I was scared.
It wasn't like we were happy
when they informed us.
I wasn't happy. I was scared.
I was afraid they wouldn't get out.
-[water dripping]
-[indistinct chatter]
[Eak] They phrased it
like they were trying to make us think
of diving as something fun.
They didn't want to stress the kids out.
[man in Thai]
We have to wait for level three.
We have to wait
for the water level to drop.
[in English] I wanted to dive.
[Mix] I was excited to do it.
[Titan] I had no idea it was that risky.
Back then all I thought about
was getting out.
That was it.
[crickets chirping]
[pensive music playing]
Because you had to dive a long distance
to get to them,
you used the entire oxygen tank.
When you dived back,
you had to use a tank that was put there
to replace the one you had used up.
[man] The starting point
is only 300 meters from this spot.
But here the water is falling down
from the cave walls.
We have to dive down to get through.
Stay tuned for tomorrow.
We can do it.
We SEALs can do it. We never back down.
His name was Saman Gunan.
He was a petty officer in the SEALs.
That day, he had volunteered
to place the equipment.
While diving back he lost consciousness.
[somber music playing]
He never woke up.
[woman] I found out in the morning.
I texted someone
who was in the same department.
They…
They said he had passed.
[women sobbing]
[in Thai] I just saw him.
[wailing]
[in English] That day,
they sent him on a plane.
I was delirious.
I kept calling out his name.
I kept calling out to him
and saying to myself,
"It's not true. It's not true."
I knew he had to do the rescue mission.
These boys were still in there.
I understood that.
PETTY OFFICER SAMAN GUNAN
BORN DECEMBER 23,1980 - DIED JULY 6, 2018
I remember just thinking, "If it's killed
a professional former Navy SEAL,
there's no way
these boys are gonna make it out."
[boys shivering]
[tense music playing]
[Craig] We all turned up thinking
there was really very little prospect
of any success in this.
[Eak] We were able to breathe normally,
but it was getting tougher.
[labored breathing]
They said the amount of oxygen
was getting lower inside the cave.
I was quite worried about
what would happen if they ran out of air.
And in the following week,
there would be more rain coming in
that would create more risks.
[James] With the water rising
and oxygen going down,
they had no choice
but to start the rescue mission.
Today, we are fully prepared.
Today is our D-Day.
Authorities say that high-risk operation
is now under way.
Just minutes ago
the local governor called it "D-Day."
It's a rescue attempt
"like no other," they call it.
It was the first time
this method was used in the world.
[suspenseful music playing]
Just about 9:00, 9:30,
someone just announced, "We're on."
Where the boys were
is a little bit over two kilometers.
[Richard] So we knew these kids
were going to have
a three-hour journey out of the cave.
[music continues]
[water sloshing]
I remember as we approached, I thought,
"Here we are. We finally made it through
the cave and they're all going to die."
That's when this was
all about to become a real thing.
[indistinct chatter]
The kids were amazingly very accepting.
You know, at that stage,
we could've told them
they were gonna be taken out
on a flying carpet,
and they would have agreed to it.
They were just so desperate
to be out of that place by then.
The funny thing was they decided
the kids who lived the farthest distance
from the entrance of the cave
would go first.
Once they got out, the kids planned
to ride their bikes back home
and get something to eat.
I asked to be the last to leave.
[in Thai] Come on, let's go. Ready?
[Richard in English]
The first child that I anesthetized,
you know,
I can still remember very clearly.
It's hard to describe what it feels like,
pushing an unconscious child's face
into the water.
That's about as low
as you can go, I think.
Closely followed by, you know,
restraining someone's hands
behind their backs.
The implications of what
I might be doing to these kids,
and that… that might be
signing their death warrant.
[water bubbles popping]
[Craig] Sixteen hundred meters
or so, they were diving.
The boys then
had to come out of the water,
be carried across, uh, the dry land…
[Apakorn] The British diver told us
he would be responsible
for bringing the kids to us
at the third chamber.
From there, we had to come up with a plan
to bring them to the cave entrance.
From the third chamber,
we used 200 people.
[in Thai] Be careful.
[in English] We just waited all day
for news. So it was full on.
[SEAL 1 in Thai] Hey, left, right.
[SEAL 2] Left, right, left, right.
[tense music playing]
[in English] I was the second out.
The needle they used hurt a lot.
I blacked out.
[Saksipong] The first group
was the most at risk.
We wished for a miracle.
[indistinct chatter]
[SEAL] Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Okay.
[in Thai] Go, go, go.
[indistinct chatter]
Slowly.
[speaking indistinctly]
[solemn music playing]
[in English]
The rescue team came out so quietly.
I wondered if the kids
had actually survived.
That is the first ambulance.
The whole world
has been waiting to see this.
[helicopter whirring]
[dramatic music playing]
[siren wailing]
[Narongsak] After ten days of waiting,
we finally get to see the Wild Boars.
[crowd cheering]
MR.NARONGSAK OSATANAKORN,
HEAD OF THE JOINT COMMAND CENTRE
I was so happy.
FOURTH MEMBER OF THE WILD BOARS
BEING TAKEN TO HOSPITAL
Reports from Northern Thailand say
at least four boys have been brought out.
The first rescue was perfect.
It was an incredible day. We did it.
[tense music playing]
[Eak] When the last day came,
the plan changed.
I had to go first. I was like, "What?"
They wanted to take out the biggest first
and the smallest last.
I started to feel uneasy.
I thought that if I got out first
and the parents found out,
they might be mad
that I left their kids behind.
It wouldn't be good.
I didn't know how I was
going to explain it to their parents.
I sat with Dr. Harris.
While I was looking at him,
the needle was stuck into my thigh.
[imitates needle injecting]
I started thanking the rescue workers.
I told them, "Please take care
of the kids. I'll see you outside."
[gentle piano music playing]
[SEAL in Thai] Are you okay?
[Richard in English] The last boy
on the last day turned out to be Mark.
[Mark] It felt lonely.
I was the only one left.
There was no one to tell me
to get out safely and cheer me on.
But I thought, "It's fine."
Then I realize being last is cool.
I get to finish the story.
Mark was the last one.
I thought, "It doesn't matter if he's last
as long as he comes out safely."
[gentle instrumental music playing]
When I woke up,
I felt like I was born again.
I was lying there naked.
And then, they were…
taking such good care of me
as if I was a baby.
[all applauding]
[crowd cheering]
I was so happy. I didn't know what to say.
Mission accomplished.
All 12 boys and their coach
have been successfully rescued.
[audience cheering]
You can only imagine.
I mean, what, as you say, a miracle.
I've never seen an event
bring a world together like this.
[crowd applauding]
The hero in all of this
is everyone from around the world.
We did something
no one expected we could do
for the first time in history.
-[siren wailing]
-[crowd applauding and cheering]
It's our Mission Possible.
[reporter] There's the ambulance
carrying Coach Eak.
Coach Eak!
-[stretcher wheels rattling]
-[music continues]
It was a miracle that everyone survived.
Some of the parents came up to me.
As they were walking up, I was like,
"All right. Whatever happens, happens."
I had prepared myself. I would take it.
They said they would go to sleep
holding each other's hands.
Well, seeing them,
I felt as if they were all my children.
They loved each other.
Some people criticized Eak.
But for us, we're like family.
We understand each other.
We know it was an accident.
They came up to me and said,
"Stay strong, Eak."
"Don't worry about anything.
Everybody understands."
When I heard that, I was like, "Okay."
All my worries were gone. [sighs]
[gentle music playing]
When I saw my mother for the first time,
I was surprised.
I wanted to get up and walk to her
and hug her, but I couldn't.
I had no strength in my legs,
so my mother ran to me and hugged me.
The first thing I saw
was my parents crying.
They were crying tears of joy
because I made it out.
I hugged him and said,
"Tee, don't do this again."
"You have to tell me
where you're going. I love you."
We were ecstatic. We hugged each other.
We were just so happy.
I remember it to this day.
When I saw my parents, I started crying.
I was still thinking
that it could be a dream.
[Patchanee] Tle said he thought
he would never get to see us again.
When he said that,
I had a lump in my throat.
-[Saksipong] We couldn't say anything.
-I couldn't say anything.
[clipper buzzing]
[Titan] We saw Officer Sam's picture.
I got quiet. I was stunned.
Officer Sam came to rescue us,
but he didn't get to come out with us.
Why did someone have to die
because we went into the cave?
[somber music playing]
When I saw these boys, I was proud.
What my husband did, was a success.
I never blame them because I understand.
No one wanted it to happen.
What I wish for them is
to live a normal life
and to follow their dreams
just like every other kid.
I just want them to continue
chasing their dreams.
[solemn music playing]
[inaudible]
I never think I'm a celebrity.
I'm just a kid who got stuck in a cave
and got famous
because other people rescued me.
But because this happened to me,
I've had to adjust, to be more polite,
so that when people look at me…
they will be happy
that the boy they saved is a good person.
[solemn music continues]
[inaudible]
We can't just do whatever we want anymore.
We have to be good kids.
We have to study hard.
We can't let the people
who rescued us down.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Thank you.
[all applauding]
I'll never give up.
You did great.
[all] Wild Boars!
-[kid] Wild Boars!
-[all laugh]
When I found out how many people
were involved in helping us,
I didn't know how
I could ever repay this act of kindness.
There is just no way I could make up
for it in this lifetime.
[Thai music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[Eak] Hold the position.
Down! Up!
Down!
[groans]
[Eak] Down!
Again?
[whistle blows]
-[Titan] I'm tired.
-[Eak] I don't care!
Tao, don't let a younger kid beat you.
Don't give up.
Tao, go faster.
That was the last one.
Okay, send one person out.
[Thai song continues]
[song fades]
[gentle music playing]
[music fades]
[gentle instrumental music playing]